<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>People on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/people/</link>
    <description>Recent content in People on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 17:41:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay participates in Health 2.0 Valencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, participated yesterday in the Health 2.0 event organized by InnDEA, and featuring Tellmegen, eKuore and Kanteron, in Las Naves (Valencia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Memarian to Join Kanteron as President and Chief Commercial Officer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/john-memarian-to-join-kanteron-as-president-and-chief-commercial-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 15:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/john-memarian-to-join-kanteron-as-president-and-chief-commercial-officer/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems USA, Inc. today announced that John Memarian, President of International Businesses at Merge (recently acquired by IBM), will be joining Kanteron in a newly created position, as President and Chief Commercial Officer, joining the executive team and reporting directly to Founder and CEO Jorge Cortell.
Memarian will be responsible for executing the commercial strategy and business development of Kanteron, overseeing activities relating to marketing, sales, product development and customer service, to drive business growth and market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th EU Health Innovation event at Microsoft’s Brussels EBC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 20:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</guid>
      <description>This Tuesday and Wednesday Kanteron Systems was invited to participate in Microsoft’s 5th Health Innovation event, in the Exhibition Area, along with 5 other selected partners.
Titled “EmpoweringHealth: the journey towards more personalized, productive, collaborative and predictive health services &amp;amp; systems” it took place at the Microsoft Executive Briefing Center in Brussels.Kanteron Systems‘ CEO, Jorge Cortell, participated in the round table “Medical Imaging Storage in the Cloud”, moderated by Kelly Limonte (Microsoft UK Healthcare Team), and in the Expert Panel “The future of preventive and predictive health powered by data in the intelligent cloud”, along with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The London Stock Exchange invites Kanteron to participate in the market opening ceremony</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/the-london-stock-exchange-invites-kanteron-to-participate-in-the-market-opening-ceremony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/the-london-stock-exchange-invites-kanteron-to-participate-in-the-market-opening-ceremony/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, November 6th, Kanteron Systems‘ CEO Jorge Cortell was invited by Marcus Stuttard, head of AIM (the London Stock Exchange‘s growth market), to participate in the London Stock Exchange market opening ceremony, which takes place daily at 8:00 am.

The ceremony offers companies joining London Stock Exchange‘s markets the opportunity to mark their success on the day of their admission. The event was followed by drinks and breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM features Kanteron Systems in an ad</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-an-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 19:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-an-ad/</guid>
      <description>IBM has produced an advertising featuring Kanteron Systems, titled: &amp;ldquo;More precise diagnostics with Kanteron and IBM Cloud&amp;rdquo;.
Here is the IBM press release.
The ad, featuring Kanteron COO Juan Tatay and Kanteron CIO Alvaro Gonzalez, was filmed in Kanteron‘s offices in Valencia and Madrid (Spain), for the IBM Business Connectevent.
Watch the video here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two top level scientists joined Kanteron Systems’ team today</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/two-top-level-scientists-joined-kanteron-systems-team-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 23:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/two-top-level-scientists-joined-kanteron-systems-team-today/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Raminder Singh and Santiago Gala join Kanteron’s team.
Dr Raminderpal Singh has joined Kanteron Systems as Strategic Advisor.
Dr. Singh was until now Business Development &amp;amp; Strategy Lead at IBM Research-Genomic Medicine. His experience in Venture Capital at 3i Group, as well as his international experience with healthcare organizations in countries like Singapore, UK, and Canada, and with deals and partnerships in USA, China, India, Russia, and Brazil fit perfectly well with Kanteron’s momentum of explosive international growth and exploration of new partnerships and corporate options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay and Alvaro Gonzalez presentation at IBM Cloud event in Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/06/juan-tatay-and-alvaro-gonzalez-presentation-at-ibm-cloud-event-in-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 22:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/06/juan-tatay-and-alvaro-gonzalez-presentation-at-ibm-cloud-event-in-madrid/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday June 2 Kanteron System‘ Alvaro González – CIO and Juan Tatay – COO presented Kanteron Systems‘ experience with IBM at the IBM Cloud event &amp;ldquo;Dream it! Build it!&amp;rdquo; in Madrid. #IBMCloudDreamIt
Kanteron‘s success case was presented along two other companies: Evolufarma and SKIOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems seeks candidate to join Dubai team</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-seeks-candidate-to-join-dubai-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-seeks-candidate-to-join-dubai-team/</guid>
      <description>We are seeking a solution architect, CTO level: an energetic person, with technical knowledge in network administration (especially in a hospital setting), complete English fluency, and good communication skills. We offer annual contract, but a willingness to stay in Dubai after training in Valencia (Spain) for at least 3 years is required.
For further info please contact hr@kanteron.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in the VII Biomedical Engineering Workshop</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-vii-biomedical-engineering-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 21:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-vii-biomedical-engineering-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Organizedby the Inter-University (Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia, Spain) MSc. in Biomedical Engineering, the VII Biomedical Engineering Workshop will take place February 3-6, 2015.
Juan Tatay, COO, and Jorge Cortell, Founder and CEO of Kanteron Systems, will talk about &amp;ldquo;Computational paradigm shift in medical imaging&amp;rdquo;. Juan Tatay will be present during the event in Valencia, while Jorge Cortell will participate via videoconference from New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems collaborates in world‘s first Scientific Photography Postgraduate course</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-collaborates-in-worlds-first-scientific-photography-postgraduate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 10:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-collaborates-in-worlds-first-scientific-photography-postgraduate-course/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will collaborate with the world‘s first _ Scientific Photography Postgraduate course_ at the University of Alcala (Spain) October 6 to November 21, 2014.
The lectures will be taught in the classroom‘s School of Sciences. The practical classes are taught in the Cabinet of Scientific Photography lab, Cell Biology lab and National Museum of Natural Sciences.
The course involves 20 teachers selected among the best Spanish and foreign specialists (including Kanteron Systems‘ CIO, Alvaro Gonzalez) who will teach 30 different specialties handling equipment worth over 1,000 million euros, thanks to the collaboration of the Ministry of Defense, National Museum of Natural Sciences, Astronomical Observatory La Hita, various hospitals, universities and other entities like Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay presents at the 2014 International Conference on Biomedical and Health Informatics</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/juan-tatay-presents-at-the-2014-international-conference-on-biomedical-and-health-informatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 20:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/juan-tatay-presents-at-the-2014-international-conference-on-biomedical-and-health-informatics/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay (Kanteron Systems‘ COO) presented Kanteron Systems‘ solutions and vision at the 2014 BHI (International Conference on Biomedical and Health Informatics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to deliver a lecture at the VI Biomedical Engineering Meeting</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, February 6 2014 at 16h, Kanteron Systems‘ Juan Tatay (Director) and Carlos Villanueva (R&amp;amp;D Engineer) will deliver the lecture “Precise diagnostics for personalized medicine: medical imaging and big data” at the Cajal Room, 1st floor, School of Medicine, University of Valencia (Spain) within the VI Biomedical Engineering Meetingof the Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia‘s Official Interuniversity Master Degree in Biomedical Engineering. Other lectures will be delivered by Philips Research, Indra Sistemas and General Electric Healthcare amongst others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Cortell wins Executive of the Year Bronze Award in 2013 International Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/jorge-cortell-wins-executive-of-the-year-bronze-award-in-2013-international-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/jorge-cortell-wins-executive-of-the-year-bronze-award-in-2013-international-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems Founder &amp;amp; CEO, was named the winner of a Bronze Award in the Executive of the Year – Health Products &amp;amp; Services category in the 10th Annual International Business Awardstoday.
More than 3,300 nominations from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were considered in several categories, including Management Team of the Year, Corporate Social Responsibility Program of the Year, among others. Jorge Cortell won (bronze) in the Executive of the Year for Health Products &amp;amp; Services category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron COO interviewed by Inndea</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/05/kanteron-coo-interviewed-by-inndea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 00:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/05/kanteron-coo-interviewed-by-inndea/</guid>
      <description>Spanish magazine Inndea interviews Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems COO. Read the whole interview (Spanish) here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello to deliver two conferences at Colombia Radiology Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-to-deliver-two-conferences-at-colombia-radiology-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 08:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-to-deliver-two-conferences-at-colombia-radiology-congress/</guid>
      <description>During the Colombia Radiology Congress(August 4th &amp;amp; 5th, Cartagena de Indias, Colombia, Congress Center), Kanteron System‘s Marco Schiavottiello will deliver three conferences:
II Latin-American Congreso of Diagnostic Imaging Technologist, Academic Program, Barahona 1 room:
 Saturday 4th, 14:30-15:30: &amp;ldquo;DICOM for technologist&amp;rdquo; Saturday 4th, 16:00-16:30: &amp;ldquo;The rol of the technologist in the integration of new IT solutions in the radiology department&amp;rdquo; Saturday 4th, 17:00-17:30: &amp;ldquo;Image Post process: new technologies and the extended rol of the technologist&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Alvaro Gonzalez and Jorge Cortell talk about healthcare IT security at HOPE9</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘ Alvaro González(CTO) and Jorge Cortell(CEO) spoke today about &amp;ldquo;Digital Security in Health Care Institutions&amp;rdquo; during Hackers On Planet Earth number 9, New York, one of the most creative and diverse hacker events in the world (since 1994).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivers Master Class at London event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivered a Master Class about the NHS Great Ormond Street‘s successful implementation by Kanteron Systems of a new Cardiac PACS, at London event &amp;ldquo;A patient centered approach&amp;rdquo; (Central Hall Westminster, Storey‘s Gate) July 4th, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems passes yearly quality audit with 0 non-conformities</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-passes-yearly-quality-audit-with-0-non-conformities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-passes-yearly-quality-audit-with-0-non-conformities/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems has received the audit report from independent auditors Bureau Veritas International, regarding our ISO 9001:2008 Quality System, and the results are perfect: 0 major non-conformities, and 0 minor non-conformities.
Congratulations to everybody in the team, led by Juan Tatay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems USA‘s new office in Times Square (New York)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/12/kanteron-systems-usas-new-office-in-times-square-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 18:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/12/kanteron-systems-usas-new-office-in-times-square-new-york/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems USA is proud to announce the inauguration of our new offices in the heart of Times Square, New York (USA).1515 BroadwayLocated on 1515 Broadway, in the Viacom and MTV headquarters building, our new offices provide the perfect venue to offer our customers in the USA and Canada the best support.Vivian and Felicia, 11th floor reception, will welcome you to Kanteron Systems USAWith plenty of space for leisure and informal meeting areas,7th floor cafeteriakitchen and water bar11th floor bar (Christmas party!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARSOR v2.0 sensors ready</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/arsor-v2.0-sensors-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/arsor-v2.0-sensors-ready/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the work of Kanteron Systems hardware development team lead by Engineer C. Villanueva, the integrated sensors for ARSOR version 2.0 are ready.
After full testing is undertaken at CHIP Hospital‘s Operating Rooms in Malaga (Spain), full production will go into effect before the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello interviewed in Venezuela Radio Station</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-interviewed-in-venezuela-radio-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 21:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-interviewed-in-venezuela-radio-station/</guid>
      <description>Marco Schiavottiello (Kanteron Systems‘ Product Manager), interviewed about IT solutions for digital medicla images by TecnologiaHechaPalabra, radio station broadcasting on 95.5fm, and belonging to the Venezuelan healthcare web portal most visited in Latin America.
The audio can be listened to here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invited to Tech Ventures Conference – U. of Cambridge</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kanteron-systems-invited-to-tech-ventures-conference-u.-of-cambridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kanteron-systems-invited-to-tech-ventures-conference-u.-of-cambridge/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited to participate in:
Technology Ventures Conference 2011
Ideas Economy: Changing the World by Connecting Ideas
9th of June 2011 – Cambridge Union, Cambridge, UK
Hosted by The Cambridge University Technology and Enterprise Club to enhance the entrepreneurial spirit amongst academics and students, by facilitating interaction between industry experts and students. Investors and the industries that support them in turn gain access to the vibrant research and entrepreneurial communities at the University of Cambridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitor admiring our work</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/competitor-admiring-our-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 00:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/competitor-admiring-our-work/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Kanteron‘s technician: Images seem to have arrived correctly, would you like to check anything in particular? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; **MultinationalX**‘s technician: It would be nice to know if you have received all the data without errors or if I have to take any information field out in case your workstation does not support it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Kanteron‘s technician: Here you have the transmission log, everything correct, and if you press this button, you can see the whole associated metadata list, including your data from **MultinationalX**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wishing well to Japan</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/03/wishing-well-to-japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 09:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/03/wishing-well-to-japan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems nominated for the 2011 European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-the-2011-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 19:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-the-2011-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased and honored to announce that Kanteron Systems has been selected for inclusion in the European Business Awards.
Every year the European Business Awards research team spend six months analysing over 15,000 companies across Europe to seek out the very best businesses that demonstrate the guiding principles of the Awards:
· Commercial success
· Innovation
· Business ethics
The award nomination research team &amp;ldquo;were particularly impressed with the success Jorge Cortell has had in leading and driving Kanteron Systems and the impact this has had across the business, having won the 4th Edition of Premio Emprendedor XXI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDS named Distributor of the Year 2010, IBM named Reseller of the Year 2010</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/bds-named-distributor-of-the-year-2010-ibm-named-reseller-of-the-year-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 12:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/bds-named-distributor-of-the-year-2010-ibm-named-reseller-of-the-year-2010/</guid>
      <description>It is a pleasure to announce the winner of Kanteron‘s Distributor of the Year Award (Lima, Peru) and Reseller of the Year Award (IBM Peru).  It has been a close call, since competition was strong, but our Peru distributor and IBM deserve it since they have managed one very complex and successful project that joined Kanteron Systems, our Peru distributor and IBM in the most ambitious large-scale outsourced distributed medical imaging PACS in South America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron’s co-founder and President finalist for Spanish Young Businessman of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/11/kanterons-co-founder-and-president-finalist-for-spanish-young-businessman-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 10:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/11/kanterons-co-founder-and-president-finalist-for-spanish-young-businessman-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems co-founder and President, has been named finalist for the Spanish Young Businessman of the Year award by the Young Businessmen Confederation of Spain, sponsored by Santander Bank. Source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marco Schiavottiello (Kanteron Systems) awarded the IET 2010 Dennis Hill Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/08/marco-schiavottiello-kanteron-systems-awarded-the-iet-2010-dennis-hill-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 23:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/08/marco-schiavottiello-kanteron-systems-awarded-the-iet-2010-dennis-hill-award/</guid>
      <description>Mr. Marco Schiavottiello has been awarded the IET 2010 Dennis Hill Award for his work on “iCHEST: Development of a Web Application for Chest Radiography”
&amp;ldquo;The Dennis Hill Award recognises outstanding work in the field of healthcare technologies. It is awarded annually to a student on a taught MSc programme. This award is presented in memory of Professor Dennis Hill, a pioneering researcher and practitioner in many areas of endeavour, particularly in relation to anaesthesia and intensive care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron programmer’s discover (and fix) bug in SQL MacOSX</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/10/kanteron-programmers-discover-and-fix-bug-in-sql-macosx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/10/kanteron-programmers-discover-and-fix-bug-in-sql-macosx/</guid>
      <description>Currently being reported and the solution shared, Kanteron‘s programmers, while developing new functionalities for Kanteron‘s HIS (Hospital Information Systems) discovered a bug in SQL MacOSX by which the database would randomly (upon not detecting activity for an undetermined period of time) shutdown.After a few days of hard work, a solution has been discovered, and is now being shared with the rest of the community.Long live Open Source and Free Software!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron’s founder nominated for Entrepreneur of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/kanterons-founder-nominated-for-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 22:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/kanterons-founder-nominated-for-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron System‘s founder, Jorge Cortell, was nominated today for the Entrepreneur of the Year awardby the Spanish Government. We wish him good luck! (honestly, no sucking-up here 😉</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world! (again)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/01/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2009 01:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/01/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>To make a long story short: We‘ve had a blog for a while. Then we moved the office, then the servers and the hosting. In all those changes, we left the blog behind. Now we regain the blog. Hello world&amp;hellip;again. By the way, we will be writing in English and Spanish, here and there, about this and that. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>