<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Customers on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/customers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Customers on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 18:06:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/customers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Biggest telemedicine network in South America chooses Kanteron</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/biggest-telemedicine-network-in-south-america-chooses-kanteron/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 18:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/biggest-telemedicine-network-in-south-america-chooses-kanteron/</guid>
      <description>ITMS Chile, the largest international telemedicine network in South America, has chosen Kanteron Systems as their new platform to handle thousands of studies per day of medical imaging, reporting, and collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 UK NHS hospitals choose Kanteron in less than a month</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/15-uk-nhs-hospitals-choose-kanteron-in-less-than-a-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/15-uk-nhs-hospitals-choose-kanteron-in-less-than-a-month/</guid>
      <description>In less than a month, 15 Hospital Trusts from the UK‘s National Health Service (NHS) have chosen Kanteron Systems‘ platform (TMIS) to integrate medical imaging and clinical genomics.
Only weeks after the general availability of Kanteron Systems source code for the NHS was announced, the following NHS Trusts have already joined the group of TMIS users around the world:
 North Bristol Trust Liverpool Heart &amp;amp; Chest Hospital NHS FT University Hospital of South Manchester Guy’s and St Thomas’ NHS Foundation Trust Newcastle upon Tyne Hospitals Addenbrooke’s Hospital | Cambridge University Hospitals NHS Greater Glasgow and Clyde University of Bradford Plymouth Hospitals NHS Trust The Royal Marsden Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust NHS Forth Valley Portsmouth Hospitals NHS Trust Salford Royal North Cumbria University Hospital NHS Trust UCLH – University College London Hospitals  Note: Previously, Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) was already a customer of Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Partners with TellMeGen for Clinical Genomics Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-partners-with-tellmegen-for-clinical-genomics-interpretation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 15:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-partners-with-tellmegen-for-clinical-genomics-interpretation/</guid>
      <description>Turn-key Solution to Provide Clinical Genomic Interpretation on Leading Precision Medicine Data Platform
LONDON (UK) – VALENCIA (Spain), July 18, 2016 —
Kanteron Systems, the leading provider of medical imaging and clinical genomics software for precision medicine, and TellMeGen, a leading provider of genomic interpretation, announce a partnership to make TellMeGen’s clinical interpretation available to hospitals through the Kanteron platform.
Clinicians need to translate molecular information and interpretation into actionable therapeutic strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General availability of Kanteron source code for NHS announced at the UK Radiology Congress 2016</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/general-availability-of-kanteron-source-code-for-nhs-announced-at-the-uk-radiology-congress-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/general-availability-of-kanteron-source-code-for-nhs-announced-at-the-uk-radiology-congress-2016/</guid>
      <description>Shawn Larson, Senior Project Manager at HSCIC, announced the general availability of Kanteron source code for the NHS on Monday, June 6, at UKRC (the largest diagnostic imaging event in the UK). The announcement was made during the session: PACS 2.0 (the next generation) has now happened – any real difference?
In conjunction with HSCIC’s OpenPACS and NHS England’s Code 4 Health / Open Source initiatives, Kanteron Systems has made the source code of its Translational Medical Information Server (TMIS) platform freely available to the NHS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems Selects Dicom Systems Unifier as Universal Enterprise Imaging Adapter</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/03/kanteron-systems-selects-dicom-systems-unifier-as-universal-enterprise-imaging-adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 22:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/03/kanteron-systems-selects-dicom-systems-unifier-as-universal-enterprise-imaging-adapter/</guid>
      <description>Campbell, CA, March 16, 2016 – Dicom Systems, Inc., an Enterprise Imaging interoperability expert, announced today its partnership with Kanteron Systems, Inc. (USA, Spain, and UK). This partnership will deliver more comprehensive, real-time patient information to specialists, enabling improved correlation of clinical data and medical imaging within one, consolidated visual context.
Kanteron Systems, the leading aggregator of Genomics, Pathology and Radiology imaging and data for multi-discipline clinical specialists, has selected Dicom Systems and its Enterprise Imaging Workflow Unifier as a universal adapter to seamlessly integrate its clinical data management solutions within any healthcare enterprise environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking agreement allows the NHS to access an innovative platform providing integrated imaging and genomic data at the point of care</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/groundbreaking-agreement-allows-the-nhs-to-access-an-innovative-platform-providing-integrated-imaging-and-genomic-data-at-the-point-of-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/groundbreaking-agreement-allows-the-nhs-to-access-an-innovative-platform-providing-integrated-imaging-and-genomic-data-at-the-point-of-care/</guid>
      <description>Healthcare information systems leader Kanteron Systems, in collaboration with the NHS National Health System (NHS) England’s Open Source and Code 4 Health Programmes, has agreed to allow the entire NHS unrestricted access to Kanteron’s medical imaging and genomic data integration platform under the custodianship of an NHS clinically led OpenPACS Code 4 Health community. The agreement was announced at RSNA – the world’s largest gathering of clinical medical imaging professionals – in Chicago (USA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron and Ver2 Digital Medicine Bring Medical Imaging and Genomics Data Integration to Middle East Markets</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/kanteron-and-ver2-digital-medicine-bring-medical-imaging-and-genomics-data-integration-to-middle-east-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/kanteron-and-ver2-digital-medicine-bring-medical-imaging-and-genomics-data-integration-to-middle-east-markets/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems and Ver2 Digital Medicine introduce the first Medical Imaging and Genomics Data Integration platform in the United Arab Emirates.
Doctors in the Middle East can now examine your symptoms, correlate them with your electronic medical records, medical imaging exams, pathology tests, and your genomic data. Doctors then instantly compare those results with the data on thousands of other individuals to deliver a detailed diagnosis — or even detect an illness before the symptoms appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHS England selects Kanteron Systems for second round of testing combinatorial innovation</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/nhs-england-selects-kanteron-systems-for-second-round-of-testing-combinatorial-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 12:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/nhs-england-selects-kanteron-systems-for-second-round-of-testing-combinatorial-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Together with the Academic Health Science Networks (AHSNs), and HM Government, NHS England has invited Kanteron Systems to the second round of their ‘test bed programme.
The test bed programme is about deploying technologies that are ready to use, in NHS settings—not about inventing new ones.
Kanteron Systems is ready to accept this challenge and deliver what the NHS has described as ‘high value innovation‘.
July 29th, at The Kia Oval, London, Kanteron Systems will meet several NHS sites interested in deploying our solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Ormond Street Hospital (NHS – London) renews contract with Kanteron Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/great-ormond-street-hospital-nhs-london-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/great-ormond-street-hospital-nhs-london-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</guid>
      <description>Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) for Children, a National Health Service (NHS) Foundation Trust in London, UK, has just renewed their services contract for a Cardiology PACS (Picture Archiving and Communication System) with Kanteron Systems.
The NHS has some of the most strict and demanding service contracts in the world. We are proud and honored that such an iconic institution in pediatric care as GOSH has been trusting Kanteron Systems for four years already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron joins forces with Hitachi Data Systems to advance personalized medicine</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-joins-forces-with-hitachi-data-systems-to-advance-personalized-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 23:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-joins-forces-with-hitachi-data-systems-to-advance-personalized-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems
Victoria Sanchis
marketing@kanteron.com
Tel: 963312287</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>everis presents the first Electronic Health Record (EHR) with Kanteron‘s clinical genomic capabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/everis-presents-the-first-electronic-health-record-ehr-with-kanterons-clinical-genomic-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 23:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/everis-presents-the-first-electronic-health-record-ehr-with-kanterons-clinical-genomic-capabilities/</guid>
      <description>• Precision Medicine: Genomic data integrated with EMRs means precise diagnostics and pharmacogenomic indications (which medications will work better in each specific patient).
• 360º View of the Patient: Radiology and Pathology imaging is only part of the picture in many cases.
• Genomic data has been, until now, the missing key piece of information in digital records for personalized medicine.
everis, an NTT Data company, announces a partnership with Kanteron Systems to provide its Next-Generation Electronic Health Record, ehCOS CLINIC, with a robust platform for clinical genomics, key to precise diagnostics and personalized medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to supply technology behind Deployable Mobile Hospitals</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-to-supply-technology-behind-deployable-mobile-hospitals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 01:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-to-supply-technology-behind-deployable-mobile-hospitals/</guid>
      <description>On February 10th, the Peruvian government awarded through public bid contract LP 013-2014-MINSA the supply of technology behind three Deployable Mobile Hospitals to Kanteron Systems.
The three Deployable Mobile Hospitals will be delivered by a consortium of companies.
 We are proud that Kanteron Systems‘ technology has been selected for this large project, which will enable the Peruvian Government to better serve its citizens through mobile hospitals deployable in remote regions, in cases of natural disasters, or in conflict zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems in Arab Health, Dubai</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems was back in Arab Healththis year (January 26-28), due to the increased interest and activity regarding Healthcare Technology in the Middle Eastern region.
Through our new partners in the region, we have over twenty projects going on in United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Iran, Iraq, Nigeria, Tanzania, and Ethiopia.Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems CEO, in the lobby of Arab Health Dubai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MD Anderson Madrid signs order for Kanteron Systems digital pathology workflow solution</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/md-anderson-madrid-signs-order-for-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-workflow-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/md-anderson-madrid-signs-order-for-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-workflow-solution/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 2000 as the first international affiliate of The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Centerin Houston (Texas), which is ranked number 2 as the best cancer center in the USA, and with facilities spanning 15,300 m2, over a hundred beds, and about 400 employees, MD Anderson Cancer Center Madridis the first fully specialized cancer care center in Spain, where patients can receive all of their diagnostic tests, inpatient and outpatient treatment, and see all of their physicians at a single site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University Hospital in Bogota updates its Kanteron Systems solution to IBM Pure Flex System</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/university-hospital-in-bogota-updates-its-kanteron-systems-solution-to-ibm-pure-flex-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 18:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/university-hospital-in-bogota-updates-its-kanteron-systems-solution-to-ibm-pure-flex-system/</guid>
      <description>The University Hospital San Ignacio (HUSI) at the Javeriana University in Bogota (Colombia) has chosen to renew the Kanteron Systems digital medical imaging solution they have been using since 2011.
This updates the PACS and RIS system to the corresponding modules of the newKanteron Systems TMIS (Translational Medical Imaging System). The new system is being installed in an IBM Pure Flex platform providing HUSI with new features, improved performance and speed, flexibility and unparalleled convenience to provide access to users through a web interface (HTML5) without installing any software (zero-footprint) and accessible from any device (responsive design).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Largest outsourced medical imaging PACS in Latin America renews contract with Kanteron Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/largest-outsourced-medical-imaging-pacs-in-latin-america-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/largest-outsourced-medical-imaging-pacs-in-latin-america-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</guid>
      <description>On Monday October 6, EsSalud – Social Security Administration of Peru – signed a renewal of services contract (number 4600044350, process number 1499E00031) with Kanteron Systems to continue supporting the largest medical imaging outsourced system in Latin America. This renewal is proof of EsSalud‘s satisfaction with a system they have been using for over 3 years now.
Hosted in IBM data center in Lima, Peru, the Kanteron PACS provides a single repository, workflow management, monitoring and security backups for all medical imaging generated by EsSalud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portuguese Hospital Distrital da Horta chooses Kanteron&#43;IBM medical imaging solution</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/portuguese-hospital-distrital-da-horta-chooses-kanteron-ibm-medical-imaging-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 11:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/portuguese-hospital-distrital-da-horta-chooses-kanteron-ibm-medical-imaging-solution/</guid>
      <description>Portuguese Hospital Distrital da Horta EPE, located in the Azores Islands and founded in 1834, has chosen a Kanteron Systems PACS and diagnostic workstation solution to replace their previous Siemens PACS.
VBData and Kanteron Systems, as IBM partners, through its Portuguese subsidiary Softinsa, were awarded the contract on August 14. The installation has already started, after the solution has been completely translated into Portuguese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems and IBM win international bid in Uruguay</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-and-ibm-win-international-bid-in-uruguay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-and-ibm-win-international-bid-in-uruguay/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems and its partner IBM were notified today by the Uruguayan Government of the awarding of the international bid (ref: E. E. Nº 2014-17-1-0001474, Ent. N° 1098/14) for the supply of a PACS (Picture Archiving and Communication System) for ASSE(Public Healthcare System Administration), beating competing offers by General Electric, Carestream, Indra, and Geocom.
 This is our first installation in Uruguay, we are both very happy and proud to have won the contract, and we are looking forward to working with the Uruguayan government in supplying the most advanced and complete medical imaging management system</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The value of repeat customers</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/the-value-of-repeat-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 23:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/the-value-of-repeat-customers/</guid>
      <description>Any MBA student will agree that returning customers hold great economic value and much higher margins for any business. At Kanteron Systems, what we value the most about our returning customers is the validation that their new orders mean. When within days different customers, from CHIP to La Ribera Hospital, Fraternidad Muprespa, Monticello Imaging or EsSalud, request more products and services from us, we know we must be doing something right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM features Kanteron Systems in success case</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-success-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-success-case/</guid>
      <description>In the Case Studies section of their website, IBM published the case &amp;ldquo;A healthcare system in South America deploys a private cloud. Using virtualization to extend medical services to rural communities&amp;rdquo; featuring Kanteron Systems.
Link.
PDF version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participats in Siapec Rome</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, along with our new partner NoemaLife, participated in the 6th triennal Siapec(Italian Society for Anatomic Pathology and Cytopathology Diagnostic – Italian Division of the International Academy of Pathology) congressheld at the Hotel Ergife Palace in Rome October 26-30, 2013, where we will presented Noemalife Athenapowered by Kanteron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems: 8 years without losing a single customer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems turns 8 years old.
We want to thank those that have made this possible, that believed in us, that helped us, that are part of our organization, and specially that have trusted us with their business.
We have as many reasons to be proud about as we have things to improve. But if there is one very telling fact looking back in all those years, it‘s this: we have not lost a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems’ first multi-site multi-year contract in the USA</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-first-multi-site-multi-year-contract-in-the-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-first-multi-site-multi-year-contract-in-the-usa/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systemsis proud to announce a three-year contract with Monticello Diagnostic Imagingfor its imaging centers’ enterprise PACS-VNA storage, WorkList and RIS, providing Kanteron Systems’ KMIIS (Medical Imaging Integrated Server) DICOM standards-based storage and workflow management solution.
&amp;ldquo;At Kanteron Systems we are very happy to have the opportunity to work with the experienced team at Monticello Diagnostic Imaging. They have made it their priority to offer their referring physicians and patients easy access to the best medical imaging and reports, and we are proud to have been chosen, after testing several other systems available in the market, to help them accomplish that goal&amp;rdquo;, said Jorge Cortell, CEO of Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</guid>
      <description> Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Start013#Start013, November 6th 2012, at Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain). See you there!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems delivers new Cardiac PACS at NHS-GOSH and migrates more than 10 million images in a weekend</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-delivers-new-cardiac-pacs-at-nhs-gosh-and-migrates-more-than-10-million-images-in-a-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-delivers-new-cardiac-pacs-at-nhs-gosh-and-migrates-more-than-10-million-images-in-a-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As seen in The Guardian, Building Better Healthcare, BBC, Healthcare IT News, E-Health Insider, Open Health News, eHealth Europe, Hospital IT Europe, UK Government Online, UK Government Opportunities, and Healthcare Today:
London’s Great Ormond Street Children’s Hospital (GOSH) is making a major shift towards integrating Apple technology – benefiting staff and patients. A key project has been in Cardiology where clinicians now use iPads and iMacs for instant access to 3D images of patients’ hearts while planning for surgery, or even in theatre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Ribera Hospital chosen as &#34;model&#34; by European Union, orders more systems from Kanteron</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/la-ribera-hospital-chosen-as-model-by-european-union-orders-more-systems-from-kanteron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 05:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/la-ribera-hospital-chosen-as-model-by-european-union-orders-more-systems-from-kanteron/</guid>
      <description>La Ribera University Hospital (Spain) has been chosen along with other 3 European healthcare institutions, as basis for the report titled “Healthcare of the Future”. This has been approved by the European Commissioner for Health and Consumer Policy, John Dalli and La Ribera University Hospital managers, in a meeting in Paris. The report is written by the European Union Directorate General for Health and Consumer Policy in collaboration with COCIR (European Coordination Commitee of the Radiological, Electromedical and Heathcare IT Industry), group that includes some of the main healthcare tech companies in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico‘s President, Felipe Calderon, inaugurates a new hospital with Kanteron Systems technology</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/mexicos-president-felipe-calderon-inaugurates-a-new-hospital-with-kanteron-systems-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 19:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/mexicos-president-felipe-calderon-inaugurates-a-new-hospital-with-kanteron-systems-technology/</guid>
      <description>Mexico‘s President Felipe Calderón inaugurates a new ISSSTE hospital in Michoacan (Mexico) with Kanteron Systems technology (integrated by our distributors and partners in Mexico: Ceurac).
Video of the news in Televisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer oriented development</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/customer-oriented-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 15:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/customer-oriented-development/</guid>
      <description>At Kanteron Systems we pride ourselves in focusing our development efforts in what our customers need, what our customers like, what our customers could have&amp;hellip; and to do it fast!
Examples range from the one-week development and testing time of the &amp;ldquo;Review previous studies from the same patient&amp;rdquo; one-button new functionality in KDS, to the &amp;ldquo;custom color look-up tables to offset deficiencies and particularities in a specific modality&amp;rdquo;, or the DICOM Structured Report web tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CENIEH: Anthropology research using Kanteron solutions</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/cenieh-anthropology-research-using-kanteron-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 16:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/cenieh-anthropology-research-using-kanteron-solutions/</guid>
      <description>The National Research Centre on Human Evolutionuses Kanteron Systems‘ solutions to discover things like: Atapuerca‘s hominids could be a Neanderthal sister species.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>