<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 20:14:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems Nearly Triples Sales Worldwide in Preliminary EoY 2016 Results</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-nearly-triples-sales-worldwide-in-preliminary-eoy-2016-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 20:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-nearly-triples-sales-worldwide-in-preliminary-eoy-2016-results/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Spanish medical data software firm attributed the growth to an increase in its Platform sales during the last months of 2016.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected among Top 50 UK ScaleUps</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-systems-selected-among-top-50-uk-scaleups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 12:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-systems-selected-among-top-50-uk-scaleups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In its tenth year, &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Silicon Valley Comes to the UK (‘SVC2UK’) has invited 50 UK high-growth technology companies&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; to join the 2016 ‘&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Scale Up Club&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;’. One of those companies is Kanteron Systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron selected to represent the EU in Silicon Valley as the &#34;next EU unicorn&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>The European Commission, through Startup Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems amongst the top 18 European scaleups (from Belgium, Czech Republic, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Spain, and the UK) to represent the European Union in Silicon Valley as the &amp;ldquo;next EU unicorn&amp;rdquo;.
 The Startup Europeinitiative brings together EU policy makers (commissioners, prime ministers), the best of the new EU Scaleups and corporations to meet Silicon Valley stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay participates in Health 2.0 Valencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, participated yesterday in the Health 2.0 event organized by InnDEA, and featuring Tellmegen, eKuore and Kanteron, in Las Naves (Valencia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>According to Business Insider Kanteron Systems &#34;could soon be a unicorn&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/according-to-business-insider-kanteron-systems-could-soon-be-a-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/according-to-business-insider-kanteron-systems-could-soon-be-a-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>Business Insider UK features Kanteron Systems in the article &amp;ldquo;These 58 UK tech startups could soon be unicorns&amp;rdquo; by Sam Shead, dated Saturday November 14th.
Original article here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in Iberian Tech Tour</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-iberian-tech-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-iberian-tech-tour/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected, pre-screened and chosen from over 250 companies by the selection committee, to present in Iberian Tech Tour, October 1-3, 2014, which will cover 25 companies from Portugal and Spain.
Why &amp;ldquo;Iberian&amp;rdquo;? The City of Lisbon and the Region of Valencia in late June were named European Entrepreneurial Region (EER) for 2015. The EER project identifies and rewards EU regions that show a remarkable and innovative entrepreneurial strategy regardless of their size or economic situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in the VIII TEIBIO meeting &#34;From beginning to growth&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-participates-in-the-viii-teibio-meeting-from-beginning-to-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 22:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-participates-in-the-viii-teibio-meeting-from-beginning-to-growth/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, and Mariano Collantes, co-founder of Uvat bio, were the panelist in today‘s VIII TEI Bio meeting &amp;ldquo;From beginning to growth&amp;rdquo;. Organized by InnDEA Valencia, through VIT Salud and Genera Biotech, the TEI Bio events try to foster knowledge transfer, entrepreneurship and investment in Biomedicine and Biotechnology.
Here is the full description by BIOVAL, and here is another chronicle published by VIT Salud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems receives El Mundo newspaper &#34;Innovation of the Year Award&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-receives-el-mundo-newspaper-innovation-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-receives-el-mundo-newspaper-innovation-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description>The Jury of the V Innovation Awards (Spanish newspaper El Mundo) has awarded Kanteron Systems the Award for Best Innovation of the Year 2013. Attending the ceremonywere: the President of the European Commission and Commissioner for Entrepreneurship Antonio Tajani, the Israeli Ambassador in Spain (who presented the award to Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems CEO in Spain), Bankia‘s President and the President of the Valencian Government, among others. The event took place at the Red Sea auditorium in the Oceanographic in Valencia (Spain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The value of repeat customers</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/the-value-of-repeat-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 23:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/the-value-of-repeat-customers/</guid>
      <description>Any MBA student will agree that returning customers hold great economic value and much higher margins for any business. At Kanteron Systems, what we value the most about our returning customers is the validation that their new orders mean. When within days different customers, from CHIP to La Ribera Hospital, Fraternidad Muprespa, Monticello Imaging or EsSalud, request more products and services from us, we know we must be doing something right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems increases stock capital by issuing new stock</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-increases-stock-capital-by-issuing-new-stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 17:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-increases-stock-capital-by-issuing-new-stock/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems increased its stock share capital today by issuing nearly 30% new stock, bringing it’s outstanding stock share capital to nearly half a million US dollars. This issued share capital has been subscribed by Jorge Cortell, founder and CEO of Kanteron Systems, who remains the sole proprietor of the company.
 This new issue of share capital is meant to provide further stability and strength so Kanteron Systems can undertake the ambitious expansion it has planned for 2014</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected for the Investors Forum – MIT EmTech Spain 2013 Conference</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-selected-for-the-investors-forum-mit-emtech-spain-2013-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-selected-for-the-investors-forum-mit-emtech-spain-2013-conference/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as one of the participants for this year‘s edition of the Investors Forum, to be held Nov. 6 in Valencia (Spain) as part of the MIT Enterprise Forum EmTech Spain 2013 Conference.
#invertorsforum @mitefspain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems: 8 years without losing a single customer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems turns 8 years old.
We want to thank those that have made this possible, that believed in us, that helped us, that are part of our organization, and specially that have trusted us with their business.
We have as many reasons to be proud about as we have things to improve. But if there is one very telling fact looking back in all those years, it‘s this: we have not lost a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Cortell wins Executive of the Year Bronze Award in 2013 International Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/jorge-cortell-wins-executive-of-the-year-bronze-award-in-2013-international-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/jorge-cortell-wins-executive-of-the-year-bronze-award-in-2013-international-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems Founder &amp;amp; CEO, was named the winner of a Bronze Award in the Executive of the Year – Health Products &amp;amp; Services category in the 10th Annual International Business Awardstoday.
More than 3,300 nominations from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were considered in several categories, including Management Team of the Year, Corporate Social Responsibility Program of the Year, among others. Jorge Cortell won (bronze) in the Executive of the Year for Health Products &amp;amp; Services category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article in El Mundo “Innovators” section about Kanteron Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/article-in-el-mundo-innovators-section-about-kanteron-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 21:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/article-in-el-mundo-innovators-section-about-kanteron-systems/</guid>
      <description>Here (PDF)is a 3 page article in Spanish newspaper El Mundo published on Monday in their &amp;ldquo;Innovators&amp;rdquo; section, featuring Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in MIT‘s Emtech 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</guid>
      <description>Emtechis the main emerging technologies conference in the world, organized by MIT‘s (Massachusetts Institute of Technology) Technology Review, in which outstanding scientist and researchers present the most innovative emerging technologies, still unknown to the general public and with great potential to improve people‘s lives and transform society and business in the following years.
After Emtech Spain 2011‘s success, MIT chooses Spain again to celebrate their second annual conference in Europe. Emtech Spain 2012 will takwe place November 22nd and 23rd in the city of Malaga and it will be an exceptional opportunity for scientists, technologist, business, innovators and entrepreneurs to attend a unique event which will change their vision of the near future and how to lead the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems named &#34;National Champion&#34; and through to final round of European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-named-national-champion-and-through-to-final-round-of-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-named-national-champion-and-through-to-final-round-of-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>This year, for the first time, entrants in the European Business Awards submitted a video case study for online voting. In addition, an esteemed panel of judges chose organisations that exhibited innovation, business excellence and sustainability.
Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems:
 We’re proud to be selected to represent Spain as a National Champion in our category, along with companies like Bankinter, Iberdrola, or everis. The European Business Awards is widely recognised as the showcase for Europe’s most dynamic companies and we are now looking forward to the next round of the judging process where we can explain in more depth how we are achieving business success in these tough economic conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected for Valencian Global Growth accelerator 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-selected-for-valencian-global-growth-accelerator-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-selected-for-valencian-global-growth-accelerator-2012/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, along with 10 other companies (out of over 400), has been selected to participate in the Valencian Global accelerator program, organized by Business Innovationand Entrepreneurship Ventures. The seminars will take place at Sloan School of Management, MIT (Boston, USA) and Valencia (Spain), led by Kenneth Morse, William K. Aulet, Jacques Talbot and Laura Baker Morse.
As reported by the media: Europa Press, Expansión, 20 minutos, La Vanguardia, Las Provincias, Invertia, Valencia Plaza, TV Canal 9 (1st ed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins International Business Awards &#34;Company of the Year&#34; Bronze award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/08/kanteron-systems-wins-international-business-awards-company-of-the-year-bronze-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/08/kanteron-systems-wins-international-business-awards-company-of-the-year-bronze-award/</guid>
      <description>The International Business Awardsare the world’s premier business awards program. More than 3,200 nominations from over 50 countries from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were submitted this year for consideration. Award winners were selected by more than 300 executives worldwide who participated in the judging process this year. Kanteron Systems won Bronze Award in the Company of the Year category for Health Products &amp;amp; Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to represent Spain in Europe‘s most competitive business awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-represent-spain-in-europes-most-competitive-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 17:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-represent-spain-in-europes-most-competitive-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>The European Business Awardshas announced today that Kanteron Systemsis to represent Spain as a National Finalist in the prestigious 2012/13 Awards program. Kanteron Systems, the only Free Software company among the finalists, beat off stiff competition to be selected as National Finalists and will now compete for National Champion status in the next round of the competition. Final category Award winners will be unveiled April 2013.
The European Business Awards has identified some of Europe’s brightest businesses based on their ability to demonstrate the three core principles at the heart of the Awards program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kauffman report: Biomedical IPOs had the highest survival and lowest bankruptcy rates among all sectors</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kauffman-report-biomedical-ipos-had-the-highest-survival-and-lowest-bankruptcy-rates-among-all-sectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 16:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kauffman-report-biomedical-ipos-had-the-highest-survival-and-lowest-bankruptcy-rates-among-all-sectors/</guid>
      <description>According to a Kauffman study:
 Among Emerging Growth Companies firms that made IPOs from 1996 through 2000, only 29 percent were still operating 10 years later. However, acquisition was a far more common outcome than was failure (55 percent vs. 16 percent). Biomedical IPOs had the highest survival and lowest bankruptcy rates among all sectors; the highest failure rates were in manufacturing and retail.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems presentation at NYC Health 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems, presented (soon available via livestream) yesterday some of the company‘s solutions geared towards reducing hospital readmission to a group of 70 professionals at the VNS of NY HQ (10 E 70th St., New York) during a Health 2.0 NYC – The New York Healthcare Innovation Groupmeeting.
Here are some of the twitter-comments from that session:
globalfjord ‏ @globalfjord
Health 2.0 companies to watch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected again for inclusion in the 2012 European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/02/kanteron-systems-selected-again-for-inclusion-in-the-2012-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 17:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/02/kanteron-systems-selected-again-for-inclusion-in-the-2012-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>The European Business Awards Research team spend six months analysing over 15000 companies across Europe to seek out the very best businesses that demonstrate the guiding principles of the Awards: Commercial success, Innovation, Business ethics.
Wish us luck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spain, second worst country for entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/07/spain-second-worst-country-for-entrepreneurship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 18:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/07/spain-second-worst-country-for-entrepreneurship/</guid>
      <description>Source(thank‘s for the head‘s up, Ana).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invited to Tech Ventures Conference – U. of Cambridge</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kanteron-systems-invited-to-tech-ventures-conference-u.-of-cambridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kanteron-systems-invited-to-tech-ventures-conference-u.-of-cambridge/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited to participate in:
Technology Ventures Conference 2011
Ideas Economy: Changing the World by Connecting Ideas
9th of June 2011 – Cambridge Union, Cambridge, UK
Hosted by The Cambridge University Technology and Enterprise Club to enhance the entrepreneurial spirit amongst academics and students, by facilitating interaction between industry experts and students. Investors and the industries that support them in turn gain access to the vibrant research and entrepreneurial communities at the University of Cambridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems finalist for the Young Innovative Company of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/kanteron-systems-finalist-for-the-young-innovative-company-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 11:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/kanteron-systems-finalist-for-the-young-innovative-company-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems nominated for the 2011 European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-the-2011-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 19:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-the-2011-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased and honored to announce that Kanteron Systems has been selected for inclusion in the European Business Awards.
Every year the European Business Awards research team spend six months analysing over 15,000 companies across Europe to seek out the very best businesses that demonstrate the guiding principles of the Awards:
· Commercial success
· Innovation
· Business ethics
The award nomination research team &amp;ldquo;were particularly impressed with the success Jorge Cortell has had in leading and driving Kanteron Systems and the impact this has had across the business, having won the 4th Edition of Premio Emprendedor XXI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems first finalist in the national Entrepreneur of the Year Award XXI</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/06/kanteron-systems-first-finalist-in-the-national-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award-xxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 23:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/06/kanteron-systems-first-finalist-in-the-national-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award-xxi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins the Entrepreneur of the Year (Comunidad Valenciana) Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/05/kanteron-systems-wins-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-comunidad-valenciana-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/05/kanteron-systems-wins-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-comunidad-valenciana-award/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireless telehealth to reach 15 million systems in North America by 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/wireless-telehealth-to-reach-15-million-systems-in-north-america-by-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 17:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/wireless-telehealth-to-reach-15-million-systems-in-north-america-by-2012/</guid>
      <description>A publication from ABI Research examines wireless telehealth and forecasts that 15 million systems will be in use–mainly in North America–by early in 2012. Source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Innovation and Entrepreneurship Have to Be Incompatible with Organization Size?</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/do-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-have-to-be-incompatible-with-organization-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2009 11:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/do-innovation-and-entrepreneurship-have-to-be-incompatible-with-organization-size/</guid>
      <description>Forum and Articleby Harvard Business School Baker Foundation Professor Emeritus, James Heskett.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron’s founder nominated for Entrepreneur of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/kanterons-founder-nominated-for-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 22:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/kanterons-founder-nominated-for-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron System‘s founder, Jorge Cortell, was nominated today for the Entrepreneur of the Year awardby the Spanish Government. We wish him good luck! (honestly, no sucking-up here 😉</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persisten entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/02/persisten-entrepreneur/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 19:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/02/persisten-entrepreneur/</guid>
      <description>It sounds obvious, but researchfrom Harvard University has found that the persistently successful entrepreneur is much more likely to succeed again than first-timers or entrepreneurs who come from failure.[Note.- Kanteron System‘s entrepreneur comes from 3 previous successful ventures in a row 😉 ] </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>