<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kanteron News on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/kanteron-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kanteron News on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/kanteron-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Kanteron found &#34;AI in Health Partner Alliance&#34; along with 20 other tech companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft, Kanteron Systems, and 20 other technology companies have set up the &amp;ldquo;AI in Health Partner Alliance&amp;rdquo; to leverage the founding members&amp;rsquo; vision of Democratizing Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems Nearly Triples Sales Worldwide in Preliminary EoY 2016 Results</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-nearly-triples-sales-worldwide-in-preliminary-eoy-2016-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 20:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-nearly-triples-sales-worldwide-in-preliminary-eoy-2016-results/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Spanish medical data software firm attributed the growth to an increase in its Platform sales during the last months of 2016.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems featured in latest Frost &amp; Sullivan’s healthcare report</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-featured-in-latest-frost-sullivans-healthcare-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-featured-in-latest-frost-sullivans-healthcare-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The report lists Kanteron Systems as one of the 12 leading companies in Healthcare’s Emerging Business Models.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biggest telemedicine network in South America chooses Kanteron</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/biggest-telemedicine-network-in-south-america-chooses-kanteron/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 18:06:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/biggest-telemedicine-network-in-south-america-chooses-kanteron/</guid>
      <description>ITMS Chile, the largest international telemedicine network in South America, has chosen Kanteron Systems as their new platform to handle thousands of studies per day of medical imaging, reporting, and collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected among Top 50 UK ScaleUps</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-systems-selected-among-top-50-uk-scaleups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 12:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-systems-selected-among-top-50-uk-scaleups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In its tenth year, &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Silicon Valley Comes to the UK (‘SVC2UK’) has invited 50 UK high-growth technology companies&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; to join the 2016 ‘&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Scale Up Club&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;’. One of those companies is Kanteron Systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron among &#34;the most promising emerging digital health companies&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/10/kanteron-among-the-most-promising-emerging-digital-health-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/10/kanteron-among-the-most-promising-emerging-digital-health-companies/</guid>
      <description>Tech Tour, a platform for Innovative Investors, hi-tech Entrepreneurs (from early to late stage), Corporates and Government Influencers, committed to the development of emerging technology companies from Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems among the most promising emerging digital health companies in Europe. The selection was be based on Business potential, Team experience, Product / Technology merit, and Competitive position.
Taking place October 25 in Las Naves, Valencia (Spain), the Digital Health Venture Forum, organized by Tech Tour, will bring together the most promising emerging digital health companies (like Kanteron Systems), investors (from organisations like Philips, Teijin Pharma, Kreos Capital, Merck Global Health Innovation Fund, etc), and institutions (like Health 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron wins the California Impact Challenge in Precision Medicine award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/09/kanteron-wins-the-california-impact-challenge-in-precision-medicine-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/09/kanteron-wins-the-california-impact-challenge-in-precision-medicine-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been recognized as the leader in Precision Medicine, and awarded the 2016 Precision Medicine Impact Challenge Award by The California Governor’s Office of Planning and Research (OPR) and the Governor’s Office of Business and Economic Development (GO-Biz), in collaboration with Singularity University (SU).
The Precision Medicine Impact Challenge was announced by Atul Butte, MD, PhD, director of the UCSF Institute for Computational Health Sciences, and Elizabeth Baca, MD, MPA, from the Governor‘s OPR at the Precision Public Health summit hosted by UCSF in June 2016, convened by the White House and Bill &amp;amp; Melinda Gates Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron selected to represent the EU in Silicon Valley as the &#34;next EU unicorn&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>The European Commission, through Startup Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems amongst the top 18 European scaleups (from Belgium, Czech Republic, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Spain, and the UK) to represent the European Union in Silicon Valley as the &amp;ldquo;next EU unicorn&amp;rdquo;.
 The Startup Europeinitiative brings together EU policy makers (commissioners, prime ministers), the best of the new EU Scaleups and corporations to meet Silicon Valley stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 UK NHS hospitals choose Kanteron in less than a month</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/15-uk-nhs-hospitals-choose-kanteron-in-less-than-a-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/15-uk-nhs-hospitals-choose-kanteron-in-less-than-a-month/</guid>
      <description>In less than a month, 15 Hospital Trusts from the UK‘s National Health Service (NHS) have chosen Kanteron Systems‘ platform (TMIS) to integrate medical imaging and clinical genomics.
Only weeks after the general availability of Kanteron Systems source code for the NHS was announced, the following NHS Trusts have already joined the group of TMIS users around the world:
 North Bristol Trust Liverpool Heart &amp;amp; Chest Hospital NHS FT University Hospital of South Manchester Guy’s and St Thomas’ NHS Foundation Trust Newcastle upon Tyne Hospitals Addenbrooke’s Hospital | Cambridge University Hospitals NHS Greater Glasgow and Clyde University of Bradford Plymouth Hospitals NHS Trust The Royal Marsden Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust NHS Forth Valley Portsmouth Hospitals NHS Trust Salford Royal North Cumbria University Hospital NHS Trust UCLH – University College London Hospitals  Note: Previously, Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) was already a customer of Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems shortlisted for Top 10 Medical Imaging Solution Providers 2016</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-systems-shortlisted-for-top-10-medical-imaging-solution-providers-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-systems-shortlisted-for-top-10-medical-imaging-solution-providers-2016/</guid>
      <description>Healthcare Tech Outlook magazine has shortlisted Kanteron Systems for Top 10 Medical Imaging Solution Providers 2016 award.© Healthcare Tech Outlook magazineThis prestigious award recognizes companies who have stood out among the rest in the industry.
Healthcare Tech Outlook magazine reaches out to 41,000 CIOs, Directors, Hospital Information Management and Healthcare Research Teams and senior technology decision makers in the healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Partners with TellMeGen for Clinical Genomics Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-partners-with-tellmegen-for-clinical-genomics-interpretation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 15:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-partners-with-tellmegen-for-clinical-genomics-interpretation/</guid>
      <description>Turn-key Solution to Provide Clinical Genomic Interpretation on Leading Precision Medicine Data Platform
LONDON (UK) – VALENCIA (Spain), July 18, 2016 —
Kanteron Systems, the leading provider of medical imaging and clinical genomics software for precision medicine, and TellMeGen, a leading provider of genomic interpretation, announce a partnership to make TellMeGen’s clinical interpretation available to hospitals through the Kanteron platform.
Clinicians need to translate molecular information and interpretation into actionable therapeutic strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General availability of Kanteron source code for NHS announced at the UK Radiology Congress 2016</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/general-availability-of-kanteron-source-code-for-nhs-announced-at-the-uk-radiology-congress-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/general-availability-of-kanteron-source-code-for-nhs-announced-at-the-uk-radiology-congress-2016/</guid>
      <description>Shawn Larson, Senior Project Manager at HSCIC, announced the general availability of Kanteron source code for the NHS on Monday, June 6, at UKRC (the largest diagnostic imaging event in the UK). The announcement was made during the session: PACS 2.0 (the next generation) has now happened – any real difference?
In conjunction with HSCIC’s OpenPACS and NHS England’s Code 4 Health / Open Source initiatives, Kanteron Systems has made the source code of its Translational Medical Information Server (TMIS) platform freely available to the NHS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to join Microsoft in Festival of Genomics Boston</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-to-join-microsoft-in-festival-of-genomics-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 13:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-to-join-microsoft-in-festival-of-genomics-boston/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate, along with Microsoft Genomics group, in the Festival of Genomics conference to be held at Boston Convention Center (USA) June 27-29.
CEO Jorge Cortell, and President &amp;amp; CCO John Memarian, will be demonstrating how Kanteron‘s Translational Medical Information Server integrates medical images with clinical genomics, pharmacogenomics and other relevant data for the delivery of precision medicine at the point of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New 0 non-conformities ISO audit</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/new-0-non-conformities-iso-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 19:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/new-0-non-conformities-iso-audit/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce another annual ISO 9001 audit review passed with perfect &amp;ldquo;score&amp;rdquo;: zero major and zero minor non-conformities.
Congratulations to the QA team!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems Selects Dicom Systems Unifier as Universal Enterprise Imaging Adapter</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/03/kanteron-systems-selects-dicom-systems-unifier-as-universal-enterprise-imaging-adapter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 22:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/03/kanteron-systems-selects-dicom-systems-unifier-as-universal-enterprise-imaging-adapter/</guid>
      <description>Campbell, CA, March 16, 2016 – Dicom Systems, Inc., an Enterprise Imaging interoperability expert, announced today its partnership with Kanteron Systems, Inc. (USA, Spain, and UK). This partnership will deliver more comprehensive, real-time patient information to specialists, enabling improved correlation of clinical data and medical imaging within one, consolidated visual context.
Kanteron Systems, the leading aggregator of Genomics, Pathology and Radiology imaging and data for multi-discipline clinical specialists, has selected Dicom Systems and its Enterprise Imaging Workflow Unifier as a universal adapter to seamlessly integrate its clinical data management solutions within any healthcare enterprise environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron’s DirectTransfer radically transforms medical imaging device connectivity: no more need for firewalls, SSL or NAT</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanterons-directtransfer-radically-transforms-medical-imaging-device-connectivity-no-more-need-for-firewalls-ssl-or-nat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 05:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanterons-directtransfer-radically-transforms-medical-imaging-device-connectivity-no-more-need-for-firewalls-ssl-or-nat/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron in the top 15% of analyzed software startups according to rating agency EarlyMetrics</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanteron-in-the-top-15-of-analyzed-software-startups-according-to-rating-agency-earlymetrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 09:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanteron-in-the-top-15-of-analyzed-software-startups-according-to-rating-agency-earlymetrics/</guid>
      <description>After a comprehensive and independent analysis and review by Early Metrics, the first ratings agency for startups, has awarded Kanteron Systems &amp;ldquo;3 stars&amp;rdquo;, it‘s top honors.
Early Metrics audits and analyzes over 100 startups each month, including the matrix rating (Managers – Project – Market) and the FSRC indicator, which evaluates the reliability and consistency of the financial statements.
 Kanteron is part of the top 15% of our software startups – Sarah Noeckel, Venture Capital Analyst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Memarian to Join Kanteron as President and Chief Commercial Officer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/john-memarian-to-join-kanteron-as-president-and-chief-commercial-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 15:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/john-memarian-to-join-kanteron-as-president-and-chief-commercial-officer/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems USA, Inc. today announced that John Memarian, President of International Businesses at Merge (recently acquired by IBM), will be joining Kanteron in a newly created position, as President and Chief Commercial Officer, joining the executive team and reporting directly to Founder and CEO Jorge Cortell.
Memarian will be responsible for executing the commercial strategy and business development of Kanteron, overseeing activities relating to marketing, sales, product development and customer service, to drive business growth and market share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking agreement allows the NHS to access an innovative platform providing integrated imaging and genomic data at the point of care</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/groundbreaking-agreement-allows-the-nhs-to-access-an-innovative-platform-providing-integrated-imaging-and-genomic-data-at-the-point-of-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 19:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/groundbreaking-agreement-allows-the-nhs-to-access-an-innovative-platform-providing-integrated-imaging-and-genomic-data-at-the-point-of-care/</guid>
      <description>Healthcare information systems leader Kanteron Systems, in collaboration with the NHS National Health System (NHS) England’s Open Source and Code 4 Health Programmes, has agreed to allow the entire NHS unrestricted access to Kanteron’s medical imaging and genomic data integration platform under the custodianship of an NHS clinically led OpenPACS Code 4 Health community. The agreement was announced at RSNA – the world’s largest gathering of clinical medical imaging professionals – in Chicago (USA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come visit us at HIMSS 2016 Las Vegas (HDS booth 846)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/come-visit-us-at-himss-2016-las-vegas-hds-booth-846/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 11:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/come-visit-us-at-himss-2016-las-vegas-hds-booth-846/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will exhibit alongside its partner Hitachi at the HIMSSconference and exhibition Tues. March 1, Thurs. March 3, 2016, Sands Convention Center, Las Vegas (USA).
Schedule a meeting or demo here, and come visit us at Hitachi Data Systems Booth 846.
Note: Exhibition Hall‘s opening hours are 9:30 am – 6:00 pm (closing time Thursday, March 3: 4:00pm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected as part of the Mayor’s International Programme</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/kanteron-systems-selected-as-part-of-the-mayors-international-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 21:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/kanteron-systems-selected-as-part-of-the-mayors-international-programme/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as one of the 35 companies forming the initial cohort of the Mayor’s International Programme.
The programme will support high growth businesses from London’s Technology, Life Sciences and Urban sectors to expand their businesses internationally. It is run by London &amp;amp; Partners (supported by the Mayor), partly funded by the European Development Fund and partly by five private sector delivery partners: BDO, Benoy, KPMG, London Chamber of Commerce and Industry &amp;amp; PA Consulting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th EU Health Innovation event at Microsoft’s Brussels EBC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 20:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</guid>
      <description>This Tuesday and Wednesday Kanteron Systems was invited to participate in Microsoft’s 5th Health Innovation event, in the Exhibition Area, along with 5 other selected partners.
Titled “EmpoweringHealth: the journey towards more personalized, productive, collaborative and predictive health services &amp;amp; systems” it took place at the Microsoft Executive Briefing Center in Brussels.Kanteron Systems‘ CEO, Jorge Cortell, participated in the round table “Medical Imaging Storage in the Cloud”, moderated by Kelly Limonte (Microsoft UK Healthcare Team), and in the Expert Panel “The future of preventive and predictive health powered by data in the intelligent cloud”, along with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Report “Valencia: Healthcare Innovation and Research” Features Kanteron as a Success Case</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/the-report-valencia-healthcare-innovation-and-research-features-kanteron-as-a-success-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 19:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/the-report-valencia-healthcare-innovation-and-research-features-kanteron-as-a-success-case/</guid>
      <description>InnDEA Valencia Foundation, through the VIT Salud Innovation Network, released yesterday the report “Valencia: Healthcare Innovation and Research”, produced by the Valencian Institute of Economic Research (IVIE).
Javier Quesada, author of the report, is an IVIE researcher and Professor of Economic Analysis at Valencia University (UV). The report highlights that the healthcare economic activity in the city has grown “much faster” than the rest of the economic activity and it represents 5,3% of all economic activity in the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research lists Kanteron as major player in the global digital pathology market</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/market-research-lists-kanteron-as-major-player-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/market-research-lists-kanteron-as-major-player-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</guid>
      <description>Market Research firm P&amp;amp;S Market Research featuresKanteron Systems as &amp;ldquo;major player operating in the global digital pathology market&amp;rdquo; in their Digital Pathology Market Trends and Forecast to 2020 report issued November 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>According to Business Insider Kanteron Systems &#34;could soon be a unicorn&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/according-to-business-insider-kanteron-systems-could-soon-be-a-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 17:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/according-to-business-insider-kanteron-systems-could-soon-be-a-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>Business Insider UK features Kanteron Systems in the article &amp;ldquo;These 58 UK tech startups could soon be unicorns&amp;rdquo; by Sam Shead, dated Saturday November 14th.
Original article here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The London Stock Exchange invites Kanteron to participate in the market opening ceremony</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/the-london-stock-exchange-invites-kanteron-to-participate-in-the-market-opening-ceremony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/the-london-stock-exchange-invites-kanteron-to-participate-in-the-market-opening-ceremony/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, November 6th, Kanteron Systems‘ CEO Jorge Cortell was invited by Marcus Stuttard, head of AIM (the London Stock Exchange‘s growth market), to participate in the London Stock Exchange market opening ceremony, which takes place daily at 8:00 am.

The ceremony offers companies joining London Stock Exchange‘s markets the opportunity to mark their success on the day of their admission. The event was followed by drinks and breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron featured by The Telegraph as it joins the ScaleUpClub</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanteron-featured-by-the-telegraph-as-it-joins-the-scaleupclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 13:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanteron-featured-by-the-telegraph-as-it-joins-the-scaleupclub/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems UK has been selected as a member of the #ScaleUpClub 2015. The club is hand-picked by Silicon Valley Comes to the UK (@svc2uk), a not-for-profit organisation that brings together US early-stage investors and disruptive UK start-ups, identifying the 58 firms that could hit £100m in revenue in the next three to five years.
 According to the UK‘s The Telegraph newspaper, the report lists &amp;ldquo;the British companies most likely to become technology giants to rival Facebook and Google&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM features Kanteron Systems in an ad</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-an-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 19:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-an-ad/</guid>
      <description>IBM has produced an advertising featuring Kanteron Systems, titled: &amp;ldquo;More precise diagnostics with Kanteron and IBM Cloud&amp;rdquo;.
Here is the IBM press release.
The ad, featuring Kanteron COO Juan Tatay and Kanteron CIO Alvaro Gonzalez, was filmed in Kanteron‘s offices in Valencia and Madrid (Spain), for the IBM Business Connectevent.
Watch the video here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s solutions to be exhibited in Medica 2015 trade show</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanterons-solutions-to-be-exhibited-in-medica-2015-trade-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 16:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanterons-solutions-to-be-exhibited-in-medica-2015-trade-show/</guid>
      <description>Our partners Mediphealthwill exhibit and demonstrate Kanteron‘s solutions at Hall 15, booth B01, of Medica2015 trade show which will take place16-19 November in Düsseldorf (Germany).
Medica is the world’s largest event for the medical sector, and has been held for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Of London‘s Export Programme selects Kanteron to participate in BioJapan 2015</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/mayor-of-londons-export-programme-selects-kanteron-to-participate-in-biojapan-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 01:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/mayor-of-londons-export-programme-selects-kanteron-to-participate-in-biojapan-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Mayor of London Boris Johnson MP travelled to Yokohama (Japan) with representatives from 8 of the most promising BioTech companies in London to promote UK-Japan collaboration in cell therapy and regenerative medicine at the BioJapan 2015. BioJapan is Asia’s leading biotechnology event, attracting thousands of representatives from some 700 of the world’s leading bioscience companies every year. This year it took place October 14th – 16th at Pacifico Yokohama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron and Ver2 Digital Medicine Bring Medical Imaging and Genomics Data Integration to Middle East Markets</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/kanteron-and-ver2-digital-medicine-bring-medical-imaging-and-genomics-data-integration-to-middle-east-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 20:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/kanteron-and-ver2-digital-medicine-bring-medical-imaging-and-genomics-data-integration-to-middle-east-markets/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems and Ver2 Digital Medicine introduce the first Medical Imaging and Genomics Data Integration platform in the United Arab Emirates.
Doctors in the Middle East can now examine your symptoms, correlate them with your electronic medical records, medical imaging exams, pathology tests, and your genomic data. Doctors then instantly compare those results with the data on thousands of other individuals to deliver a detailed diagnosis — or even detect an illness before the symptoms appear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM invites Kanteron Systems to participate in IBMBCES</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/ibm-invites-kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-ibmbces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/ibm-invites-kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-ibmbces/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited by IBM Spain to participate in the IBM Business Connect, to be held in Madrid (Spain) November 25, 2015.
Click herefor more info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NHS England selects Kanteron Systems for second round of testing combinatorial innovation</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/nhs-england-selects-kanteron-systems-for-second-round-of-testing-combinatorial-innovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 12:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/nhs-england-selects-kanteron-systems-for-second-round-of-testing-combinatorial-innovation/</guid>
      <description>Together with the Academic Health Science Networks (AHSNs), and HM Government, NHS England has invited Kanteron Systems to the second round of their ‘test bed programme.
The test bed programme is about deploying technologies that are ready to use, in NHS settings—not about inventing new ones.
Kanteron Systems is ready to accept this challenge and deliver what the NHS has described as ‘high value innovation‘.
July 29th, at The Kia Oval, London, Kanteron Systems will meet several NHS sites interested in deploying our solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two top level scientists joined Kanteron Systems’ team today</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/two-top-level-scientists-joined-kanteron-systems-team-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 23:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/07/two-top-level-scientists-joined-kanteron-systems-team-today/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Raminder Singh and Santiago Gala join Kanteron’s team.
Dr Raminderpal Singh has joined Kanteron Systems as Strategic Advisor.
Dr. Singh was until now Business Development &amp;amp; Strategy Lead at IBM Research-Genomic Medicine. His experience in Venture Capital at 3i Group, as well as his international experience with healthcare organizations in countries like Singapore, UK, and Canada, and with deals and partnerships in USA, China, India, Russia, and Brazil fit perfectly well with Kanteron’s momentum of explosive international growth and exploration of new partnerships and corporate options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay and Alvaro Gonzalez presentation at IBM Cloud event in Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/06/juan-tatay-and-alvaro-gonzalez-presentation-at-ibm-cloud-event-in-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 22:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/06/juan-tatay-and-alvaro-gonzalez-presentation-at-ibm-cloud-event-in-madrid/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday June 2 Kanteron System‘ Alvaro González – CIO and Juan Tatay – COO presented Kanteron Systems‘ experience with IBM at the IBM Cloud event &amp;ldquo;Dream it! Build it!&amp;rdquo; in Madrid. #IBMCloudDreamIt
Kanteron‘s success case was presented along two other companies: Evolufarma and SKIOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems passes FDA inspection and ISO audit with flying colors</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/05/kanteron-systems-passes-fda-inspection-and-iso-audit-with-flying-colors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2015 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/05/kanteron-systems-passes-fda-inspection-and-iso-audit-with-flying-colors/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘ New York office was inspected by the FDA on February 5th 2015 pursuant to FDA NYK-DO‘s 2015 workplan under FACTS Assignment #11499178 in accordance to Compliance Program, Inspection of Medical Device Manufacturers, 7382.845 covering PAC‘s 82845A.
The inspection covered Kanteron Systems‘ operations. The QSIT inspection approach was used in conducting the QSR/cGMP covering the Corrective and Preventive Action and the Production and Process Control subsystems. No FDA 483 was issued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Ormond Street Hospital (NHS – London) renews contract with Kanteron Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/great-ormond-street-hospital-nhs-london-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/great-ormond-street-hospital-nhs-london-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</guid>
      <description>Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) for Children, a National Health Service (NHS) Foundation Trust in London, UK, has just renewed their services contract for a Cardiology PACS (Picture Archiving and Communication System) with Kanteron Systems.
The NHS has some of the most strict and demanding service contracts in the world. We are proud and honored that such an iconic institution in pediatric care as GOSH has been trusting Kanteron Systems for four years already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new report from ASDReports recognizes Kanteron Systems as &#34;Prominent Vendor&#34; in the Global Digital Pathology Market</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/a-new-report-from-asdreports-recognizes-kanteron-systems-as-prominent-vendor-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 10:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/a-new-report-from-asdreports-recognizes-kanteron-systems-as-prominent-vendor-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</guid>
      <description>A new reportfrom ASDReports titled &amp;ldquo;Global Digital Pathology Market 2014-2018&amp;rdquo; recognizes Kanteron Systems as &amp;ldquo;Prominent Vendor&amp;rdquo; in the Global Digital Pathology Market.
Source: Tissue Pathology Blog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron joins forces with Hitachi Data Systems to advance personalized medicine</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-joins-forces-with-hitachi-data-systems-to-advance-personalized-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 23:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-joins-forces-with-hitachi-data-systems-to-advance-personalized-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems
Victoria Sanchis
marketing@kanteron.com
Tel: 963312287</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>everis presents the first Electronic Health Record (EHR) with Kanteron‘s clinical genomic capabilities</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/everis-presents-the-first-electronic-health-record-ehr-with-kanterons-clinical-genomic-capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 23:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/everis-presents-the-first-electronic-health-record-ehr-with-kanterons-clinical-genomic-capabilities/</guid>
      <description>• Precision Medicine: Genomic data integrated with EMRs means precise diagnostics and pharmacogenomic indications (which medications will work better in each specific patient).
• 360º View of the Patient: Radiology and Pathology imaging is only part of the picture in many cases.
• Genomic data has been, until now, the missing key piece of information in digital records for personalized medicine.
everis, an NTT Data company, announces a partnership with Kanteron Systems to provide its Next-Generation Electronic Health Record, ehCOS CLINIC, with a robust platform for clinical genomics, key to precise diagnostics and personalized medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems at HIMSS 2015 Chicago</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-systems-at-himss-2015-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 20:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-systems-at-himss-2015-chicago/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Chicago April 12-16, stop by HIMSS 2015 Booth # 2480, Hitachi Data Systems Corporation (HDS), or Booth #1425, IBM, to see Kanteron Systems‘ clinical genomics in action.
As for Jorge, Stephanie, Craig or Kurt. See you in Chicago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems finalist in IBM Innovation Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/03/kanteron-systems-finalist-in-ibm-innovation-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/03/kanteron-systems-finalist-in-ibm-innovation-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as finalist, along with British Telecom and nusys, in the IBM Innovation Awards, New Business Model category, for our Split and Pathology Imaging Algorithms solutions. The award, finally won by nusys (congratulations!) was presented at the IBM Leadership Summitthat took place at the Royal Spanish Academy in Madrid (Spain), March 3rd, 2015.
  According to IBM, this nomination celebrates Kanteron Systems as pioneers in the development of solutions for the healthcare environment and visionaries in new technologies and business models in cloud and Watson Cognitive Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to supply technology behind Deployable Mobile Hospitals</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-to-supply-technology-behind-deployable-mobile-hospitals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2015 01:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-to-supply-technology-behind-deployable-mobile-hospitals/</guid>
      <description>On February 10th, the Peruvian government awarded through public bid contract LP 013-2014-MINSA the supply of technology behind three Deployable Mobile Hospitals to Kanteron Systems.
The three Deployable Mobile Hospitals will be delivered by a consortium of companies.
 We are proud that Kanteron Systems‘ technology has been selected for this large project, which will enable the Peruvian Government to better serve its citizens through mobile hospitals deployable in remote regions, in cases of natural disasters, or in conflict zones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems seeks candidate to join Dubai team</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-seeks-candidate-to-join-dubai-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-seeks-candidate-to-join-dubai-team/</guid>
      <description>We are seeking a solution architect, CTO level: an energetic person, with technical knowledge in network administration (especially in a hospital setting), complete English fluency, and good communication skills. We offer annual contract, but a willingness to stay in Dubai after training in Valencia (Spain) for at least 3 years is required.
For further info please contact hr@kanteron.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to begin operations in London this May</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-to-begin-operations-in-london-this-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-to-begin-operations-in-london-this-may/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has set May as the date to begin operations in London, UK.
The list of opportunities in the UK and the whole Northern Europe region is growing quite rapidly, and Kanteron Systems wants to show commitment to its current and future customers in the region by being physically closer to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems in Arab Health, Dubai</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems was back in Arab Healththis year (January 26-28), due to the increased interest and activity regarding Healthcare Technology in the Middle Eastern region.
Through our new partners in the region, we have over twenty projects going on in United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Iran, Iraq, Nigeria, Tanzania, and Ethiopia.Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems CEO, in the lobby of Arab Health Dubai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in the VII Biomedical Engineering Workshop</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-vii-biomedical-engineering-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 21:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-vii-biomedical-engineering-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Organizedby the Inter-University (Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia, Spain) MSc. in Biomedical Engineering, the VII Biomedical Engineering Workshop will take place February 3-6, 2015.
Juan Tatay, COO, and Jorge Cortell, Founder and CEO of Kanteron Systems, will talk about &amp;ldquo;Computational paradigm shift in medical imaging&amp;rdquo;. Juan Tatay will be present during the event in Valencia, while Jorge Cortell will participate via videoconference from New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MD Anderson Madrid signs order for Kanteron Systems digital pathology workflow solution</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/md-anderson-madrid-signs-order-for-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-workflow-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2015 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/md-anderson-madrid-signs-order-for-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-workflow-solution/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 2000 as the first international affiliate of The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Centerin Houston (Texas), which is ranked number 2 as the best cancer center in the USA, and with facilities spanning 15,300 m2, over a hundred beds, and about 400 employees, MD Anderson Cancer Center Madridis the first fully specialized cancer care center in Spain, where patients can receive all of their diagnostic tests, inpatient and outpatient treatment, and see all of their physicians at a single site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems listed as Prominent Vendor in Digital Pathology market report</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-listed-as-prominent-vendor-in-digital-pathology-market-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 15:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-listed-as-prominent-vendor-in-digital-pathology-market-report/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems featured in El Mundo – leading Spanish online information site and newspaper</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-featured-in-el-mundo-leading-spanish-online-information-site-and-newspaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 17:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-featured-in-el-mundo-leading-spanish-online-information-site-and-newspaper/</guid>
      <description>Full article, in Spanish, here:
https://www.elmundo.es/economia/2014/11/14/546507d2ca4741c6398b457c.html </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems publishes advanced medical image algorithms in IBM Cloud marketplace</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-publishes-advanced-medical-image-algorithms-in-ibm-cloud-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 10:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-publishes-advanced-medical-image-algorithms-in-ibm-cloud-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems today announced a partnership with IBM that brings the power of Medical Imaging Analysis to the IBM Cloud marketplace. Starting today, IBM clients can integrate very specific tools for medical image processing and analysis into their workflows with the click of a button.
The first available digital pathology image algorithms perform color separation for Hematoxylin, Eosin and Diaminobenzidine immunohistochemical staining.
The IBM Cloud marketplace offers client’s access to more than 100 SaaS applications, IBM‘s Bluemix™ platform-as-a-service with its suite of composable services, the powerful SoftLayer infrastructure-as-a-service and IBM‘s rich intellectual capital and deep industry expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University Hospital in Bogota updates its Kanteron Systems solution to IBM Pure Flex System</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/university-hospital-in-bogota-updates-its-kanteron-systems-solution-to-ibm-pure-flex-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 18:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/university-hospital-in-bogota-updates-its-kanteron-systems-solution-to-ibm-pure-flex-system/</guid>
      <description>The University Hospital San Ignacio (HUSI) at the Javeriana University in Bogota (Colombia) has chosen to renew the Kanteron Systems digital medical imaging solution they have been using since 2011.
This updates the PACS and RIS system to the corresponding modules of the newKanteron Systems TMIS (Translational Medical Imaging System). The new system is being installed in an IBM Pure Flex platform providing HUSI with new features, improved performance and speed, flexibility and unparalleled convenience to provide access to users through a web interface (HTML5) without installing any software (zero-footprint) and accessible from any device (responsive design).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in the national HealthIT Innovation tour</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-national-healthit-innovation-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-national-healthit-innovation-tour/</guid>
      <description>The TIC Salud National HealthIT Innovation Touris an initiative that organizes events in different Spanish regions so that companies in the industry can present their latest innovations in the field of HealthIT to healthcare professionals and executives. The Committee will be formed by deputy directors of Information Technology, CEO‘s, CIO‘s and medical directors. Following each of the presentations, committee members will ask questions directed to the speakers about their innovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Largest outsourced medical imaging PACS in Latin America renews contract with Kanteron Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/largest-outsourced-medical-imaging-pacs-in-latin-america-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 16:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/largest-outsourced-medical-imaging-pacs-in-latin-america-renews-contract-with-kanteron-systems/</guid>
      <description>On Monday October 6, EsSalud – Social Security Administration of Peru – signed a renewal of services contract (number 4600044350, process number 1499E00031) with Kanteron Systems to continue supporting the largest medical imaging outsourced system in Latin America. This renewal is proof of EsSalud‘s satisfaction with a system they have been using for over 3 years now.
Hosted in IBM data center in Lima, Peru, the Kanteron PACS provides a single repository, workflow management, monitoring and security backups for all medical imaging generated by EsSalud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in Iberian Tech Tour</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-iberian-tech-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-iberian-tech-tour/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected, pre-screened and chosen from over 250 companies by the selection committee, to present in Iberian Tech Tour, October 1-3, 2014, which will cover 25 companies from Portugal and Spain.
Why &amp;ldquo;Iberian&amp;rdquo;? The City of Lisbon and the Region of Valencia in late June were named European Entrepreneurial Region (EER) for 2015. The EER project identifies and rewards EU regions that show a remarkable and innovative entrepreneurial strategy regardless of their size or economic situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portuguese Hospital Distrital da Horta chooses Kanteron&#43;IBM medical imaging solution</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/portuguese-hospital-distrital-da-horta-chooses-kanteron-ibm-medical-imaging-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2014 11:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/portuguese-hospital-distrital-da-horta-chooses-kanteron-ibm-medical-imaging-solution/</guid>
      <description>Portuguese Hospital Distrital da Horta EPE, located in the Azores Islands and founded in 1834, has chosen a Kanteron Systems PACS and diagnostic workstation solution to replace their previous Siemens PACS.
VBData and Kanteron Systems, as IBM partners, through its Portuguese subsidiary Softinsa, were awarded the contract on August 14. The installation has already started, after the solution has been completely translated into Portuguese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: Global Digital Pathology Market CAGR 11.8% to 2018, Kanteron listed as &#34;major player&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/report-global-digital-pathology-market-cagr-11.8-to-2018-kanteron-listed-as-major-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 19:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/report-global-digital-pathology-market-cagr-11.8-to-2018-kanteron-listed-as-major-player/</guid>
      <description>MarketsandMarketsrecently published “Digital Pathology Market by Slide Scanners (Whole Slide Imaging), Analytics (Image Analysis Software), Delivery Modes (Web Based/Cloud Based) &amp;amp; by Whole Slide Image Storage – Global Forecasts &amp;amp; Trends to 2018″ (available for purchase online), listing Kanteron Systems as a &amp;ldquo;major player&amp;quot;in the worldwide Digital Pathology market.
This report covers the definition, description, and forecast of the digital pathology market in terms of products and applications; the digital pathology market comprises of scanners, analytics, storage, and communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The latest healthcare technology report from Gartner features Kanteron as VNA sample vendor</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/the-latest-healthcare-technology-report-from-gartner-features-kanteron-as-vna-sample-vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 16:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/the-latest-healthcare-technology-report-from-gartner-features-kanteron-as-vna-sample-vendor/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been featured as VNA (Vendor-Neutral Archive) sample vendor in Gartner‘s latest healthcare technology report: Hype Cycle for Healthcare Providers Technologies and Standards, written by veteran industry analyst Barry Runyon.
 The Hype Cycle for Healthcare Providers Technologies and Standards is a vital reference for healthcare delivery organization CIOs and IT leadership when assessing the value of existing and emerging information technologies and standards. It provides insight necessary to remain competitive in a rapidly evolving healthcare provider marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems completes move to new, larger headquarters</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-completes-move-to-new-larger-headquarters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2014 03:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-completes-move-to-new-larger-headquarters/</guid>
      <description>Effective August 1st, Kanteron Systems has moved its headquarters to a new, larger building in Puçol (Valencia – Spain).
 Our new physical address is:   Our new postal address is:   Our new legal registered address is:   Our telephone line remains the same: +34 963312287
In its new location, Kanteron’s employees will enjoy a series of unique benefits, such as outdoor swimming pools (in the summer), tennis and basketball courts, soccer field, restaurant, easy parking, and several terraces with great views of the Mediterranean sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems collaborates in world‘s first Scientific Photography Postgraduate course</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-collaborates-in-worlds-first-scientific-photography-postgraduate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 10:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-collaborates-in-worlds-first-scientific-photography-postgraduate-course/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will collaborate with the world‘s first _ Scientific Photography Postgraduate course_ at the University of Alcala (Spain) October 6 to November 21, 2014.
The lectures will be taught in the classroom‘s School of Sciences. The practical classes are taught in the Cabinet of Scientific Photography lab, Cell Biology lab and National Museum of Natural Sciences.
The course involves 20 teachers selected among the best Spanish and foreign specialists (including Kanteron Systems‘ CIO, Alvaro Gonzalez) who will teach 30 different specialties handling equipment worth over 1,000 million euros, thanks to the collaboration of the Ministry of Defense, National Museum of Natural Sciences, Astronomical Observatory La Hita, various hospitals, universities and other entities like Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to exhibit at Federal Summit 2014 in Washington DC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/kanteron-systems-to-exhibit-at-federal-summit-2014-in-washington-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/kanteron-systems-to-exhibit-at-federal-summit-2014-in-washington-dc/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday June 11 (7:30-15:30h) Kanteron Systems will be demonstrating its state-of-the-art biomedical informatics solution at the 2nd Annual Federal Summit, where IT and management executives from government and industry tap the full potential of today’s computing environment to drive innovation, reduce operating costs, and deliver better mission outcomes and customer satisfaction.
Featuring Keynote Speakers:
Gen. Keith B. Alexander, USA (Ret.)
Former Commander, U.S. Cyber Command
Former Director, National Security Agency/Chief, Central Security Service</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems joins BioVal Association</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/05/kanteron-systems-joins-bioval-association/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/05/kanteron-systems-joins-bioval-association/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems has joined the Valencia BioRegion BioVal Association. More info here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems successfully passes another ISO 9001 audit</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/05/kanteron-systems-successfully-passes-another-iso-9001-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 18:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/05/kanteron-systems-successfully-passes-another-iso-9001-audit/</guid>
      <description>Since we first received our ISO 9001 quality certification in 2008, we have always passed audits. Since 2012, we have passed them with ZERO non-conformities. But in a clear sign of continuous improvement, this year the auditor‘s report reads:
 The quality management system has been implemented and maintained quite successfully at Kanteron Systems, showing a positive evolution since last year.
 He also recommends us to be included in the Excellence recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in Transbio Sudoe Barcelona Emergence Forum</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-participates-in-transbio-sudoe-barcelona-emergence-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 18:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-participates-in-transbio-sudoe-barcelona-emergence-forum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems and IBM win international bid in Uruguay</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-and-ibm-win-international-bid-in-uruguay/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2014 00:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-and-ibm-win-international-bid-in-uruguay/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems and its partner IBM were notified today by the Uruguayan Government of the awarding of the international bid (ref: E. E. Nº 2014-17-1-0001474, Ent. N° 1098/14) for the supply of a PACS (Picture Archiving and Communication System) for ASSE(Public Healthcare System Administration), beating competing offers by General Electric, Carestream, Indra, and Geocom.
 This is our first installation in Uruguay, we are both very happy and proud to have won the contract, and we are looking forward to working with the Uruguayan government in supplying the most advanced and complete medical imaging management system</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems joins the Global Alliance for Genomics and Health</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/03/kanteron-systems-joins-the-global-alliance-for-genomics-and-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 23:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/03/kanteron-systems-joins-the-global-alliance-for-genomics-and-health/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce it has joined institutions like Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard, American Society of Clinical Oncology, Massachusetts General Hospital, Mayo Clinic, Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, IBM, or Google, in the Global Alliance for Genomics and Health.
The Global Alliance for Genomics and Health (Global Alliance) is an international coalition, formed by over 150 of the world’s leading organizations (including healthcare providers, research funders, research institutions, disease advocacy organizations, and life science and information technology companies) to enable the sharing of genomic and clinical data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Top 50 to Top 10 in a week! Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 10 (Healthcare) for Web Traffic Rank Growth</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/from-top-50-to-top-10-in-a-week-kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-10-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 16:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/from-top-50-to-top-10-in-a-week-kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-10-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 for Web Traffic Rank Growth according to new ranking company SIGNL.
Rank: #9 of 2,436 Health Care Methodology: SIGNL’s algorithm analyzes millions of data points including web/mobile traffic, social buzz, company growth, and more to identify companies with the highest momentum.
Kanteron Systems, following the stellar presentation of TMIS at RSNAChicago, is experiencing incredible momentum with the anticipated new product developments introduced at HIMSSOrlando (Genomics + Pharmacogenomics + Activity and Sleep Trackers + Analytics) as third party vendor independent PACS-VNA-EMR add-on plug-ins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in the VIII TEIBIO meeting &#34;From beginning to growth&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-participates-in-the-viii-teibio-meeting-from-beginning-to-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 22:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-participates-in-the-viii-teibio-meeting-from-beginning-to-growth/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, and Mariano Collantes, co-founder of Uvat bio, were the panelist in today‘s VIII TEI Bio meeting &amp;ldquo;From beginning to growth&amp;rdquo;. Organized by InnDEA Valencia, through VIT Salud and Genera Biotech, the TEI Bio events try to foster knowledge transfer, entrepreneurship and investment in Biomedicine and Biotechnology.
Here is the full description by BIOVAL, and here is another chronicle published by VIT Salud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 (Healthcare) for Web Traffic Rank Growth</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-50-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 19:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-50-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 for Web Traffic Rank Growth according to new ranking company SIGNL.
Rank: #32 of 2,436 Health CareMethodology: SIGNL‘s algorithm analyzes millions of data points including web/mobile traffic, social buzz, company growth, and more to identify companies with the highest momentum.
Kanteron Systems, following the stellar presentation of TMIS at RSNAChicago, is experiencing incredible momentum with the anticipated new product developments to be introduced at HIMSSOrlando (hint: Genomics + Pharmacogenomics + Activity and Sleep Trackers + Analytics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems receives El Mundo newspaper &#34;Innovation of the Year Award&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-receives-el-mundo-newspaper-innovation-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-receives-el-mundo-newspaper-innovation-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description>The Jury of the V Innovation Awards (Spanish newspaper El Mundo) has awarded Kanteron Systems the Award for Best Innovation of the Year 2013. Attending the ceremonywere: the President of the European Commission and Commissioner for Entrepreneurship Antonio Tajani, the Israeli Ambassador in Spain (who presented the award to Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems CEO in Spain), Bankia‘s President and the President of the Valencian Government, among others. The event took place at the Red Sea auditorium in the Oceanographic in Valencia (Spain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to deliver a lecture at the VI Biomedical Engineering Meeting</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, February 6 2014 at 16h, Kanteron Systems‘ Juan Tatay (Director) and Carlos Villanueva (R&amp;amp;D Engineer) will deliver the lecture “Precise diagnostics for personalized medicine: medical imaging and big data” at the Cajal Room, 1st floor, School of Medicine, University of Valencia (Spain) within the VI Biomedical Engineering Meetingof the Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia‘s Official Interuniversity Master Degree in Biomedical Engineering. Other lectures will be delivered by Philips Research, Indra Sistemas and General Electric Healthcare amongst others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in consortium to develop 3D implants</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-participates-in-consortium-to-develop-3d-implants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 12:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-participates-in-consortium-to-develop-3d-implants/</guid>
      <description>A new generation of personalized implants has been designed to compete in time and costs with traditional manufacturing. The project, co-financed by CDTI has achieved excellent results in its initial phases and aims to be the definitive step towards personalized implants.
The consortium members are: Surgival, AMES, Biotechnology Institute, QuironHospital Group, Kanteron Systems (developing the imaging component); and the research institutes Biomedical Institute of Valencia (IBV), and Metalmechanic Technology Institute (AIMME).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems joins IHE as a full Member Organization</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-joins-ihe-as-a-full-member-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 21:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-joins-ihe-as-a-full-member-organization/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to have been approved as a Member Organization of IHE International, an active and growing volunteer-led non-profit entity with over 200 member organizations from across the globe.
Integrating the Healthcare Enterprise (IHE) is an initiative by healthcare professionals and industry to improve the way computer systems in healthcare share information. IHE promotes the coordinated use of established standards such as DICOM and HL7 to address specific clinical needs in support of optimal patient care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems increases stock capital by issuing new stock</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-increases-stock-capital-by-issuing-new-stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 17:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-increases-stock-capital-by-issuing-new-stock/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems increased its stock share capital today by issuing nearly 30% new stock, bringing it’s outstanding stock share capital to nearly half a million US dollars. This issued share capital has been subscribed by Jorge Cortell, founder and CEO of Kanteron Systems, who remains the sole proprietor of the company.
 This new issue of share capital is meant to provide further stability and strength so Kanteron Systems can undertake the ambitious expansion it has planned for 2014</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan on Kanteron Systems’ latest innovation: “WOW!”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</guid>
      <description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivanprofiles Kanteron Systems in the “WOW!” section of their latest Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics report.
Global growth consulting firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, which provides market research and analysis for the Healthcare Industry (amongst others), published today the report “RSNA 2013 Review: Scouting the Showfloor for the Latest-Greatest in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics”. In the report’s “Select WOW! Findings from the Showfloor” section, Nadim Michel Daher, Principal Analyst – Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics, and Siddharth Saha, Global Program Leader Advanced MedTech, identify six companies with disruptive innovations in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM features Kanteron Systems in success case</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-success-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-success-case/</guid>
      <description>In the Case Studies section of their website, IBM published the case &amp;ldquo;A healthcare system in South America deploys a private cloud. Using virtualization to extend medical services to rural communities&amp;rdquo; featuring Kanteron Systems.
Link.
PDF version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems introduces the first Translational PACS-VNA in the world at RSNA 2013</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 00:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</guid>
      <description>PRESS RELEASE First Translational Medical Imaging System in the World New York, NY, USA, November 27, 2013
 Kanteron Systems will launch the world‘s first Translational Medical Imaging System (“TMIS”) at the Radiology Society of North America (“RSNA”) annual meeting in Chicago, December 1-5, 2013. TMIS is a fully integrated solution for radiology, genetic and pathology workflows that could change the way medicine is practiced.
 Translational research is an emerging field that aims to provide a better understanding of the molecular basis of disease, which in turn will inform clinical practice and ultimately improve human health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in RSNA2013 along with IBM and AVNET (Booth B7510)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-rsna2013-along-with-ibm-and-avnet-booth-b7510/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 16:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-rsna2013-along-with-ibm-and-avnet-booth-b7510/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate in this year‘s RSNAalong with Avnet &amp;amp; IBM at Booth B7510, North Building – Hall B, December 1-5, 2013 in Chicago (USA). More details to be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participats in Siapec Rome</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, along with our new partner NoemaLife, participated in the 6th triennal Siapec(Italian Society for Anatomic Pathology and Cytopathology Diagnostic – Italian Division of the International Academy of Pathology) congressheld at the Hotel Ergife Palace in Rome October 26-30, 2013, where we will presented Noemalife Athenapowered by Kanteron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected for the Investors Forum – MIT EmTech Spain 2013 Conference</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-selected-for-the-investors-forum-mit-emtech-spain-2013-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-selected-for-the-investors-forum-mit-emtech-spain-2013-conference/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as one of the participants for this year‘s edition of the Investors Forum, to be held Nov. 6 in Valencia (Spain) as part of the MIT Enterprise Forum EmTech Spain 2013 Conference.
#invertorsforum @mitefspain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in IBM START014 in Madrid (Spain)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/09/kanteron-systems-participates-in-ibm-start014-in-madrid-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 16:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/09/kanteron-systems-participates-in-ibm-start014-in-madrid-spain/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems had a booth in the IBM #START014 congress, November 20, 2013, Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems: 8 years without losing a single customer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems turns 8 years old.
We want to thank those that have made this possible, that believed in us, that helped us, that are part of our organization, and specially that have trusted us with their business.
We have as many reasons to be proud about as we have things to improve. But if there is one very telling fact looking back in all those years, it‘s this: we have not lost a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins Silver Award Company of the Year in the 10th Annual International Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-wins-silver-award-company-of-the-year-in-the-10th-annual-international-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 15:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-wins-silver-award-company-of-the-year-in-the-10th-annual-international-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems was named the winner of a Silver Award in the Company of the Year – Health Products &amp;amp; Services category in the 10th Annual International Business Awardstoday.
More than 3,300 nominations from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were considered in several categories, including Management Team of the Year, Corporate Social Responsibility Program of the Year, among others. Kanteron Systems won (silver) in the Company of the Year for Health Products &amp;amp; Services category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jorge Cortell wins Executive of the Year Bronze Award in 2013 International Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/jorge-cortell-wins-executive-of-the-year-bronze-award-in-2013-international-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2013 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/jorge-cortell-wins-executive-of-the-year-bronze-award-in-2013-international-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems Founder &amp;amp; CEO, was named the winner of a Bronze Award in the Executive of the Year – Health Products &amp;amp; Services category in the 10th Annual International Business Awardstoday.
More than 3,300 nominations from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were considered in several categories, including Management Team of the Year, Corporate Social Responsibility Program of the Year, among others. Jorge Cortell won (bronze) in the Executive of the Year for Health Products &amp;amp; Services category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems’ first multi-site multi-year contract in the USA</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-first-multi-site-multi-year-contract-in-the-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2013 17:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-first-multi-site-multi-year-contract-in-the-usa/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systemsis proud to announce a three-year contract with Monticello Diagnostic Imagingfor its imaging centers’ enterprise PACS-VNA storage, WorkList and RIS, providing Kanteron Systems’ KMIIS (Medical Imaging Integrated Server) DICOM standards-based storage and workflow management solution.
&amp;ldquo;At Kanteron Systems we are very happy to have the opportunity to work with the experienced team at Monticello Diagnostic Imaging. They have made it their priority to offer their referring physicians and patients easy access to the best medical imaging and reports, and we are proud to have been chosen, after testing several other systems available in the market, to help them accomplish that goal&amp;rdquo;, said Jorge Cortell, CEO of Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron and HistoIndex Announce Collaboration to Expand Digital Pathology in Asian EHR &amp;amp; PACS Markets</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-and-histoindex-announce-collaboration-to-expand-digital-pathology-in-asian-ehr-amp-pacs-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 21:47:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-and-histoindex-announce-collaboration-to-expand-digital-pathology-in-asian-ehr-amp-pacs-markets/</guid>
      <description>**PRESS RELEASE **
New York, NY, USA, July 27, 2013
Kanteron Systems, Inc. (USA) and HistoIndex Pte Ltd (Singapore) today announce they have signed a Joint Marketing Agreement to offer a fully integrated digital pathology &amp;amp; radiology solution. Kanteron’s KMIIS, a cutting-edge hospital information system, enhances management of radiology and pathology information and images within hospital networks. While fully interoperable with PACS-Vendor Neutral Archive, EHR, RIS, and LIS via standards (like DICOM and HL7), KMIIS also includes an HTML5 zero-footprint remote single interface for access to PACS, VNA, RIS, WorkList Server, and Digital Pathology image viewer that includes zoom, pan, measure, annotate, and report tools functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems chosen as top innovative company in Valencia (Spain)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-chosen-as-top-innovative-company-in-valencia-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 20:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-chosen-as-top-innovative-company-in-valencia-spain/</guid>
      <description>The Council of Commerce Chambersof Valencian Community region (Spain), along with the Research Institutes Association has chosen Kanteron Systems to be included in their &amp;ldquo;Top Innovative Valencian Companies&amp;rdquo; guide, presented last Thursday. Kanteron Systems is the only biomedical informatics company in the guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invested over half a million euros in R&amp;amp;D in 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-invested-over-half-a-million-euros-in-rampd-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2013 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-invested-over-half-a-million-euros-in-rampd-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>Despite adverse economic conditions in Europe, Kanteron Systems invested over half a million euros in R&amp;amp;D in 2012.
We believe private and public research investment is absolutely necessary, and we ask the Spanish Government to keep funding research projects and research institutions, like CSIC(national research center, which needs 75 million euros to survive), and not waste our tax money in unnecesary megalomaniac projects like Madrid 2020 olympic (2,418.75 million euros budget, over 30 million already wasted in bid), or corruptionscandals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems USA passes FDA inspection without issues</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-systems-usa-passes-fda-inspection-without-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 21:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-systems-usa-passes-fda-inspection-without-issues/</guid>
      <description>On April 25th Kanteron Systems had its first routine FDA (U.S. Food and Drug Administration) Medical Device Establishment Inspection. Agent (Investigator) Kimberley A. Ricketts gave us a routine “Notice of Inspection pursuant to Section 704(a)(1) of the Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetics Act [21 U.S.C. 374(a)] and Part F or G, Title III of the Public Health Service Act [42 U.S.C. 262-264]“. This Level 1 inspection was conducted as part of the NYK-DO Work Plan under FACTS ID#1456352 in accordance with Compliance Program 7382.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron and DigiPath Collaboration Expands Digital Pathology into EHR &amp;amp; PACS Markets</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-and-digipath-collaboration-expands-digital-pathology-into-ehr-amp-pacs-markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2013 20:21:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-and-digipath-collaboration-expands-digital-pathology-into-ehr-amp-pacs-markets/</guid>
      <description>PRESS RELEASE
Kanteron and DigiPath Collaboration Expands Digital Pathology into EHR &amp;amp; PACS Markets
Kanteron Systems and DigiPath, Inc. (OTCBB: DIGP) today announce they have entered in a Joint Selling &amp;amp; Marketing Agreement to shared resources and implement a fully integrated digital pathology &amp;amp; radiology solution.
Kanteron’s KMIIS, a cutting-edge hospital information system, simplifies the management of radiology and pathology within hospital networks. The solution is fully interoperable with PACS-Vendor Neutral Archive, EHR, RIS, and LIS via standards-compliant protocols (like DICOM and HL7).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron featured in IBM ad</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-featured-in-ibm-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 20:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-featured-in-ibm-ad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron COO interviewed by Inndea</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/05/kanteron-coo-interviewed-by-inndea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2013 00:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/05/kanteron-coo-interviewed-by-inndea/</guid>
      <description>Spanish magazine Inndea interviews Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems COO. Read the whole interview (Spanish) here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems featured in Diario Medico</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/04/kanteron-systems-featured-in-diario-medico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2013 19:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/04/kanteron-systems-featured-in-diario-medico/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is featured, full page, in this week‘s edition of Diario Medico(Spanish).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems develops new Hanging Protocols Plug-In for OsirixMD</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-develops-new-hanging-protocols-plug-in-for-osirixmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 23:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-develops-new-hanging-protocols-plug-in-for-osirixmd/</guid>
      <description>The new OsirixMD plug-indeveloped by Kanteron Systems allows you to apply a personalized Hanging Protocol based on very configurable specific parameters (any DICOM tag).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins 2013 IBM Beacon Award for Healthcare and Life Sciences</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-wins-2013-ibm-beacon-award-for-healthcare-and-life-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 01:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-wins-2013-ibm-beacon-award-for-healthcare-and-life-sciences/</guid>
      <description>IBM Beacon Awards recognize IBM Business Partners for their technical excellence, industry expertise, and innovative solutions.
Kanteron Systems was named a winner of a 2013 IBM Beacon Award for Healthcare and Life Sciences. This honor is awarded each year in recognition of a select number of IBM Business Partners who have delivered not only innovative solutions but have set the standards for business excellence, ingenuity, and creation of an exceptional client experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article in El Mundo “Innovators” section about Kanteron Systems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/article-in-el-mundo-innovators-section-about-kanteron-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 21:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/article-in-el-mundo-innovators-section-about-kanteron-systems/</guid>
      <description>Here (PDF)is a 3 page article in Spanish newspaper El Mundo published on Monday in their &amp;ldquo;Innovators&amp;rdquo; section, featuring Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to participate in IBM PartnerWorld Leadership Conference in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/kanteron-to-participate-in-ibm-partnerworld-leadership-conference-in-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 20:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/kanteron-to-participate-in-ibm-partnerworld-leadership-conference-in-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate in IBM PartnerWorld Leadership Conferenceto be held February 25 – February 28, 2013 at Caesars Palace in Las Vegas, attended by: 1,500 C-Level Business Partners, 500 IBM Senior level Executives, 60 Press and Analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems awarded &#34;Best Clinical Poster Award&#34; at Digital Pathology Association Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 01:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is honored to have been awarded &amp;ldquo;Best Clinical Poster Award&amp;rdquo; at Digital Pathology Association Congress 2012 Pathology Visions, held in Baltimore (USA), October 28th-October 31st.
The poster was titled: &amp;ldquo;Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web)&amp;rdquo; and was presented and authored by Jorge Cortell CEO &amp;amp; President, Kanteron Systems USA, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in MIT‘s Emtech 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</guid>
      <description>Emtechis the main emerging technologies conference in the world, organized by MIT‘s (Massachusetts Institute of Technology) Technology Review, in which outstanding scientist and researchers present the most innovative emerging technologies, still unknown to the general public and with great potential to improve people‘s lives and transform society and business in the following years.
After Emtech Spain 2011‘s success, MIT chooses Spain again to celebrate their second annual conference in Europe. Emtech Spain 2012 will takwe place November 22nd and 23rd in the city of Malaga and it will be an exceptional opportunity for scientists, technologist, business, innovators and entrepreneurs to attend a unique event which will change their vision of the near future and how to lead the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems named &#34;National Champion&#34; and through to final round of European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-named-national-champion-and-through-to-final-round-of-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-named-national-champion-and-through-to-final-round-of-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>This year, for the first time, entrants in the European Business Awards submitted a video case study for online voting. In addition, an esteemed panel of judges chose organisations that exhibited innovation, business excellence and sustainability.
Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems:
 We’re proud to be selected to represent Spain as a National Champion in our category, along with companies like Bankinter, Iberdrola, or everis. The European Business Awards is widely recognised as the showcase for Europe’s most dynamic companies and we are now looking forward to the next round of the judging process where we can explain in more depth how we are achieving business success in these tough economic conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems receives International Business of the Year Award in Seoul</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/10/kanteron-systems-receives-international-business-of-the-year-award-in-seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 06:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/10/kanteron-systems-receives-international-business-of-the-year-award-in-seoul/</guid>
      <description>High resolution photograph for media reproduction.
October 15th, 2012; Seoul (South Korea)
Kanteron Systems receives the International Business of the Year bronze Award, Healthcare Products &amp;amp; Services.
At a ceremony held at the Ritz Carlton Hotel, where over 400 international executives and dignataries from 20 different countries gathered to celebrate the best companies in the world, Jorge Cortell (president &amp;amp; founder of Kanteron Systems) was presented the award by Michael Gallagher, president of the Stevie Awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</guid>
      <description> Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Start013#Start013, November 6th 2012, at Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain). See you there!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins IAIR Corporate Award 3rd annual edition: Best Company for leadership – Europe</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-wins-iair-corporate-award-3rd-annual-edition-best-company-for-leadership-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-wins-iair-corporate-award-3rd-annual-edition-best-company-for-leadership-europe/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce that Kanteron Systems is a winner for the IAIR CORPORATE AWARDS3rd annual edition in the Best Company for leadership – Europe TOP 50 category.
Some of the past winners: Morgan Stanley, Bank of China, Rockefeller, BNP Paribas, IBM, Rothschild, Deutsche Bank, Aviva, Vodafone, Novartis, BASF, Daimler, Royal Dutch Shell, Christian Dior, Cartier, Fedex, ABB, 3i Group, CMS.
According to Alexa – Amazon and Google page rankings, IAIR – International Alternative Investment Reviewis ranked # 1 amongst financial and legal awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected for Valencian Global Growth accelerator 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-selected-for-valencian-global-growth-accelerator-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2012 10:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-selected-for-valencian-global-growth-accelerator-2012/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, along with 10 other companies (out of over 400), has been selected to participate in the Valencian Global accelerator program, organized by Business Innovationand Entrepreneurship Ventures. The seminars will take place at Sloan School of Management, MIT (Boston, USA) and Valencia (Spain), led by Kenneth Morse, William K. Aulet, Jacques Talbot and Laura Baker Morse.
As reported by the media: Europa Press, Expansión, 20 minutos, La Vanguardia, Las Provincias, Invertia, Valencia Plaza, TV Canal 9 (1st ed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems USA moves to new offices in coworking SoHo loft (New York)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-usa-moves-to-new-offices-in-coworking-soho-loft-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2012 08:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-usa-moves-to-new-offices-in-coworking-soho-loft-new-york/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to present a poster at DPA 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-present-a-poster-at-dpa-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 21:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-present-a-poster-at-dpa-2012/</guid>
      <description>
Kanteron Systems will present the poster “Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web&amp;hellip;)” at the Digital Pathology Association’s (DPA) annual conference Pathology Visions, being held October 28-31, 2012 at the Hilton Hotel in Baltimore, MD (USA).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins International Business Awards &#34;Company of the Year&#34; Bronze award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/08/kanteron-systems-wins-international-business-awards-company-of-the-year-bronze-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/08/kanteron-systems-wins-international-business-awards-company-of-the-year-bronze-award/</guid>
      <description>The International Business Awardsare the world’s premier business awards program. More than 3,200 nominations from over 50 countries from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were submitted this year for consideration. Award winners were selected by more than 300 executives worldwide who participated in the judging process this year. Kanteron Systems won Bronze Award in the Company of the Year category for Health Products &amp;amp; Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online demo of Kanteron Systems digital pathology image (WSI) viewer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/online-demo-of-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-image-wsi-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 17:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/online-demo-of-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-image-wsi-viewer/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces an online demo to try the speed of our digital pathology image (Whole Slide Image) viewer: https://pathoarchive.kanteron.com/As you try it, keep in mind there might be thousands of concurrent users, your bandwidth may be limited, and most important: you will be browsing 2 to 6 GIGABYTE images (from different scanner manufacturers and formats, DICOM ready)&amp;hellip; in real time!! with a zero footprint viewer (no need to install any additional software).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Alvaro Gonzalez and Jorge Cortell talk about healthcare IT security at HOPE9</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘ Alvaro González(CTO) and Jorge Cortell(CEO) spoke today about &amp;ldquo;Digital Security in Health Care Institutions&amp;rdquo; during Hackers On Planet Earth number 9, New York, one of the most creative and diverse hacker events in the world (since 1994).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems nominated for Company of the Year, International Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-company-of-the-year-international-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 23:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-company-of-the-year-international-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to be nominated for the 2012 Company of the Year Award at the International Business Awards. Go team!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivers Master Class at London event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivered a Master Class about the NHS Great Ormond Street‘s successful implementation by Kanteron Systems of a new Cardiac PACS, at London event &amp;ldquo;A patient centered approach&amp;rdquo; (Central Hall Westminster, Storey‘s Gate) July 4th, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems passes yearly quality audit with 0 non-conformities</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-passes-yearly-quality-audit-with-0-non-conformities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-passes-yearly-quality-audit-with-0-non-conformities/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems has received the audit report from independent auditors Bureau Veritas International, regarding our ISO 9001:2008 Quality System, and the results are perfect: 0 major non-conformities, and 0 minor non-conformities.
Congratulations to everybody in the team, led by Juan Tatay!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invited to attend IBM‘s &#34;Redefining Value and Success in Healthcare&#34; business event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-invited-to-attend-ibms-redefining-value-and-success-in-healthcare-business-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 17:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-invited-to-attend-ibms-redefining-value-and-success-in-healthcare-business-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited to attend, as Independent Software Vendor (ISV) IBM‘s &amp;ldquo;Redefining Value and Success in Healthcare&amp;rdquo; business event, led by Dan Pelino, at the IBM Innovation Center and Healthcare Transformation Lab, Chicago (USA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems delivers new Cardiac PACS at NHS-GOSH and migrates more than 10 million images in a weekend</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-delivers-new-cardiac-pacs-at-nhs-gosh-and-migrates-more-than-10-million-images-in-a-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-delivers-new-cardiac-pacs-at-nhs-gosh-and-migrates-more-than-10-million-images-in-a-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As seen in The Guardian, Building Better Healthcare, BBC, Healthcare IT News, E-Health Insider, Open Health News, eHealth Europe, Hospital IT Europe, UK Government Online, UK Government Opportunities, and Healthcare Today:
London’s Great Ormond Street Children’s Hospital (GOSH) is making a major shift towards integrating Apple technology – benefiting staff and patients. A key project has been in Cardiology where clinicians now use iPads and iMacs for instant access to 3D images of patients’ hearts while planning for surgery, or even in theatre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to represent Spain in Europe‘s most competitive business awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-represent-spain-in-europes-most-competitive-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 17:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-represent-spain-in-europes-most-competitive-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>The European Business Awardshas announced today that Kanteron Systemsis to represent Spain as a National Finalist in the prestigious 2012/13 Awards program. Kanteron Systems, the only Free Software company among the finalists, beat off stiff competition to be selected as National Finalists and will now compete for National Champion status in the next round of the competition. Final category Award winners will be unveiled April 2013.
The European Business Awards has identified some of Europe’s brightest businesses based on their ability to demonstrate the three core principles at the heart of the Awards program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to attend 2012 M&#43;Visión Consortium Biomedical Innovation Conference</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-attend-2012-m-visi%C3%B3n-consortium-biomedical-innovation-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-attend-2012-m-visi%C3%B3n-consortium-biomedical-innovation-conference/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will attend and exhibit at MIT‘s 2012 M+Visión Consortium Biomedical InnovationConference in Madrid (Spain), June 5th and 6th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated Kanteron WEB-RIS (optimized for mobile)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/updated-kanteron-web-ris-optimized-for-mobile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 16:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/updated-kanteron-web-ris-optimized-for-mobile/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce the new version of our Web-RIS, with a completely redesigned interface, optimized for mobile devices (rotation, finger input, etc), while remaining 100% web standard and accesible via web browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron receives the Integrity in Supplier Relationships certification by IBM</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-receives-the-integrity-in-supplier-relationships-certification-by-ibm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 17:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-receives-the-integrity-in-supplier-relationships-certification-by-ibm/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to have received the Integrity in Supplier Relationships certification by our partners IBM (to whom we are ISV), proof of our commitment and adherence to the highest ethical and legal standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to sponsor SEACV‘s diagnostic photo contest</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-systems-to-sponsor-seacvs-diagnostic-photo-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 18:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-systems-to-sponsor-seacvs-diagnostic-photo-contest/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to sponsor this year‘s diagnostic photo contestfrom the Spanish Society of Angiology and Vascular Surgery (SEACV).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to sponsor TEDxValencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-to-sponsor-tedxvalencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 16:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-to-sponsor-tedxvalencia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Ribera Hospital chosen as &#34;model&#34; by European Union, orders more systems from Kanteron</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/la-ribera-hospital-chosen-as-model-by-european-union-orders-more-systems-from-kanteron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 05:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/la-ribera-hospital-chosen-as-model-by-european-union-orders-more-systems-from-kanteron/</guid>
      <description>La Ribera University Hospital (Spain) has been chosen along with other 3 European healthcare institutions, as basis for the report titled “Healthcare of the Future”. This has been approved by the European Commissioner for Health and Consumer Policy, John Dalli and La Ribera University Hospital managers, in a meeting in Paris. The report is written by the European Union Directorate General for Health and Consumer Policy in collaboration with COCIR (European Coordination Commitee of the Radiological, Electromedical and Heathcare IT Industry), group that includes some of the main healthcare tech companies in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems presentation at NYC Health 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems, presented (soon available via livestream) yesterday some of the company‘s solutions geared towards reducing hospital readmission to a group of 70 professionals at the VNS of NY HQ (10 E 70th St., New York) during a Health 2.0 NYC – The New York Healthcare Innovation Groupmeeting.
Here are some of the twitter-comments from that session:
globalfjord ‏ @globalfjord
Health 2.0 companies to watch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New KDS-Osirix plug-in to apply &#34;curved CLUTs&#34; (sigmoidal or S-shaped)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/new-kds-osirix-plug-in-to-apply-curved-cluts-sigmoidal-or-s-shaped/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2012 15:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/new-kds-osirix-plug-in-to-apply-curved-cluts-sigmoidal-or-s-shaped/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces a new KDS-Osirix plug-in that allows the user to easily apply &amp;ldquo;curved CLUTs&amp;rdquo; (sigmoidal or S-shaped) to DICOM digital medical images (particularly X-rays) to enhance their contrast in an advanced way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems USA‘s FDA registration and listing</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-usas-fda-registration-and-listing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 15:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-usas-fda-registration-and-listing/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems USA, Inc. has received formal notification of its device facility registration and listing of devices at the USA FDA (Food and Drug Administration).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico‘s President, Felipe Calderon, inaugurates a new hospital with Kanteron Systems technology</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/mexicos-president-felipe-calderon-inaugurates-a-new-hospital-with-kanteron-systems-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 19:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/mexicos-president-felipe-calderon-inaugurates-a-new-hospital-with-kanteron-systems-technology/</guid>
      <description>Mexico‘s President Felipe Calderón inaugurates a new ISSSTE hospital in Michoacan (Mexico) with Kanteron Systems technology (integrated by our distributors and partners in Mexico: Ceurac).
Video of the news in Televisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected again for inclusion in the 2012 European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/02/kanteron-systems-selected-again-for-inclusion-in-the-2012-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 17:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/02/kanteron-systems-selected-again-for-inclusion-in-the-2012-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>The European Business Awards Research team spend six months analysing over 15000 companies across Europe to seek out the very best businesses that demonstrate the guiding principles of the Awards: Commercial success, Innovation, Business ethics.
Wish us luck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems joins the Spain-US Chamber of Commerce</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/kanteron-systems-joins-the-spain-us-chamber-of-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 22:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/kanteron-systems-joins-the-spain-us-chamber-of-commerce/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce it has joined the Spain-US Chamber of Commerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer oriented development</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/customer-oriented-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2012 15:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/customer-oriented-development/</guid>
      <description>At Kanteron Systems we pride ourselves in focusing our development efforts in what our customers need, what our customers like, what our customers could have&amp;hellip; and to do it fast!
Examples range from the one-week development and testing time of the &amp;ldquo;Review previous studies from the same patient&amp;rdquo; one-button new functionality in KDS, to the &amp;ldquo;custom color look-up tables to offset deficiencies and particularities in a specific modality&amp;rdquo;, or the DICOM Structured Report web tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems USA‘s new office in Times Square (New York)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/12/kanteron-systems-usas-new-office-in-times-square-new-york/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2011 18:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/12/kanteron-systems-usas-new-office-in-times-square-new-york/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems USA is proud to announce the inauguration of our new offices in the heart of Times Square, New York (USA).1515 BroadwayLocated on 1515 Broadway, in the Viacom and MTV headquarters building, our new offices provide the perfect venue to offer our customers in the USA and Canada the best support.Vivian and Felicia, 11th floor reception, will welcome you to Kanteron Systems USAWith plenty of space for leisure and informal meeting areas,7th floor cafeteriakitchen and water bar11th floor bar (Christmas party!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDS helps in intracraneal electrode surgery planning for an OCD patient</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/kds-helps-in-intracraneal-electrode-surgery-planning-for-an-ocd-patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 17:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/kds-helps-in-intracraneal-electrode-surgery-planning-for-an-ocd-patient/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Gutierrez, a neurosurgeon in La Fe hospital (Valencia, Spain), uses KDS to plan intracraneal electrode surgery for OCD.
Source: El Mundo, LevanteVideo: EFE KDS in surgery planning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron approved as United Nations supplier</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/kanteron-approved-as-united-nations-supplier/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 20:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/kanteron-approved-as-united-nations-supplier/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, after a 14 step process, has finally been approved as a United Nations supplier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARSOR v2.0 sensors ready</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/arsor-v2.0-sensors-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 20:22:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/arsor-v2.0-sensors-ready/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to the work of Kanteron Systems hardware development team lead by Engineer C. Villanueva, the integrated sensors for ARSOR version 2.0 are ready.
After full testing is undertaken at CHIP Hospital‘s Operating Rooms in Malaga (Spain), full production will go into effect before the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems will develop software for security company Fermax</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/kanteron-systems-will-develop-software-for-security-company-fermax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 08:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/kanteron-systems-will-develop-software-for-security-company-fermax/</guid>
      <description>The international security and residential communications company Fermaxhas chosen Kanteron Systems to develop the new access control management software for their fingerprint reader and proximity sensor.
With this contract, Kanteron Systems shows once again the capacity of its programmers to meet development needs of the most demanding software, and opens a new business line in the competitive and challenging world of electronic security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems delivers a Vascular Diagnostic Update Course</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-delivers-a-vascular-diagnostic-update-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-delivers-a-vascular-diagnostic-update-course/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems delivers a lecture in the Vascular Diagnostic Update Course held at the Polytechnic and University Hospital La Fe (Valencia – Spain), September 29 and 30, 2011, during the XIV National CDVNI-SEACV Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems introduces big-data solution HDI</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-introduces-big-data-solution-hdi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 12:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-introduces-big-data-solution-hdi/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces a ground-breaking new solution: HDI (Hospital Data Intelligence).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article about Kanteron Systems in Valencia Plaza</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-valencia-plaza/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 10:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-valencia-plaza/</guid>
      <description>https://www.valenciaplaza.com/ver/32764/Kanteron-se-instala-en-EE-UU-con-el-primer-sistema-de-realidad-aumentada-en-quirófano.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHIP pioneer in iPad healthcare application</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/chip-pioneer-in-ipad-healthcare-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 09:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/chip-pioneer-in-ipad-healthcare-application/</guid>
      <description>CHIP Hospital, always on the leading edge of technology, has started implementation of Apple‘s IPAD in its daily routine. Now CHIP‘s doctors and nurses can annotate, graph, access and process medical images, enter data, check status…, from anywhere in the hospital without the need to be in front of a computer.
The system adaptation has been developed by Kanteron Systems, who has added bar code scanning and medical use cameras, further enhancing the iPad‘s possibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDS translated into Catalan-Valencian among other languages</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/kds-translated-into-catalan-valencian-among-other-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2011 17:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/kds-translated-into-catalan-valencian-among-other-languages/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to offer KDS in Catalan-Valencian language (along with many others, such as English, Spanish, Italian, French, Japanese, Arabic&amp;hellip;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New KDS version 3.93</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/new-kds-version-3.93/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2011 10:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/new-kds-version-3.93/</guid>
      <description>Main improvements (most &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; to improve performance, stability and simplicity):
 PURE 64 BIT. KDS does not contain a single bit of 32 bit code any more. In fact, the program takes up very little room in the hard disk. It is lightweight, efficient, and fast (even much faster than OsiriX), because it has been developed with the latest development and code optimization tools from Apple (LLVM). NEW PLUG-IN MANAGEMENT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘ s solution for Dermatology</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/kanteron-s-solution-for-dermatology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 18:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/kanteron-s-solution-for-dermatology/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces a new solution for Dermatology. Based on a special microscope mounted on an iPhone, and a KDSworkstation, it allows the Dermatologist to take close-up pictures of the skin, which are automatically and wirelessly sent to the workstation, where the images are turned into DICOM (and therefore can be measured, annotated, etc), and sent to the PACS.
Should you wish to receive more information about this solution, please do not hesitate to contact Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems donates free DICOM CloudApp plug-in for Osirix</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/07/kanteron-systems-donates-free-dicom-cloudapp-plug-in-for-osirix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2011 22:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/07/kanteron-systems-donates-free-dicom-cloudapp-plug-in-for-osirix/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce the release of the CloudApp plug-in for Osirix and is making it available to the whole Osirix community for free.
The ever-growing involvement of Kanteron Systems with Free and Open Source healthcare projects like Osirix goes beyond being the largest (&amp;ldquo;Diamond&amp;rdquo;) Sponsors and involves coding, developing, from bug-detection and solution, to code improvement (such as increased AppleScript interoperability) to contributions both inside Osirix and externally such as this plug-in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems featured as a &#34;success case&#34; by AECTA</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/07/kanteron-systems-featured-as-a-success-case-by-aecta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2011 13:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/07/kanteron-systems-featured-as-a-success-case-by-aecta/</guid>
      <description>AECTA(Advanced Services Sector Consulting Association of Valencian Community) has chosen Kanteron Systems to be featured in their third edition of their book &amp;ldquo;Success Cases: competitive solutions&amp;rdquo; (pages 191-197), describing our R&amp;amp;D project &amp;ldquo;SICEIVI&amp;rdquo; as presented by the Valencian Innovation Institute (IVAI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems renews audited ISO 9001 quality management system</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/06/kanteron-systems-renews-audited-iso-9001-quality-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 18:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/06/kanteron-systems-renews-audited-iso-9001-quality-management-system/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems renews audited (by Bureau Veritas) ISO 9001 quality management system without a single non-conformance. The new certificate will soon be available in our Quality webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello interviewed in Venezuela Radio Station</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-interviewed-in-venezuela-radio-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 21:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-interviewed-in-venezuela-radio-station/</guid>
      <description>Marco Schiavottiello (Kanteron Systems‘ Product Manager), interviewed about IT solutions for digital medicla images by TecnologiaHechaPalabra, radio station broadcasting on 95.5fm, and belonging to the Venezuelan healthcare web portal most visited in Latin America.
The audio can be listened to here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering surgery with Kanteron PACS featured in TV</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/pioneering-surgery-with-kanteron-pacs-featured-in-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/pioneering-surgery-with-kanteron-pacs-featured-in-tv/</guid>
      <description>Televisa, Mexican TV, features in this video a pioneering surgical procedure in which Kanteron PACS (distributed in Mexico by Ceurac) referred to as &amp;ldquo;the most advanced, unique, in the country&amp;rdquo;, plays a fundamental part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDS plug-in for voice DICOM reports</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kds-plug-in-for-voice-dicom-reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kds-plug-in-for-voice-dicom-reports/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces a new KDS plug-in for recording voice reports directly in DICOM format. Based on NEMA specifications (completely standard and compatible). These recordings are automatically assigned to the corresponding study. Perfectly integrated with KDS, it allows to easily recognize all available audio series. With a simple click, recording can be listened to, modified (given the right permissions) and shared as many times as needed, with other nodes and workstations in the DICOM network, including other KDS and PACS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invited to Tech Ventures Conference – U. of Cambridge</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kanteron-systems-invited-to-tech-ventures-conference-u.-of-cambridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/kanteron-systems-invited-to-tech-ventures-conference-u.-of-cambridge/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited to participate in:
Technology Ventures Conference 2011
Ideas Economy: Changing the World by Connecting Ideas
9th of June 2011 – Cambridge Union, Cambridge, UK
Hosted by The Cambridge University Technology and Enterprise Club to enhance the entrepreneurial spirit amongst academics and students, by facilitating interaction between industry experts and students. Investors and the industries that support them in turn gain access to the vibrant research and entrepreneurial communities at the University of Cambridge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems finalist for the Young Innovative Company of the Year Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/kanteron-systems-finalist-for-the-young-innovative-company-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2011 11:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/kanteron-systems-finalist-for-the-young-innovative-company-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems financial performance</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/kanteron-systems-financial-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2011 00:06:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/kanteron-systems-financial-performance/</guid>
      <description>As the graph of audited end-of-year financial performance clearly shows, Kanteron Systems continues a strong growth year after year, having dedicated 25% of profits to R&amp;amp;D in 2010.
We would like to thank all our customers, distributors, employees, suppliers and collaborators, (we consider all of you friends) all of whom make this strong and continuous growth possible even in the most adverse and competitive market conditions ever.
Thank you!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems nominated for the 2011 European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-the-2011-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 19:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-the-2011-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased and honored to announce that Kanteron Systems has been selected for inclusion in the European Business Awards.
Every year the European Business Awards research team spend six months analysing over 15,000 companies across Europe to seek out the very best businesses that demonstrate the guiding principles of the Awards:
· Commercial success
· Innovation
· Business ethics
The award nomination research team &amp;ldquo;were particularly impressed with the success Jorge Cortell has had in leading and driving Kanteron Systems and the impact this has had across the business, having won the 4th Edition of Premio Emprendedor XXI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BDS named Distributor of the Year 2010, IBM named Reseller of the Year 2010</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/bds-named-distributor-of-the-year-2010-ibm-named-reseller-of-the-year-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 12:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/02/bds-named-distributor-of-the-year-2010-ibm-named-reseller-of-the-year-2010/</guid>
      <description>It is a pleasure to announce the winner of Kanteron‘s Distributor of the Year Award (Lima, Peru) and Reseller of the Year Award (IBM Peru).  It has been a close call, since competition was strong, but our Peru distributor and IBM deserve it since they have managed one very complex and successful project that joined Kanteron Systems, our Peru distributor and IBM in the most ambitious large-scale outsourced distributed medical imaging PACS in South America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New distributors</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/01/new-distributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/01/new-distributors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article about Kanteron in ValenciaPlaza</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/06/article-about-kanteron-in-valenciaplaza/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 19:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/06/article-about-kanteron-in-valenciaplaza/</guid>
      <description>Article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems first finalist in the national Entrepreneur of the Year Award XXI</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/06/kanteron-systems-first-finalist-in-the-national-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award-xxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 23:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/06/kanteron-systems-first-finalist-in-the-national-entrepreneur-of-the-year-award-xxi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article about Kanteron Systems in the news (Las Provincias)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/05/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-the-news-las-provincias/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2010 23:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/05/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-the-news-las-provincias/</guid>
      <description>Article(Spanish)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins the Entrepreneur of the Year (Comunidad Valenciana) Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/05/kanteron-systems-wins-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-comunidad-valenciana-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 23:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/05/kanteron-systems-wins-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-comunidad-valenciana-award/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron programmer’s discover (and fix) bug in SQL MacOSX</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/10/kanteron-programmers-discover-and-fix-bug-in-sql-macosx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 17:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/10/kanteron-programmers-discover-and-fix-bug-in-sql-macosx/</guid>
      <description>Currently being reported and the solution shared, Kanteron‘s programmers, while developing new functionalities for Kanteron‘s HIS (Hospital Information Systems) discovered a bug in SQL MacOSX by which the database would randomly (upon not detecting activity for an undetermined period of time) shutdown.After a few days of hard work, a solution has been discovered, and is now being shared with the rest of the community.Long live Open Source and Free Software!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON AMONG THE TOP 3 IN THE WORLD</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/kanteron-among-the-top-3-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 11:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/kanteron-among-the-top-3-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SELECTED BY EU TO PARTICIPATE IN THE GATEWAY PROGRAMME</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/kanteron-selected-by-eu-to-participate-in-the-gateway-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2009 15:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/kanteron-selected-by-eu-to-participate-in-the-gateway-programme/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON INTRODUCES ARSOR AT THE UNIVERSITY OF MALAGA</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/kanteron-introduces-arsor-at-the-university-of-malaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 15:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/kanteron-introduces-arsor-at-the-university-of-malaga/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS PROFILED AS SUCCESS CASE IN MASTER’S CLASS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/03/kanteron-systems-profiled-as-success-case-in-masters-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 15:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/03/kanteron-systems-profiled-as-success-case-in-masters-class/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON APPROVES A CAPITAL INCREASE</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/02/kanteron-approves-a-capital-increase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2009 15:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/02/kanteron-approves-a-capital-increase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON ACHIEVES RECORD RESULTS IN 2008 WITH A 456% GROWTH</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/01/kanteron-achieves-record-results-in-2008-with-a-456-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 15:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/01/kanteron-achieves-record-results-in-2008-with-a-456-growth/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS PROFILED IN TV PROGRAM ABOUT FREE SOFTWARE</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/11/kanteron-systems-profiled-in-tv-program-about-free-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2008 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/11/kanteron-systems-profiled-in-tv-program-about-free-software/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPEECH AT OPEN SOURCE WORLD CONFERENCE</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/10/speech-at-open-source-world-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 16:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/10/speech-at-open-source-world-conference/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON BECOMES OSIRIX FOUNDATION DIAMOND SPONSOR</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/10/kanteron-becomes-osirix-foundation-diamond-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/10/kanteron-becomes-osirix-foundation-diamond-sponsor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SIGNS RESEARCH AGREEMENT WITH CEU UNIVERSITY AND VET HOSPITAL</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/08/kanteron-signs-research-agreement-with-ceu-university-and-vet-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 16:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/08/kanteron-signs-research-agreement-with-ceu-university-and-vet-hospital/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON AND MAKIBER (GRUPO DRAGADOS) INTRODUCTION IN BEIJING</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/07/kanteron-and-makiber-grupo-dragados-introduction-in-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2008 16:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/07/kanteron-and-makiber-grupo-dragados-introduction-in-beijing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS RECEIVES ISO 9001 CERTIFICATION FROM BVQI</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/07/kanteron-systems-receives-iso-9001-certification-from-bvqi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 16:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/07/kanteron-systems-receives-iso-9001-certification-from-bvqi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS MIGRATES SERVERS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/06/kanteron-systems-migrates-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2008 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/06/kanteron-systems-migrates-servers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COMMERCIAL MISSIONS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/06/commercial-missions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2008 16:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/06/commercial-missions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACCORDING TO A STUDY, KANTERON HAS THE FASTEST PACS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/according-to-a-study-kanteron-has-the-fastest-pacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2008 16:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/according-to-a-study-kanteron-has-the-fastest-pacs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LECTURE AT EUROPEAN UNIVERSITY OF MADRID (UEM)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/lecture-at-european-university-of-madrid-uem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2008 16:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/lecture-at-european-university-of-madrid-uem/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDS SHOWN IN A CIRD SESSION</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/kds-shown-in-a-cird-session/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2008 16:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/kds-shown-in-a-cird-session/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARTICLE ABOUT KANTERON SYSTEMS IN LAS PROVINCIAS (03/04/08)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-las-provincias-03/04/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 16:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-las-provincias-03/04/08/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS SIGNS AN AGREEMENT WITH IMAGING BIOMETRICS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/kanteron-systems-signs-an-agreement-with-imaging-biometrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2008 16:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/04/kanteron-systems-signs-an-agreement-with-imaging-biometrics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS RECEIVES FDA CLEARANCE FOR ITS MULTIMODAL DICOM WORKSTATION KDS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/03/kanteron-systems-receives-fda-clearance-for-its-multimodal-dicom-workstation-kds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2008 16:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/03/kanteron-systems-receives-fda-clearance-for-its-multimodal-dicom-workstation-kds/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS MOVES ITS HEADQUARTERS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/02/kanteron-systems-moves-its-headquarters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2008 16:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2008/02/kanteron-systems-moves-its-headquarters/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LECTURE AT THE ANNUAL OSIRIX USER GROUP MEETING</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/11/lecture-at-the-annual-osirix-user-group-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2007 16:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/11/lecture-at-the-annual-osirix-user-group-meeting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS ORGANICES A CRUISE DURING RSNA</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/11/kanteron-systems-organices-a-cruise-during-rsna/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2007 16:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/11/kanteron-systems-organices-a-cruise-during-rsna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LECTURE AT THE ANNUAL ISMRM – SMRT MEETING</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/10/lecture-at-the-annual-ismrm-smrt-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2007 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/10/lecture-at-the-annual-ismrm-smrt-meeting/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS NOMINATED FOR TWO INNOVATOR OF THE YEAR 2007 AWARDS BY THE WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/06/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-two-innovator-of-the-year-2007-awards-by-the-wall-street-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2007 16:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/06/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-two-innovator-of-the-year-2007-awards-by-the-wall-street-journal/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LECTURE AT II OPEN SOURCE WORLD CONFERENCE</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/06/lecture-at-ii-open-source-world-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jun 2007 16:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/06/lecture-at-ii-open-source-world-conference/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VALENCIA’S PRO SOCCER TEAM DOCTOR CHOOSES KDS</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/05/valencias-pro-soccer-team-doctor-chooses-kds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2007 16:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/05/valencias-pro-soccer-team-doctor-chooses-kds/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARTICLE ABOUT KANTERON SYSTEMS IN EL HOSPITAL (04/07)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/04/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-el-hospital-04/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2007 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/04/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-el-hospital-04/07/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARTICLE ABOUT KANTERON SYSTEMS IN EMPRESA Y FINANZAS (25/03/07)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/03/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-empresa-y-finanzas-25/03/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2007 16:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/03/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-empresa-y-finanzas-25/03/07/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARTICLE ABOUT KANTERON SYSTEMS IN LAS PROVINCIAS (18/03/07)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/03/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-las-provincias-18/03/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2007 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2007/03/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-las-provincias-18/03/07/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARTICLE ABOUT KANTERON SYSTEMS IN LA GACETA TECNOLÓGICA (12/06)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2006/12/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-la-gaceta-tecnol%C3%B3gica-12/06/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2006 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2006/12/article-about-kanteron-systems-in-la-gaceta-tecnol%C3%B3gica-12/06/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON SYSTEMS INTRODUCES KDS AT THE II INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM “DIGITAL IMAGE IN RADIOLOGY AND ITS SURROUNDINGS”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2006/10/kanteron-systems-introduces-kds-at-the-ii-international-symposium-digital-image-in-radiology-and-its-surroundings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 16:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2006/10/kanteron-systems-introduces-kds-at-the-ii-international-symposium-digital-image-in-radiology-and-its-surroundings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KANTERON ORGANIZES THE I TECHNOLOGY SESSION “EXTENDING DIGITAL MEDICAL IMAGING TO ALL SPECIALTIES”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2006/04/kanteron-organizes-the-i-technology-session-extending-digital-medical-imaging-to-all-specialties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2006 16:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2006/04/kanteron-organizes-the-i-technology-session-extending-digital-medical-imaging-to-all-specialties/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>