<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HealthCare on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/healthcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HealthCare on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Kanteron found &#34;AI in Health Partner Alliance&#34; along with 20 other tech companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft, Kanteron Systems, and 20 other technology companies have set up the &amp;ldquo;AI in Health Partner Alliance&amp;rdquo; to leverage the founding members&amp;rsquo; vision of Democratizing Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems featured in latest Frost &amp; Sullivan’s healthcare report</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-featured-in-latest-frost-sullivans-healthcare-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-featured-in-latest-frost-sullivans-healthcare-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The report lists Kanteron Systems as one of the 12 leading companies in Healthcare’s Emerging Business Models.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron wins the California Impact Challenge in Precision Medicine award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/09/kanteron-wins-the-california-impact-challenge-in-precision-medicine-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/09/kanteron-wins-the-california-impact-challenge-in-precision-medicine-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been recognized as the leader in Precision Medicine, and awarded the 2016 Precision Medicine Impact Challenge Award by The California Governor’s Office of Planning and Research (OPR) and the Governor’s Office of Business and Economic Development (GO-Biz), in collaboration with Singularity University (SU).
The Precision Medicine Impact Challenge was announced by Atul Butte, MD, PhD, director of the UCSF Institute for Computational Health Sciences, and Elizabeth Baca, MD, MPA, from the Governor‘s OPR at the Precision Public Health summit hosted by UCSF in June 2016, convened by the White House and Bill &amp;amp; Melinda Gates Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General availability of Kanteron source code for NHS announced at the UK Radiology Congress 2016</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/general-availability-of-kanteron-source-code-for-nhs-announced-at-the-uk-radiology-congress-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 17:04:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/general-availability-of-kanteron-source-code-for-nhs-announced-at-the-uk-radiology-congress-2016/</guid>
      <description>Shawn Larson, Senior Project Manager at HSCIC, announced the general availability of Kanteron source code for the NHS on Monday, June 6, at UKRC (the largest diagnostic imaging event in the UK). The announcement was made during the session: PACS 2.0 (the next generation) has now happened – any real difference?
In conjunction with HSCIC’s OpenPACS and NHS England’s Code 4 Health / Open Source initiatives, Kanteron Systems has made the source code of its Translational Medical Information Server (TMIS) platform freely available to the NHS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron CEO guest speaker at KPMG UK Health event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-ceo-guest-speaker-at-kpmg-uk-health-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 20:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-ceo-guest-speaker-at-kpmg-uk-health-event/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems‘ CEO was invited by KPMG UKto be a guest speaker at their Health Get Together event yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay participates in Health 2.0 Valencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, participated yesterday in the Health 2.0 event organized by InnDEA, and featuring Tellmegen, eKuore and Kanteron, in Las Naves (Valencia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron’s DirectTransfer radically transforms medical imaging device connectivity: no more need for firewalls, SSL or NAT</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanterons-directtransfer-radically-transforms-medical-imaging-device-connectivity-no-more-need-for-firewalls-ssl-or-nat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 05:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanterons-directtransfer-radically-transforms-medical-imaging-device-connectivity-no-more-need-for-firewalls-ssl-or-nat/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th EU Health Innovation event at Microsoft’s Brussels EBC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 20:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</guid>
      <description>This Tuesday and Wednesday Kanteron Systems was invited to participate in Microsoft’s 5th Health Innovation event, in the Exhibition Area, along with 5 other selected partners.
Titled “EmpoweringHealth: the journey towards more personalized, productive, collaborative and predictive health services &amp;amp; systems” it took place at the Microsoft Executive Briefing Center in Brussels.Kanteron Systems‘ CEO, Jorge Cortell, participated in the round table “Medical Imaging Storage in the Cloud”, moderated by Kelly Limonte (Microsoft UK Healthcare Team), and in the Expert Panel “The future of preventive and predictive health powered by data in the intelligent cloud”, along with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Report “Valencia: Healthcare Innovation and Research” Features Kanteron as a Success Case</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/the-report-valencia-healthcare-innovation-and-research-features-kanteron-as-a-success-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 19:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/the-report-valencia-healthcare-innovation-and-research-features-kanteron-as-a-success-case/</guid>
      <description>InnDEA Valencia Foundation, through the VIT Salud Innovation Network, released yesterday the report “Valencia: Healthcare Innovation and Research”, produced by the Valencian Institute of Economic Research (IVIE).
Javier Quesada, author of the report, is an IVIE researcher and Professor of Economic Analysis at Valencia University (UV). The report highlights that the healthcare economic activity in the city has grown “much faster” than the rest of the economic activity and it represents 5,3% of all economic activity in the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems publishes advanced medical image algorithms in IBM Cloud marketplace</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-publishes-advanced-medical-image-algorithms-in-ibm-cloud-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 10:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/11/kanteron-systems-publishes-advanced-medical-image-algorithms-in-ibm-cloud-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems today announced a partnership with IBM that brings the power of Medical Imaging Analysis to the IBM Cloud marketplace. Starting today, IBM clients can integrate very specific tools for medical image processing and analysis into their workflows with the click of a button.
The first available digital pathology image algorithms perform color separation for Hematoxylin, Eosin and Diaminobenzidine immunohistochemical staining.
The IBM Cloud marketplace offers client’s access to more than 100 SaaS applications, IBM‘s Bluemix™ platform-as-a-service with its suite of composable services, the powerful SoftLayer infrastructure-as-a-service and IBM‘s rich intellectual capital and deep industry expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in the national HealthIT Innovation tour</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-national-healthit-innovation-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-national-healthit-innovation-tour/</guid>
      <description>The TIC Salud National HealthIT Innovation Touris an initiative that organizes events in different Spanish regions so that companies in the industry can present their latest innovations in the field of HealthIT to healthcare professionals and executives. The Committee will be formed by deputy directors of Information Technology, CEO‘s, CIO‘s and medical directors. Following each of the presentations, committee members will ask questions directed to the speakers about their innovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: Global Digital Pathology Market CAGR 11.8% to 2018, Kanteron listed as &#34;major player&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/report-global-digital-pathology-market-cagr-11.8-to-2018-kanteron-listed-as-major-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 19:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/report-global-digital-pathology-market-cagr-11.8-to-2018-kanteron-listed-as-major-player/</guid>
      <description>MarketsandMarketsrecently published “Digital Pathology Market by Slide Scanners (Whole Slide Imaging), Analytics (Image Analysis Software), Delivery Modes (Web Based/Cloud Based) &amp;amp; by Whole Slide Image Storage – Global Forecasts &amp;amp; Trends to 2018″ (available for purchase online), listing Kanteron Systems as a &amp;ldquo;major player&amp;quot;in the worldwide Digital Pathology market.
This report covers the definition, description, and forecast of the digital pathology market in terms of products and applications; the digital pathology market comprises of scanners, analytics, storage, and communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The latest healthcare technology report from Gartner features Kanteron as VNA sample vendor</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/the-latest-healthcare-technology-report-from-gartner-features-kanteron-as-vna-sample-vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 16:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/the-latest-healthcare-technology-report-from-gartner-features-kanteron-as-vna-sample-vendor/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been featured as VNA (Vendor-Neutral Archive) sample vendor in Gartner‘s latest healthcare technology report: Hype Cycle for Healthcare Providers Technologies and Standards, written by veteran industry analyst Barry Runyon.
 The Hype Cycle for Healthcare Providers Technologies and Standards is a vital reference for healthcare delivery organization CIOs and IT leadership when assessing the value of existing and emerging information technologies and standards. It provides insight necessary to remain competitive in a rapidly evolving healthcare provider marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems joins the Global Alliance for Genomics and Health</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/03/kanteron-systems-joins-the-global-alliance-for-genomics-and-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2014 23:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/03/kanteron-systems-joins-the-global-alliance-for-genomics-and-health/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce it has joined institutions like Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard, American Society of Clinical Oncology, Massachusetts General Hospital, Mayo Clinic, Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, IBM, or Google, in the Global Alliance for Genomics and Health.
The Global Alliance for Genomics and Health (Global Alliance) is an international coalition, formed by over 150 of the world’s leading organizations (including healthcare providers, research funders, research institutions, disease advocacy organizations, and life science and information technology companies) to enable the sharing of genomic and clinical data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Top 50 to Top 10 in a week! Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 10 (Healthcare) for Web Traffic Rank Growth</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/from-top-50-to-top-10-in-a-week-kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-10-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 16:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/from-top-50-to-top-10-in-a-week-kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-10-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 for Web Traffic Rank Growth according to new ranking company SIGNL.
Rank: #9 of 2,436 Health Care Methodology: SIGNL’s algorithm analyzes millions of data points including web/mobile traffic, social buzz, company growth, and more to identify companies with the highest momentum.
Kanteron Systems, following the stellar presentation of TMIS at RSNAChicago, is experiencing incredible momentum with the anticipated new product developments introduced at HIMSSOrlando (Genomics + Pharmacogenomics + Activity and Sleep Trackers + Analytics) as third party vendor independent PACS-VNA-EMR add-on plug-ins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 (Healthcare) for Web Traffic Rank Growth</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-50-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 19:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-50-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 for Web Traffic Rank Growth according to new ranking company SIGNL.
Rank: #32 of 2,436 Health CareMethodology: SIGNL‘s algorithm analyzes millions of data points including web/mobile traffic, social buzz, company growth, and more to identify companies with the highest momentum.
Kanteron Systems, following the stellar presentation of TMIS at RSNAChicago, is experiencing incredible momentum with the anticipated new product developments to be introduced at HIMSSOrlando (hint: Genomics + Pharmacogenomics + Activity and Sleep Trackers + Analytics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to deliver a lecture at the VI Biomedical Engineering Meeting</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, February 6 2014 at 16h, Kanteron Systems‘ Juan Tatay (Director) and Carlos Villanueva (R&amp;amp;D Engineer) will deliver the lecture “Precise diagnostics for personalized medicine: medical imaging and big data” at the Cajal Room, 1st floor, School of Medicine, University of Valencia (Spain) within the VI Biomedical Engineering Meetingof the Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia‘s Official Interuniversity Master Degree in Biomedical Engineering. Other lectures will be delivered by Philips Research, Indra Sistemas and General Electric Healthcare amongst others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in consortium to develop 3D implants</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-participates-in-consortium-to-develop-3d-implants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 12:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-participates-in-consortium-to-develop-3d-implants/</guid>
      <description>A new generation of personalized implants has been designed to compete in time and costs with traditional manufacturing. The project, co-financed by CDTI has achieved excellent results in its initial phases and aims to be the definitive step towards personalized implants.
The consortium members are: Surgival, AMES, Biotechnology Institute, QuironHospital Group, Kanteron Systems (developing the imaging component); and the research institutes Biomedical Institute of Valencia (IBV), and Metalmechanic Technology Institute (AIMME).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan on Kanteron Systems’ latest innovation: “WOW!”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</guid>
      <description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivanprofiles Kanteron Systems in the “WOW!” section of their latest Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics report.
Global growth consulting firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, which provides market research and analysis for the Healthcare Industry (amongst others), published today the report “RSNA 2013 Review: Scouting the Showfloor for the Latest-Greatest in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics”. In the report’s “Select WOW! Findings from the Showfloor” section, Nadim Michel Daher, Principal Analyst – Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics, and Siddharth Saha, Global Program Leader Advanced MedTech, identify six companies with disruptive innovations in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM features Kanteron Systems in success case</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-success-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 01:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-success-case/</guid>
      <description>In the Case Studies section of their website, IBM published the case &amp;ldquo;A healthcare system in South America deploys a private cloud. Using virtualization to extend medical services to rural communities&amp;rdquo; featuring Kanteron Systems.
Link.
PDF version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems introduces the first Translational PACS-VNA in the world at RSNA 2013</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 00:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</guid>
      <description>PRESS RELEASE First Translational Medical Imaging System in the World New York, NY, USA, November 27, 2013
 Kanteron Systems will launch the world‘s first Translational Medical Imaging System (“TMIS”) at the Radiology Society of North America (“RSNA”) annual meeting in Chicago, December 1-5, 2013. TMIS is a fully integrated solution for radiology, genetic and pathology workflows that could change the way medicine is practiced.
 Translational research is an emerging field that aims to provide a better understanding of the molecular basis of disease, which in turn will inform clinical practice and ultimately improve human health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins 2013 IBM Beacon Award for Healthcare and Life Sciences</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-wins-2013-ibm-beacon-award-for-healthcare-and-life-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 01:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-wins-2013-ibm-beacon-award-for-healthcare-and-life-sciences/</guid>
      <description>IBM Beacon Awards recognize IBM Business Partners for their technical excellence, industry expertise, and innovative solutions.
Kanteron Systems was named a winner of a 2013 IBM Beacon Award for Healthcare and Life Sciences. This honor is awarded each year in recognition of a select number of IBM Business Partners who have delivered not only innovative solutions but have set the standards for business excellence, ingenuity, and creation of an exceptional client experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems awarded &#34;Best Clinical Poster Award&#34; at Digital Pathology Association Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 01:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is honored to have been awarded &amp;ldquo;Best Clinical Poster Award&amp;rdquo; at Digital Pathology Association Congress 2012 Pathology Visions, held in Baltimore (USA), October 28th-October 31st.
The poster was titled: &amp;ldquo;Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web)&amp;rdquo; and was presented and authored by Jorge Cortell CEO &amp;amp; President, Kanteron Systems USA, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online demo of Kanteron Systems digital pathology image (WSI) viewer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/online-demo-of-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-image-wsi-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2012 17:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/online-demo-of-kanteron-systems-digital-pathology-image-wsi-viewer/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces an online demo to try the speed of our digital pathology image (Whole Slide Image) viewer: https://pathoarchive.kanteron.com/As you try it, keep in mind there might be thousands of concurrent users, your bandwidth may be limited, and most important: you will be browsing 2 to 6 GIGABYTE images (from different scanner manufacturers and formats, DICOM ready)&amp;hellip; in real time!! with a zero footprint viewer (no need to install any additional software).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Alvaro Gonzalez and Jorge Cortell talk about healthcare IT security at HOPE9</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘ Alvaro González(CTO) and Jorge Cortell(CEO) spoke today about &amp;ldquo;Digital Security in Health Care Institutions&amp;rdquo; during Hackers On Planet Earth number 9, New York, one of the most creative and diverse hacker events in the world (since 1994).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invited to attend IBM‘s &#34;Redefining Value and Success in Healthcare&#34; business event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-invited-to-attend-ibms-redefining-value-and-success-in-healthcare-business-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 17:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-invited-to-attend-ibms-redefining-value-and-success-in-healthcare-business-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited to attend, as Independent Software Vendor (ISV) IBM‘s &amp;ldquo;Redefining Value and Success in Healthcare&amp;rdquo; business event, led by Dan Pelino, at the IBM Innovation Center and Healthcare Transformation Lab, Chicago (USA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems delivers new Cardiac PACS at NHS-GOSH and migrates more than 10 million images in a weekend</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-delivers-new-cardiac-pacs-at-nhs-gosh-and-migrates-more-than-10-million-images-in-a-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-delivers-new-cardiac-pacs-at-nhs-gosh-and-migrates-more-than-10-million-images-in-a-weekend/</guid>
      <description>As seen in The Guardian, Building Better Healthcare, BBC, Healthcare IT News, E-Health Insider, Open Health News, eHealth Europe, Hospital IT Europe, UK Government Online, UK Government Opportunities, and Healthcare Today:
London’s Great Ormond Street Children’s Hospital (GOSH) is making a major shift towards integrating Apple technology – benefiting staff and patients. A key project has been in Cardiology where clinicians now use iPads and iMacs for instant access to 3D images of patients’ hearts while planning for surgery, or even in theatre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kauffman report: Biomedical IPOs had the highest survival and lowest bankruptcy rates among all sectors</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kauffman-report-biomedical-ipos-had-the-highest-survival-and-lowest-bankruptcy-rates-among-all-sectors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 16:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kauffman-report-biomedical-ipos-had-the-highest-survival-and-lowest-bankruptcy-rates-among-all-sectors/</guid>
      <description>According to a Kauffman study:
 Among Emerging Growth Companies firms that made IPOs from 1996 through 2000, only 29 percent were still operating 10 years later. However, acquisition was a far more common outcome than was failure (55 percent vs. 16 percent). Biomedical IPOs had the highest survival and lowest bankruptcy rates among all sectors; the highest failure rates were in manufacturing and retail.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation barriers in healthcare technology</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/innovation-barriers-in-healthcare-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 16:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/innovation-barriers-in-healthcare-technology/</guid>
      <description>From a ReadWriteWeb article:
 Dr. J. Deane Waldman, Professor of Pediatrics, Pathology &amp;amp; Decision Science at the University of New Mexico said the industry has three disincentives to innovation that will partly suppress the effect of Moore‘s law, including:
 Regulatory oversight that is completely focussed on compliance. &amp;ldquo;It discourages risk-taking and innovation,&amp;rdquo; Deane said. Health care doesn‘t have the same financial reward system. Facebook isn‘t about to pay $1 billion for the latest hot-ticket item in imaging and informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical joke</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/medical-joke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 15:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/medical-joke/</guid>
      <description>source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initiative to reduce medical tests and procedures that may be unnecessary</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/initiative-to-reduce-medical-tests-and-procedures-that-may-be-unnecessary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2012 16:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/initiative-to-reduce-medical-tests-and-procedures-that-may-be-unnecessary/</guid>
      <description>Choosing Wiselyis an initiative of the ABIM Foundation focused on encouraging physicians, patients and other health care stakeholders to think and talk about medical tests and procedures that may be unnecessary, and in some instances can cause harm. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Ribera Hospital chosen as &#34;model&#34; by European Union, orders more systems from Kanteron</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/la-ribera-hospital-chosen-as-model-by-european-union-orders-more-systems-from-kanteron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 05:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/la-ribera-hospital-chosen-as-model-by-european-union-orders-more-systems-from-kanteron/</guid>
      <description>La Ribera University Hospital (Spain) has been chosen along with other 3 European healthcare institutions, as basis for the report titled “Healthcare of the Future”. This has been approved by the European Commissioner for Health and Consumer Policy, John Dalli and La Ribera University Hospital managers, in a meeting in Paris. The report is written by the European Union Directorate General for Health and Consumer Policy in collaboration with COCIR (European Coordination Commitee of the Radiological, Electromedical and Heathcare IT Industry), group that includes some of the main healthcare tech companies in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Advanced Medical Technology Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/the-u.s.-advanced-medical-technology-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 20:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/the-u.s.-advanced-medical-technology-industry/</guid>
      <description>According to the study “The Economic Impact of the U.S. Advanced Medical Technology Industry” released by the Advanced Medical Technology Association (AdvaMed) prepared by Battelle Technology Partnership Practice, the advanced medical technology industry is responsible for generating over $113 billion in personal income for workers, $381 in billion in national economic output and almost 1.9 million U.S. jobs.
Source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems presentation at NYC Health 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems, presented (soon available via livestream) yesterday some of the company‘s solutions geared towards reducing hospital readmission to a group of 70 professionals at the VNS of NY HQ (10 E 70th St., New York) during a Health 2.0 NYC – The New York Healthcare Innovation Groupmeeting.
Here are some of the twitter-comments from that session:
globalfjord ‏ @globalfjord
Health 2.0 companies to watch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMSS: Vendor-neutral archive can solve PACS problems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/himss-vendor-neutral-archive-can-solve-pacs-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/himss-vendor-neutral-archive-can-solve-pacs-problems/</guid>
      <description>According to a presentation by Michael J. Gray of Gray Consulting at a webinar on Jan. 26 hosted by the Healthcare Information and Management Systems Society (HIMSS):
 Implementation of a vendor-neutral archive (VNA) solves most of the problems associated with PACS, can save money over the long term and can prepare an enterprise to participate in a health information exchange (HIE)
 SourceKanteron Systems is a leading global supplier of vendor-neutral archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market For Mobile Health Apps Projected To Quadruple To $400 Million By 2016</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/market-for-mobile-health-apps-projected-to-quadruple-to-400-million-by-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 22:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/market-for-mobile-health-apps-projected-to-quadruple-to-400-million-by-2016/</guid>
      <description>Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: Double-digit growth to propel PACS market to $5.4B by 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/report-double-digit-growth-to-propel-pacs-market-to-5.4b-by-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 16:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/report-double-digit-growth-to-propel-pacs-market-to-5.4b-by-2017/</guid>
      <description>Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey: EU hospitals spent $3.2B on IT in 2010</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/survey-eu-hospitals-spent-3.2b-on-it-in-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2012 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/survey-eu-hospitals-spent-3.2b-on-it-in-2010/</guid>
      <description>Report</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open knowledge saves lives. Oppose H.R. 3699!</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/open-knowledge-saves-lives.-oppose-h.r.-3699/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2012 19:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/open-knowledge-saves-lives.-oppose-h.r.-3699/</guid>
      <description>Great article by Gilles Frydman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Speech Recognition is not ready for primetime&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/speech-recognition-is-not-ready-for-primetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2012 16:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/speech-recognition-is-not-ready-for-primetime/</guid>
      <description>Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KDS helps in intracraneal electrode surgery planning for an OCD patient</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/kds-helps-in-intracraneal-electrode-surgery-planning-for-an-ocd-patient/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 17:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/11/kds-helps-in-intracraneal-electrode-surgery-planning-for-an-ocd-patient/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Gutierrez, a neurosurgeon in La Fe hospital (Valencia, Spain), uses KDS to plan intracraneal electrode surgery for OCD.
Source: El Mundo, LevanteVideo: EFE KDS in surgery planning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: US Health System‘s score only 64 out of 100</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/report-us-health-systems-score-only-64-out-of-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/report-us-health-systems-score-only-64-out-of-100/</guid>
      <description>According to the Commonwealth Fund‘s &amp;ldquo;The National Scorecard on U.S. Health System Performance, 2011&amp;rdquo; report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: EHR market to hit $6.5B in 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/report-ehr-market-to-hit-6.5b-in-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 11:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/report-ehr-market-to-hit-6.5b-in-2012/</guid>
      <description>Source: Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speech recognition still worst option</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/speech-recognition-still-worst-option/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 12:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/10/speech-recognition-still-worst-option/</guid>
      <description>According to this articlein the American Journal of Roentgenography:
 Complex breast imaging reports generated with ASR were associated with higher error rates than reports generated with conventional dictation transcription. The native language and the academic rank of the speaker did not have a strong influence on error rate.
 More infoon why Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR) is still the worst option in Dalai‘s PACS Blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems delivers a Vascular Diagnostic Update Course</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-delivers-a-vascular-diagnostic-update-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-delivers-a-vascular-diagnostic-update-course/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems delivers a lecture in the Vascular Diagnostic Update Course held at the Polytechnic and University Hospital La Fe (Valencia – Spain), September 29 and 30, 2011, during the XIV National CDVNI-SEACV Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHIP pioneer in iPad healthcare application</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/chip-pioneer-in-ipad-healthcare-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 09:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/chip-pioneer-in-ipad-healthcare-application/</guid>
      <description>CHIP Hospital, always on the leading edge of technology, has started implementation of Apple‘s IPAD in its daily routine. Now CHIP‘s doctors and nurses can annotate, graph, access and process medical images, enter data, check status…, from anywhere in the hospital without the need to be in front of a computer.
The system adaptation has been developed by Kanteron Systems, who has added bar code scanning and medical use cameras, further enhancing the iPad‘s possibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron can help US radiologist with MU</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-can-help-us-radiologist-with-mu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 16:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-can-help-us-radiologist-with-mu/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot;Meaningful Use&amp;rdquo; means big incentives for US radiologistIF (and only IF) they integrate certain new technologies into their PACS/RIS systems. Lucky Kanteron Systems, as one of the lead developers in this field, is perfectly positioned to help US radiologist with this. Make sure you contactus!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘ s solution for Dermatology</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/kanteron-s-solution-for-dermatology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 18:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/08/kanteron-s-solution-for-dermatology/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems introduces a new solution for Dermatology. Based on a special microscope mounted on an iPhone, and a KDSworkstation, it allows the Dermatologist to take close-up pictures of the skin, which are automatically and wirelessly sent to the workstation, where the images are turned into DICOM (and therefore can be measured, annotated, etc), and sent to the PACS.
Should you wish to receive more information about this solution, please do not hesitate to contact Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering surgery with Kanteron PACS featured in TV</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/pioneering-surgery-with-kanteron-pacs-featured-in-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/pioneering-surgery-with-kanteron-pacs-featured-in-tv/</guid>
      <description>Televisa, Mexican TV, features in this video a pioneering surgical procedure in which Kanteron PACS (distributed in Mexico by Ceurac) referred to as &amp;ldquo;the most advanced, unique, in the country&amp;rdquo;, plays a fundamental part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambridge report on how mobile apps are changing healthcare in China</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/cambridge-report-on-how-mobile-apps-are-changing-healthcare-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2011 09:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/05/cambridge-report-on-how-mobile-apps-are-changing-healthcare-in-china/</guid>
      <description>Press release.
Report.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitor admiring our work</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/competitor-admiring-our-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2011 00:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/04/competitor-admiring-our-work/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Kanteron‘s technician: Images seem to have arrived correctly, would you like to check anything in particular? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; **MultinationalX**‘s technician: It would be nice to know if you have received all the data without errors or if I have to take any information field out in case your workstation does not support it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; Kanteron‘s technician: Here you have the transmission log, everything correct, and if you press this button, you can see the whole associated metadata list, including your data from **MultinationalX**.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We have been offering it for 5 years, now the industry names it: VNA</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/11/we-have-been-offering-it-for-5-years-now-the-industry-names-it-vna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2010 12:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2010/11/we-have-been-offering-it-for-5-years-now-the-industry-names-it-vna/</guid>
      <description>VNA, Vendor-Neutral Archive is being used to describe &amp;ldquo;digital medical imaging storage solutions independent from modality manufacturers, which offer cost reduction and interoperability&amp;rdquo;. The term has been in use for a few months, and media and studies are making it a term used more and more. Worthwile noting: Capsite study in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government could save time, money with open-source NHIN</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/11/government-could-save-time-money-with-open-source-nhin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2009 08:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/11/government-could-save-time-money-with-open-source-nhin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Role of CT in PostMortem “autopsy”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/10/role-of-ct-in-postmortem-autopsy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 18:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/10/role-of-ct-in-postmortem-autopsy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thomson Reuters: Recessionary pressures on U.S. hospitals are finally beginning to ease</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/08/thomson-reuters-recessionary-pressures-on-u.s.-hospitals-are-finally-beginning-to-ease/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2009 11:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/08/thomson-reuters-recessionary-pressures-on-u.s.-hospitals-are-finally-beginning-to-ease/</guid>
      <description>Thomson Reuters reported that the profit margin of U.S. hospitals was 3.1 % in the 3rd quarter of 2009, up from 0.17 % in the 3rd quarter of 2008. The increase in profit margin applied to all classes of hospitals, including small, medium and large community hospitals, as well as teaching hospitals and major academic medical centers.Total hospital margins improved in the 1st quarter, with about 30 % of hospitals operating in the red–a big improvement over the 50 % reported in the 3rd quarter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radiologist workload increases 7%, but work hours remain the same thanks to IT</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/08/radiologist-workload-increases-7-but-work-hours-remain-the-same-thanks-to-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 16:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/08/radiologist-workload-increases-7-but-work-hours-remain-the-same-thanks-to-it/</guid>
      <description>Source. Radiologists‘ workloads grew substantially in the past few years, with procedures increasing 7 % and physician work relative value units (RVUs) increasing 10 % from 2002-2003 to 2006-2007, according to research published in this month‘s Radiology by Mythreyi Bhargavan, PhD, from the research department at the American College of Radiology (ACR) and the department of radiology and radiological science at Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore, and colleagues.In 2006-2007, the researchers reported that the average annual workload per FTE radiologist was 14,900 procedures, an increase of 7 % since 2002-2003 and 34 % since 1991-1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe can teach the USA some lessons regarding EHR</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/08/europe-can-teach-the-usa-some-lessons-regarding-ehr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 16:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/08/europe-can-teach-the-usa-some-lessons-regarding-ehr/</guid>
      <description>Source. A recently-published report by Harald A. Deutsch, MD, and Fran Turisco of the Computer Sciences Corporation (CSC), an IT and business services company headquartered in Falls Church, Va. on EHR and health information exchange (HIE) initiatives suggests that the United States should look at similar efforts in Europe as a guide for its development of large-scale e-health systems.The report paints a bleak historical picture of U.S. e-health initiatives. According to the authors, a review of 145 HIEs implemented in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals seek vendor neutrality</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/hospitals-seek-vendor-neutrality/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2009 19:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/hospitals-seek-vendor-neutrality/</guid>
      <description>Many hospitals are considering vendor-neutral solutions for archiving and accessing medical images to avoid being locked into closed, proprietary software, according the report &amp;ldquo;In Enterprise Imaging: A Vendor Reality Check&amp;rdquo; from market research firm KLAS.The study found that while many providers are looking to their PACS vendor as a likely enterprise imaging partner, they also recognize the potential pitfalls of getting locked into a proprietary solution that may not translate well from one department to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireless telehealth to reach 15 million systems in North America by 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/wireless-telehealth-to-reach-15-million-systems-in-north-america-by-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2009 17:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/07/wireless-telehealth-to-reach-15-million-systems-in-north-america-by-2012/</guid>
      <description>A publication from ABI Research examines wireless telehealth and forecasts that 15 million systems will be in use–mainly in North America–by early in 2012. Source.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Turns Away Ambulances When Computers Go Down</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/hospital-turns-away-ambulances-when-computers-go-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2009 09:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/hospital-turns-away-ambulances-when-computers-go-down/</guid>
      <description>The Indianapolis Star reportsthat Tuesday June 2nd, Methodist Hospital turned away patients in ambulances, for the first time in its 100-plus history. Why? Because the electronic health records (EHR) system had gone down the prior afternoon — due to a power surge — and the backlog of paperwork was no longer tolerable.Kanteron Systems offers high-availability HIS and EHR technology, with off-site and disaster recovery options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study: Medical imaging increases U.S. life expectancy</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/study-medical-imaging-increases-u.s.-life-expectancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2009 21:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/study-medical-imaging-increases-u.s.-life-expectancy/</guid>
      <description>Increased utilization of advanced medical imaging has improved the life expectancy of patients in the United States by nearly nine months, according to a study, led by Columbia University economics professor Frank Lichtenberg, PhD, released this month from the National Bureau of Economic Research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EHR implementation feasible for small, rural practices</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/ehr-implementation-feasible-for-small-rural-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2009 09:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/06/ehr-implementation-feasible-for-small-rural-practices/</guid>
      <description>Source</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why lack of innovation is not sustainable long-term in HealthcareIT</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/05/why-lack-of-innovation-is-not-sustainable-long-term-in-healthcareit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 17:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/05/why-lack-of-innovation-is-not-sustainable-long-term-in-healthcareit/</guid>
      <description>Vince explainsquite simply why lack of innovation and interoperability are not sustainable in the long-term when it comes to HealthcareIT.In Kanteron Systems we are quite aware of that, and that‘s why we are constantly innovating. As a matter of fact, stay tunedbecause in less than a month we will be releasing two world-firsts that will make us world leaders in Healthcare IT innovation. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron’s solutions immune to the Conficker virus and hacker attacks</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/05/kanterons-solutions-immune-to-the-conficker-virus-and-hacker-attacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2009 10:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/05/kanterons-solutions-immune-to-the-conficker-virus-and-hacker-attacks/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce that after extensive testing we can assure our customers that our solutions (PACS, KDS, HIS, KWLS, and KRC) are immune to the Conficker virus that according to the San Jose Mercury News is affecting hundreds of medical devices and systems in dozens of hospitals in several countries. Our systems are indeed immune to any known virus and black-hat hacker intrusions, such as the one that the FBI is investigatingin which a computer black-hat hacker is demanding a ransom of 10 millions US$ in return for over 35 million patients prescriptions in Virginia (USA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US law calls for Open Source EHRs</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/us-law-calls-for-open-source-ehrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2009 10:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/us-law-calls-for-open-source-ehrs/</guid>
      <description>Source: healthimaging.comSenator John D. Rockefeller IV, D-W. Va., introduced legislation last week that will facilitate the nationwide adoption of EHRs.The Health Information Technology Public Utility Act of 2009 will build upon the use of open-source EHRs by the Department of Veterans Affairs as well as the &amp;ldquo;open-source exchange model,&amp;rdquo; which was recently expanded among federal agencies through the Nationwide Health Information Network-Connect initiative.&amp;ldquo;We need advancements in health information technology across the board to improve the quality of care Americans receive,&amp;rdquo; said Rockefeller, chairman of the Senate Finance Subcommittee on Health Care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DoD agents raid Siemens Healthcare offices</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/dod-agents-raid-siemens-healthcare-offices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2009 22:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/04/dod-agents-raid-siemens-healthcare-offices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare IT saves 15% more lives and reduces costs</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/02/healthcare-it-saves-15-more-lives-and-reduces-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2009 20:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2009/02/healthcare-it-saves-15-more-lives-and-reduces-costs/</guid>
      <description>According to a reportin the Jan. 26 issue of Archives of Internal Medicine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>