<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Awards on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/awards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Awards on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Kanteron found &#34;AI in Health Partner Alliance&#34; along with 20 other tech companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft, Kanteron Systems, and 20 other technology companies have set up the &amp;ldquo;AI in Health Partner Alliance&amp;rdquo; to leverage the founding members&amp;rsquo; vision of Democratizing Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems featured in latest Frost &amp; Sullivan’s healthcare report</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-featured-in-latest-frost-sullivans-healthcare-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/kanteron-systems-featured-in-latest-frost-sullivans-healthcare-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The report lists Kanteron Systems as one of the 12 leading companies in Healthcare’s Emerging Business Models.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected among Top 50 UK ScaleUps</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-systems-selected-among-top-50-uk-scaleups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 12:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-systems-selected-among-top-50-uk-scaleups/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In its tenth year, &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Silicon Valley Comes to the UK (‘SVC2UK’) has invited 50 UK high-growth technology companies&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; to join the 2016 ‘&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Scale Up Club&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;’. One of those companies is Kanteron Systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron among &#34;the most promising emerging digital health companies&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/10/kanteron-among-the-most-promising-emerging-digital-health-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/10/kanteron-among-the-most-promising-emerging-digital-health-companies/</guid>
      <description>Tech Tour, a platform for Innovative Investors, hi-tech Entrepreneurs (from early to late stage), Corporates and Government Influencers, committed to the development of emerging technology companies from Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems among the most promising emerging digital health companies in Europe. The selection was be based on Business potential, Team experience, Product / Technology merit, and Competitive position.
Taking place October 25 in Las Naves, Valencia (Spain), the Digital Health Venture Forum, organized by Tech Tour, will bring together the most promising emerging digital health companies (like Kanteron Systems), investors (from organisations like Philips, Teijin Pharma, Kreos Capital, Merck Global Health Innovation Fund, etc), and institutions (like Health 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron wins the California Impact Challenge in Precision Medicine award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/09/kanteron-wins-the-california-impact-challenge-in-precision-medicine-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 14:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/09/kanteron-wins-the-california-impact-challenge-in-precision-medicine-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been recognized as the leader in Precision Medicine, and awarded the 2016 Precision Medicine Impact Challenge Award by The California Governor’s Office of Planning and Research (OPR) and the Governor’s Office of Business and Economic Development (GO-Biz), in collaboration with Singularity University (SU).
The Precision Medicine Impact Challenge was announced by Atul Butte, MD, PhD, director of the UCSF Institute for Computational Health Sciences, and Elizabeth Baca, MD, MPA, from the Governor‘s OPR at the Precision Public Health summit hosted by UCSF in June 2016, convened by the White House and Bill &amp;amp; Melinda Gates Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron selected to represent the EU in Silicon Valley as the &#34;next EU unicorn&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>The European Commission, through Startup Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems amongst the top 18 European scaleups (from Belgium, Czech Republic, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Spain, and the UK) to represent the European Union in Silicon Valley as the &amp;ldquo;next EU unicorn&amp;rdquo;.
 The Startup Europeinitiative brings together EU policy makers (commissioners, prime ministers), the best of the new EU Scaleups and corporations to meet Silicon Valley stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems shortlisted for Top 10 Medical Imaging Solution Providers 2016</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-systems-shortlisted-for-top-10-medical-imaging-solution-providers-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/07/kanteron-systems-shortlisted-for-top-10-medical-imaging-solution-providers-2016/</guid>
      <description>Healthcare Tech Outlook magazine has shortlisted Kanteron Systems for Top 10 Medical Imaging Solution Providers 2016 award.© Healthcare Tech Outlook magazineThis prestigious award recognizes companies who have stood out among the rest in the industry.
Healthcare Tech Outlook magazine reaches out to 41,000 CIOs, Directors, Hospital Information Management and Healthcare Research Teams and senior technology decision makers in the healthcare industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New 0 non-conformities ISO audit</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/new-0-non-conformities-iso-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 19:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/new-0-non-conformities-iso-audit/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to announce another annual ISO 9001 audit review passed with perfect &amp;ldquo;score&amp;rdquo;: zero major and zero minor non-conformities.
Congratulations to the QA team!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron in the top 15% of analyzed software startups according to rating agency EarlyMetrics</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanteron-in-the-top-15-of-analyzed-software-startups-according-to-rating-agency-earlymetrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 09:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/02/kanteron-in-the-top-15-of-analyzed-software-startups-according-to-rating-agency-earlymetrics/</guid>
      <description>After a comprehensive and independent analysis and review by Early Metrics, the first ratings agency for startups, has awarded Kanteron Systems &amp;ldquo;3 stars&amp;rdquo;, it‘s top honors.
Early Metrics audits and analyzes over 100 startups each month, including the matrix rating (Managers – Project – Market) and the FSRC indicator, which evaluates the reliability and consistency of the financial statements.
 Kanteron is part of the top 15% of our software startups – Sarah Noeckel, Venture Capital Analyst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected as part of the Mayor’s International Programme</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/kanteron-systems-selected-as-part-of-the-mayors-international-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 21:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/kanteron-systems-selected-as-part-of-the-mayors-international-programme/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as one of the 35 companies forming the initial cohort of the Mayor’s International Programme.
The programme will support high growth businesses from London’s Technology, Life Sciences and Urban sectors to expand their businesses internationally. It is run by London &amp;amp; Partners (supported by the Mayor), partly funded by the European Development Fund and partly by five private sector delivery partners: BDO, Benoy, KPMG, London Chamber of Commerce and Industry &amp;amp; PA Consulting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Report “Valencia: Healthcare Innovation and Research” Features Kanteron as a Success Case</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/the-report-valencia-healthcare-innovation-and-research-features-kanteron-as-a-success-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 19:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/the-report-valencia-healthcare-innovation-and-research-features-kanteron-as-a-success-case/</guid>
      <description>InnDEA Valencia Foundation, through the VIT Salud Innovation Network, released yesterday the report “Valencia: Healthcare Innovation and Research”, produced by the Valencian Institute of Economic Research (IVIE).
Javier Quesada, author of the report, is an IVIE researcher and Professor of Economic Analysis at Valencia University (UV). The report highlights that the healthcare economic activity in the city has grown “much faster” than the rest of the economic activity and it represents 5,3% of all economic activity in the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research lists Kanteron as major player in the global digital pathology market</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/market-research-lists-kanteron-as-major-player-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/market-research-lists-kanteron-as-major-player-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</guid>
      <description>Market Research firm P&amp;amp;S Market Research featuresKanteron Systems as &amp;ldquo;major player operating in the global digital pathology market&amp;rdquo; in their Digital Pathology Market Trends and Forecast to 2020 report issued November 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron featured by The Telegraph as it joins the ScaleUpClub</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanteron-featured-by-the-telegraph-as-it-joins-the-scaleupclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 13:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanteron-featured-by-the-telegraph-as-it-joins-the-scaleupclub/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems UK has been selected as a member of the #ScaleUpClub 2015. The club is hand-picked by Silicon Valley Comes to the UK (@svc2uk), a not-for-profit organisation that brings together US early-stage investors and disruptive UK start-ups, identifying the 58 firms that could hit £100m in revenue in the next three to five years.
 According to the UK‘s The Telegraph newspaper, the report lists &amp;ldquo;the British companies most likely to become technology giants to rival Facebook and Google&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new report from ASDReports recognizes Kanteron Systems as &#34;Prominent Vendor&#34; in the Global Digital Pathology Market</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/a-new-report-from-asdreports-recognizes-kanteron-systems-as-prominent-vendor-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 10:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/a-new-report-from-asdreports-recognizes-kanteron-systems-as-prominent-vendor-in-the-global-digital-pathology-market/</guid>
      <description>A new reportfrom ASDReports titled &amp;ldquo;Global Digital Pathology Market 2014-2018&amp;rdquo; recognizes Kanteron Systems as &amp;ldquo;Prominent Vendor&amp;rdquo; in the Global Digital Pathology Market.
Source: Tissue Pathology Blog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems finalist in IBM Innovation Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/03/kanteron-systems-finalist-in-ibm-innovation-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/03/kanteron-systems-finalist-in-ibm-innovation-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as finalist, along with British Telecom and nusys, in the IBM Innovation Awards, New Business Model category, for our Split and Pathology Imaging Algorithms solutions. The award, finally won by nusys (congratulations!) was presented at the IBM Leadership Summitthat took place at the Royal Spanish Academy in Madrid (Spain), March 3rd, 2015.
  According to IBM, this nomination celebrates Kanteron Systems as pioneers in the development of solutions for the healthcare environment and visionaries in new technologies and business models in cloud and Watson Cognitive Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report: Global Digital Pathology Market CAGR 11.8% to 2018, Kanteron listed as &#34;major player&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/report-global-digital-pathology-market-cagr-11.8-to-2018-kanteron-listed-as-major-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 19:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/report-global-digital-pathology-market-cagr-11.8-to-2018-kanteron-listed-as-major-player/</guid>
      <description>MarketsandMarketsrecently published “Digital Pathology Market by Slide Scanners (Whole Slide Imaging), Analytics (Image Analysis Software), Delivery Modes (Web Based/Cloud Based) &amp;amp; by Whole Slide Image Storage – Global Forecasts &amp;amp; Trends to 2018″ (available for purchase online), listing Kanteron Systems as a &amp;ldquo;major player&amp;quot;in the worldwide Digital Pathology market.
This report covers the definition, description, and forecast of the digital pathology market in terms of products and applications; the digital pathology market comprises of scanners, analytics, storage, and communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The latest healthcare technology report from Gartner features Kanteron as VNA sample vendor</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/the-latest-healthcare-technology-report-from-gartner-features-kanteron-as-vna-sample-vendor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2014 16:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/the-latest-healthcare-technology-report-from-gartner-features-kanteron-as-vna-sample-vendor/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been featured as VNA (Vendor-Neutral Archive) sample vendor in Gartner‘s latest healthcare technology report: Hype Cycle for Healthcare Providers Technologies and Standards, written by veteran industry analyst Barry Runyon.
 The Hype Cycle for Healthcare Providers Technologies and Standards is a vital reference for healthcare delivery organization CIOs and IT leadership when assessing the value of existing and emerging information technologies and standards. It provides insight necessary to remain competitive in a rapidly evolving healthcare provider marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Top 50 to Top 10 in a week! Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 10 (Healthcare) for Web Traffic Rank Growth</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/from-top-50-to-top-10-in-a-week-kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-10-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2014 16:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/from-top-50-to-top-10-in-a-week-kanteron-systems-ranked-in-top-10-healthcare-for-web-traffic-rank-growth/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems ranked in Top 50 for Web Traffic Rank Growth according to new ranking company SIGNL.
Rank: #9 of 2,436 Health Care Methodology: SIGNL’s algorithm analyzes millions of data points including web/mobile traffic, social buzz, company growth, and more to identify companies with the highest momentum.
Kanteron Systems, following the stellar presentation of TMIS at RSNAChicago, is experiencing incredible momentum with the anticipated new product developments introduced at HIMSSOrlando (Genomics + Pharmacogenomics + Activity and Sleep Trackers + Analytics) as third party vendor independent PACS-VNA-EMR add-on plug-ins.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>