<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Kanteron found &#34;AI in Health Partner Alliance&#34; along with 20 other tech companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 23:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2017/01/microsoft-and-kanteron-found-ai-in-health-partner-alliance-along-with-20-other-tech-companies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microsoft, Kanteron Systems, and 20 other technology companies have set up the &amp;ldquo;AI in Health Partner Alliance&amp;rdquo; to leverage the founding members&amp;rsquo; vision of Democratizing Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to exhibit at BioEurope 2016 Cologne (Germany) November 7-9 - booth 58</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-to-exhibit-at-bioeurope-2016-cologne-germany-november-7-9-booth-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 21:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-to-exhibit-at-bioeurope-2016-cologne-germany-november-7-9-booth-58/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kanteron Systems is amongst &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://gotogrow.london/insight-and-case-studies/bioeurope-meet-the-companies&#34;&gt;the 7 high-growth digital health companies&lt;/a&gt; chosen by &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://gotogrow.london/&#34;&gt;London Mayor’s International Business Programme&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://www.medcityhq.com/&#34;&gt;MedCity&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://www.londonandpartners.com/&#34;&gt;London and Partners&lt;/a&gt;, to exhibit at &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;BioEurope 2016 Cologne&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Germany).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron among &#34;the most promising emerging digital health companies&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/10/kanteron-among-the-most-promising-emerging-digital-health-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 18:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/10/kanteron-among-the-most-promising-emerging-digital-health-companies/</guid>
      <description>Tech Tour, a platform for Innovative Investors, hi-tech Entrepreneurs (from early to late stage), Corporates and Government Influencers, committed to the development of emerging technology companies from Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems among the most promising emerging digital health companies in Europe. The selection was be based on Business potential, Team experience, Product / Technology merit, and Competitive position.
Taking place October 25 in Las Naves, Valencia (Spain), the Digital Health Venture Forum, organized by Tech Tour, will bring together the most promising emerging digital health companies (like Kanteron Systems), investors (from organisations like Philips, Teijin Pharma, Kreos Capital, Merck Global Health Innovation Fund, etc), and institutions (like Health 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron selected to represent the EU in Silicon Valley as the &#34;next EU unicorn&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 14:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/08/kanteron-selected-to-represent-the-eu-in-silicon-valley-as-the-next-eu-unicorn/</guid>
      <description>The European Commission, through Startup Europe, has selected Kanteron Systems amongst the top 18 European scaleups (from Belgium, Czech Republic, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Spain, and the UK) to represent the European Union in Silicon Valley as the &amp;ldquo;next EU unicorn&amp;rdquo;.
 The Startup Europeinitiative brings together EU policy makers (commissioners, prime ministers), the best of the new EU Scaleups and corporations to meet Silicon Valley stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron CEO guest speaker at KPMG UK Health event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-ceo-guest-speaker-at-kpmg-uk-health-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 20:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-ceo-guest-speaker-at-kpmg-uk-health-event/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems‘ CEO was invited by KPMG UKto be a guest speaker at their Health Get Together event yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to join Microsoft in Festival of Genomics Boston</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-to-join-microsoft-in-festival-of-genomics-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 13:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-to-join-microsoft-in-festival-of-genomics-boston/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate, along with Microsoft Genomics group, in the Festival of Genomics conference to be held at Boston Convention Center (USA) June 27-29.
CEO Jorge Cortell, and President &amp;amp; CCO John Memarian, will be demonstrating how Kanteron‘s Translational Medical Information Server integrates medical images with clinical genomics, pharmacogenomics and other relevant data for the delivery of precision medicine at the point of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay participates in Health 2.0 Valencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 17:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/04/juan-tatay-participates-in-health-2.0-valencia/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, participated yesterday in the Health 2.0 event organized by InnDEA, and featuring Tellmegen, eKuore and Kanteron, in Las Naves (Valencia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come visit us at HIMSS 2016 Las Vegas (HDS booth 846)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/come-visit-us-at-himss-2016-las-vegas-hds-booth-846/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 11:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/come-visit-us-at-himss-2016-las-vegas-hds-booth-846/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will exhibit alongside its partner Hitachi at the HIMSSconference and exhibition Tues. March 1, Thurs. March 3, 2016, Sands Convention Center, Las Vegas (USA).
Schedule a meeting or demo here, and come visit us at Hitachi Data Systems Booth 846.
Note: Exhibition Hall‘s opening hours are 9:30 am – 6:00 pm (closing time Thursday, March 3: 4:00pm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected as part of the Mayor’s International Programme</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/kanteron-systems-selected-as-part-of-the-mayors-international-programme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 21:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/kanteron-systems-selected-as-part-of-the-mayors-international-programme/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as one of the 35 companies forming the initial cohort of the Mayor’s International Programme.
The programme will support high growth businesses from London’s Technology, Life Sciences and Urban sectors to expand their businesses internationally. It is run by London &amp;amp; Partners (supported by the Mayor), partly funded by the European Development Fund and partly by five private sector delivery partners: BDO, Benoy, KPMG, London Chamber of Commerce and Industry &amp;amp; PA Consulting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5th EU Health Innovation event at Microsoft’s Brussels EBC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 20:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/5th-eu-health-innovation-event-at-microsofts-brussels-ebc/</guid>
      <description>This Tuesday and Wednesday Kanteron Systems was invited to participate in Microsoft’s 5th Health Innovation event, in the Exhibition Area, along with 5 other selected partners.
Titled “EmpoweringHealth: the journey towards more personalized, productive, collaborative and predictive health services &amp;amp; systems” it took place at the Microsoft Executive Briefing Center in Brussels.Kanteron Systems‘ CEO, Jorge Cortell, participated in the round table “Medical Imaging Storage in the Cloud”, moderated by Kelly Limonte (Microsoft UK Healthcare Team), and in the Expert Panel “The future of preventive and predictive health powered by data in the intelligent cloud”, along with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The London Stock Exchange invites Kanteron to participate in the market opening ceremony</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/the-london-stock-exchange-invites-kanteron-to-participate-in-the-market-opening-ceremony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/the-london-stock-exchange-invites-kanteron-to-participate-in-the-market-opening-ceremony/</guid>
      <description>On Friday, November 6th, Kanteron Systems‘ CEO Jorge Cortell was invited by Marcus Stuttard, head of AIM (the London Stock Exchange‘s growth market), to participate in the London Stock Exchange market opening ceremony, which takes place daily at 8:00 am.

The ceremony offers companies joining London Stock Exchange‘s markets the opportunity to mark their success on the day of their admission. The event was followed by drinks and breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron featured by The Telegraph as it joins the ScaleUpClub</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanteron-featured-by-the-telegraph-as-it-joins-the-scaleupclub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 13:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanteron-featured-by-the-telegraph-as-it-joins-the-scaleupclub/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems UK has been selected as a member of the #ScaleUpClub 2015. The club is hand-picked by Silicon Valley Comes to the UK (@svc2uk), a not-for-profit organisation that brings together US early-stage investors and disruptive UK start-ups, identifying the 58 firms that could hit £100m in revenue in the next three to five years.
 According to the UK‘s The Telegraph newspaper, the report lists &amp;ldquo;the British companies most likely to become technology giants to rival Facebook and Google&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Of London‘s Export Programme selects Kanteron to participate in BioJapan 2015</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/mayor-of-londons-export-programme-selects-kanteron-to-participate-in-biojapan-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 01:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/mayor-of-londons-export-programme-selects-kanteron-to-participate-in-biojapan-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Mayor of London Boris Johnson MP travelled to Yokohama (Japan) with representatives from 8 of the most promising BioTech companies in London to promote UK-Japan collaboration in cell therapy and regenerative medicine at the BioJapan 2015. BioJapan is Asia’s leading biotechnology event, attracting thousands of representatives from some 700 of the world’s leading bioscience companies every year. This year it took place October 14th – 16th at Pacifico Yokohama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM invites Kanteron Systems to participate in IBMBCES</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/ibm-invites-kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-ibmbces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/ibm-invites-kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-ibmbces/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited by IBM Spain to participate in the IBM Business Connect, to be held in Madrid (Spain) November 25, 2015.
Click herefor more info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay and Alvaro Gonzalez presentation at IBM Cloud event in Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/06/juan-tatay-and-alvaro-gonzalez-presentation-at-ibm-cloud-event-in-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 22:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/06/juan-tatay-and-alvaro-gonzalez-presentation-at-ibm-cloud-event-in-madrid/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday June 2 Kanteron System‘ Alvaro González – CIO and Juan Tatay – COO presented Kanteron Systems‘ experience with IBM at the IBM Cloud event &amp;ldquo;Dream it! Build it!&amp;rdquo; in Madrid. #IBMCloudDreamIt
Kanteron‘s success case was presented along two other companies: Evolufarma and SKIOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems at HIMSS 2015 Chicago</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-systems-at-himss-2015-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 20:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-systems-at-himss-2015-chicago/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Chicago April 12-16, stop by HIMSS 2015 Booth # 2480, Hitachi Data Systems Corporation (HDS), or Booth #1425, IBM, to see Kanteron Systems‘ clinical genomics in action.
As for Jorge, Stephanie, Craig or Kurt. See you in Chicago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems finalist in IBM Innovation Award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/03/kanteron-systems-finalist-in-ibm-innovation-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/03/kanteron-systems-finalist-in-ibm-innovation-award/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as finalist, along with British Telecom and nusys, in the IBM Innovation Awards, New Business Model category, for our Split and Pathology Imaging Algorithms solutions. The award, finally won by nusys (congratulations!) was presented at the IBM Leadership Summitthat took place at the Royal Spanish Academy in Madrid (Spain), March 3rd, 2015.
  According to IBM, this nomination celebrates Kanteron Systems as pioneers in the development of solutions for the healthcare environment and visionaries in new technologies and business models in cloud and Watson Cognitive Computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems in Arab Health, Dubai</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems was back in Arab Healththis year (January 26-28), due to the increased interest and activity regarding Healthcare Technology in the Middle Eastern region.
Through our new partners in the region, we have over twenty projects going on in United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Iran, Iraq, Nigeria, Tanzania, and Ethiopia.Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems CEO, in the lobby of Arab Health Dubai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in the VII Biomedical Engineering Workshop</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-vii-biomedical-engineering-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 21:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/01/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-vii-biomedical-engineering-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Organizedby the Inter-University (Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia, Spain) MSc. in Biomedical Engineering, the VII Biomedical Engineering Workshop will take place February 3-6, 2015.
Juan Tatay, COO, and Jorge Cortell, Founder and CEO of Kanteron Systems, will talk about &amp;ldquo;Computational paradigm shift in medical imaging&amp;rdquo;. Juan Tatay will be present during the event in Valencia, while Jorge Cortell will participate via videoconference from New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in the national HealthIT Innovation tour</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-national-healthit-innovation-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 00:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-the-national-healthit-innovation-tour/</guid>
      <description>The TIC Salud National HealthIT Innovation Touris an initiative that organizes events in different Spanish regions so that companies in the industry can present their latest innovations in the field of HealthIT to healthcare professionals and executives. The Committee will be formed by deputy directors of Information Technology, CEO‘s, CIO‘s and medical directors. Following each of the presentations, committee members will ask questions directed to the speakers about their innovations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in Iberian Tech Tour</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-iberian-tech-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 09:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/09/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-iberian-tech-tour/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected, pre-screened and chosen from over 250 companies by the selection committee, to present in Iberian Tech Tour, October 1-3, 2014, which will cover 25 companies from Portugal and Spain.
Why &amp;ldquo;Iberian&amp;rdquo;? The City of Lisbon and the Region of Valencia in late June were named European Entrepreneurial Region (EER) for 2015. The EER project identifies and rewards EU regions that show a remarkable and innovative entrepreneurial strategy regardless of their size or economic situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems collaborates in world‘s first Scientific Photography Postgraduate course</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-collaborates-in-worlds-first-scientific-photography-postgraduate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2014 10:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/08/kanteron-systems-collaborates-in-worlds-first-scientific-photography-postgraduate-course/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will collaborate with the world‘s first _ Scientific Photography Postgraduate course_ at the University of Alcala (Spain) October 6 to November 21, 2014.
The lectures will be taught in the classroom‘s School of Sciences. The practical classes are taught in the Cabinet of Scientific Photography lab, Cell Biology lab and National Museum of Natural Sciences.
The course involves 20 teachers selected among the best Spanish and foreign specialists (including Kanteron Systems‘ CIO, Alvaro Gonzalez) who will teach 30 different specialties handling equipment worth over 1,000 million euros, thanks to the collaboration of the Ministry of Defense, National Museum of Natural Sciences, Astronomical Observatory La Hita, various hospitals, universities and other entities like Kanteron Systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to exhibit at Federal Summit 2014 in Washington DC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/kanteron-systems-to-exhibit-at-federal-summit-2014-in-washington-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/kanteron-systems-to-exhibit-at-federal-summit-2014-in-washington-dc/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday June 11 (7:30-15:30h) Kanteron Systems will be demonstrating its state-of-the-art biomedical informatics solution at the 2nd Annual Federal Summit, where IT and management executives from government and industry tap the full potential of today’s computing environment to drive innovation, reduce operating costs, and deliver better mission outcomes and customer satisfaction.
Featuring Keynote Speakers:
Gen. Keith B. Alexander, USA (Ret.)
Former Commander, U.S. Cyber Command
Former Director, National Security Agency/Chief, Central Security Service</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Tatay presents at the 2014 International Conference on Biomedical and Health Informatics</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/juan-tatay-presents-at-the-2014-international-conference-on-biomedical-and-health-informatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2014 20:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/juan-tatay-presents-at-the-2014-international-conference-on-biomedical-and-health-informatics/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay (Kanteron Systems‘ COO) presented Kanteron Systems‘ solutions and vision at the 2014 BHI (International Conference on Biomedical and Health Informatics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in Transbio Sudoe Barcelona Emergence Forum</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-participates-in-transbio-sudoe-barcelona-emergence-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2014 18:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/04/kanteron-systems-participates-in-transbio-sudoe-barcelona-emergence-forum/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in the VIII TEIBIO meeting &#34;From beginning to growth&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-participates-in-the-viii-teibio-meeting-from-beginning-to-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 22:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-participates-in-the-viii-teibio-meeting-from-beginning-to-growth/</guid>
      <description>Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems‘ COO, and Mariano Collantes, co-founder of Uvat bio, were the panelist in today‘s VIII TEI Bio meeting &amp;ldquo;From beginning to growth&amp;rdquo;. Organized by InnDEA Valencia, through VIT Salud and Genera Biotech, the TEI Bio events try to foster knowledge transfer, entrepreneurship and investment in Biomedicine and Biotechnology.
Here is the full description by BIOVAL, and here is another chronicle published by VIT Salud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems receives El Mundo newspaper &#34;Innovation of the Year Award&#34;</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-receives-el-mundo-newspaper-innovation-of-the-year-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2014 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/02/kanteron-systems-receives-el-mundo-newspaper-innovation-of-the-year-award/</guid>
      <description>The Jury of the V Innovation Awards (Spanish newspaper El Mundo) has awarded Kanteron Systems the Award for Best Innovation of the Year 2013. Attending the ceremonywere: the President of the European Commission and Commissioner for Entrepreneurship Antonio Tajani, the Israeli Ambassador in Spain (who presented the award to Juan Tatay, Kanteron Systems CEO in Spain), Bankia‘s President and the President of the Valencian Government, among others. The event took place at the Red Sea auditorium in the Oceanographic in Valencia (Spain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to deliver a lecture at the VI Biomedical Engineering Meeting</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2014 20:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/01/kanteron-systems-to-deliver-a-lecture-at-the-vi-biomedical-engineering-meeting/</guid>
      <description>On Thursday, February 6 2014 at 16h, Kanteron Systems‘ Juan Tatay (Director) and Carlos Villanueva (R&amp;amp;D Engineer) will deliver the lecture “Precise diagnostics for personalized medicine: medical imaging and big data” at the Cajal Room, 1st floor, School of Medicine, University of Valencia (Spain) within the VI Biomedical Engineering Meetingof the Valencia University and Polytechnic University of Valencia‘s Official Interuniversity Master Degree in Biomedical Engineering. Other lectures will be delivered by Philips Research, Indra Sistemas and General Electric Healthcare amongst others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan on Kanteron Systems’ latest innovation: “WOW!”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</guid>
      <description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivanprofiles Kanteron Systems in the “WOW!” section of their latest Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics report.
Global growth consulting firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, which provides market research and analysis for the Healthcare Industry (amongst others), published today the report “RSNA 2013 Review: Scouting the Showfloor for the Latest-Greatest in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics”. In the report’s “Select WOW! Findings from the Showfloor” section, Nadim Michel Daher, Principal Analyst – Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics, and Siddharth Saha, Global Program Leader Advanced MedTech, identify six companies with disruptive innovations in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems introduces the first Translational PACS-VNA in the world at RSNA 2013</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 00:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</guid>
      <description>PRESS RELEASE First Translational Medical Imaging System in the World New York, NY, USA, November 27, 2013
 Kanteron Systems will launch the world‘s first Translational Medical Imaging System (“TMIS”) at the Radiology Society of North America (“RSNA”) annual meeting in Chicago, December 1-5, 2013. TMIS is a fully integrated solution for radiology, genetic and pathology workflows that could change the way medicine is practiced.
 Translational research is an emerging field that aims to provide a better understanding of the molecular basis of disease, which in turn will inform clinical practice and ultimately improve human health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participats in Siapec Rome</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, along with our new partner NoemaLife, participated in the 6th triennal Siapec(Italian Society for Anatomic Pathology and Cytopathology Diagnostic – Italian Division of the International Academy of Pathology) congressheld at the Hotel Ergife Palace in Rome October 26-30, 2013, where we will presented Noemalife Athenapowered by Kanteron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected for the Investors Forum – MIT EmTech Spain 2013 Conference</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-selected-for-the-investors-forum-mit-emtech-spain-2013-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 16:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-selected-for-the-investors-forum-mit-emtech-spain-2013-conference/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been selected as one of the participants for this year‘s edition of the Investors Forum, to be held Nov. 6 in Valencia (Spain) as part of the MIT Enterprise Forum EmTech Spain 2013 Conference.
#invertorsforum @mitefspain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in IBM START014 in Madrid (Spain)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/09/kanteron-systems-participates-in-ibm-start014-in-madrid-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 16:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/09/kanteron-systems-participates-in-ibm-start014-in-madrid-spain/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems had a booth in the IBM #START014 congress, November 20, 2013, Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems: 8 years without losing a single customer</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2013 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/08/kanteron-systems-8-years-without-losing-a-single-customer/</guid>
      <description>Today Kanteron Systems turns 8 years old.
We want to thank those that have made this possible, that believed in us, that helped us, that are part of our organization, and specially that have trusted us with their business.
We have as many reasons to be proud about as we have things to improve. But if there is one very telling fact looking back in all those years, it‘s this: we have not lost a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems chosen as top innovative company in Valencia (Spain)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-chosen-as-top-innovative-company-in-valencia-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2013 20:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/07/kanteron-systems-chosen-as-top-innovative-company-in-valencia-spain/</guid>
      <description>The Council of Commerce Chambersof Valencian Community region (Spain), along with the Research Institutes Association has chosen Kanteron Systems to be included in their &amp;ldquo;Top Innovative Valencian Companies&amp;rdquo; guide, presented last Thursday. Kanteron Systems is the only biomedical informatics company in the guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems USA passes FDA inspection without issues</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-systems-usa-passes-fda-inspection-without-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2013 21:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-systems-usa-passes-fda-inspection-without-issues/</guid>
      <description>On April 25th Kanteron Systems had its first routine FDA (U.S. Food and Drug Administration) Medical Device Establishment Inspection. Agent (Investigator) Kimberley A. Ricketts gave us a routine “Notice of Inspection pursuant to Section 704(a)(1) of the Federal Food, Drug, and Cosmetics Act [21 U.S.C. 374(a)] and Part F or G, Title III of the Public Health Service Act [42 U.S.C. 262-264]“. This Level 1 inspection was conducted as part of the NYK-DO Work Plan under FACTS ID#1456352 in accordance with Compliance Program 7382.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron featured in IBM ad</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-featured-in-ibm-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2013 20:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/06/kanteron-featured-in-ibm-ad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins 2013 IBM Beacon Award for Healthcare and Life Sciences</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-wins-2013-ibm-beacon-award-for-healthcare-and-life-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2013 01:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/03/kanteron-systems-wins-2013-ibm-beacon-award-for-healthcare-and-life-sciences/</guid>
      <description>IBM Beacon Awards recognize IBM Business Partners for their technical excellence, industry expertise, and innovative solutions.
Kanteron Systems was named a winner of a 2013 IBM Beacon Award for Healthcare and Life Sciences. This honor is awarded each year in recognition of a select number of IBM Business Partners who have delivered not only innovative solutions but have set the standards for business excellence, ingenuity, and creation of an exceptional client experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to participate in IBM PartnerWorld Leadership Conference in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/kanteron-to-participate-in-ibm-partnerworld-leadership-conference-in-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 20:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/kanteron-to-participate-in-ibm-partnerworld-leadership-conference-in-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate in IBM PartnerWorld Leadership Conferenceto be held February 25 – February 28, 2013 at Caesars Palace in Las Vegas, attended by: 1,500 C-Level Business Partners, 500 IBM Senior level Executives, 60 Press and Analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems awarded &#34;Best Clinical Poster Award&#34; at Digital Pathology Association Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 01:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is honored to have been awarded &amp;ldquo;Best Clinical Poster Award&amp;rdquo; at Digital Pathology Association Congress 2012 Pathology Visions, held in Baltimore (USA), October 28th-October 31st.
The poster was titled: &amp;ldquo;Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web)&amp;rdquo; and was presented and authored by Jorge Cortell CEO &amp;amp; President, Kanteron Systems USA, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in MIT‘s Emtech 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</guid>
      <description>Emtechis the main emerging technologies conference in the world, organized by MIT‘s (Massachusetts Institute of Technology) Technology Review, in which outstanding scientist and researchers present the most innovative emerging technologies, still unknown to the general public and with great potential to improve people‘s lives and transform society and business in the following years.
After Emtech Spain 2011‘s success, MIT chooses Spain again to celebrate their second annual conference in Europe. Emtech Spain 2012 will takwe place November 22nd and 23rd in the city of Malaga and it will be an exceptional opportunity for scientists, technologist, business, innovators and entrepreneurs to attend a unique event which will change their vision of the near future and how to lead the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems named &#34;National Champion&#34; and through to final round of European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-named-national-champion-and-through-to-final-round-of-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-named-national-champion-and-through-to-final-round-of-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>This year, for the first time, entrants in the European Business Awards submitted a video case study for online voting. In addition, an esteemed panel of judges chose organisations that exhibited innovation, business excellence and sustainability.
Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems:
 We’re proud to be selected to represent Spain as a National Champion in our category, along with companies like Bankinter, Iberdrola, or everis. The European Business Awards is widely recognised as the showcase for Europe’s most dynamic companies and we are now looking forward to the next round of the judging process where we can explain in more depth how we are achieving business success in these tough economic conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems receives International Business of the Year Award in Seoul</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/10/kanteron-systems-receives-international-business-of-the-year-award-in-seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2012 06:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/10/kanteron-systems-receives-international-business-of-the-year-award-in-seoul/</guid>
      <description>High resolution photograph for media reproduction.
October 15th, 2012; Seoul (South Korea)
Kanteron Systems receives the International Business of the Year bronze Award, Healthcare Products &amp;amp; Services.
At a ceremony held at the Ritz Carlton Hotel, where over 400 international executives and dignataries from 20 different countries gathered to celebrate the best companies in the world, Jorge Cortell (president &amp;amp; founder of Kanteron Systems) was presented the award by Michael Gallagher, president of the Stevie Awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</guid>
      <description> Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Start013#Start013, November 6th 2012, at Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain). See you there!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins IAIR Corporate Award 3rd annual edition: Best Company for leadership – Europe</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-wins-iair-corporate-award-3rd-annual-edition-best-company-for-leadership-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2012 18:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-wins-iair-corporate-award-3rd-annual-edition-best-company-for-leadership-europe/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to announce that Kanteron Systems is a winner for the IAIR CORPORATE AWARDS3rd annual edition in the Best Company for leadership – Europe TOP 50 category.
Some of the past winners: Morgan Stanley, Bank of China, Rockefeller, BNP Paribas, IBM, Rothschild, Deutsche Bank, Aviva, Vodafone, Novartis, BASF, Daimler, Royal Dutch Shell, Christian Dior, Cartier, Fedex, ABB, 3i Group, CMS.
According to Alexa – Amazon and Google page rankings, IAIR – International Alternative Investment Reviewis ranked # 1 amongst financial and legal awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to present a poster at DPA 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-present-a-poster-at-dpa-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 21:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-present-a-poster-at-dpa-2012/</guid>
      <description>
Kanteron Systems will present the poster “Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web&amp;hellip;)” at the Digital Pathology Association’s (DPA) annual conference Pathology Visions, being held October 28-31, 2012 at the Hilton Hotel in Baltimore, MD (USA).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems wins International Business Awards &#34;Company of the Year&#34; Bronze award</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/08/kanteron-systems-wins-international-business-awards-company-of-the-year-bronze-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 18:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/08/kanteron-systems-wins-international-business-awards-company-of-the-year-bronze-award/</guid>
      <description>The International Business Awardsare the world’s premier business awards program. More than 3,200 nominations from over 50 countries from organizations of all sizes and in virtually every industry were submitted this year for consideration. Award winners were selected by more than 300 executives worldwide who participated in the judging process this year. Kanteron Systems won Bronze Award in the Company of the Year category for Health Products &amp;amp; Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello to deliver two conferences at Colombia Radiology Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-to-deliver-two-conferences-at-colombia-radiology-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 08:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-to-deliver-two-conferences-at-colombia-radiology-congress/</guid>
      <description>During the Colombia Radiology Congress(August 4th &amp;amp; 5th, Cartagena de Indias, Colombia, Congress Center), Kanteron System‘s Marco Schiavottiello will deliver three conferences:
II Latin-American Congreso of Diagnostic Imaging Technologist, Academic Program, Barahona 1 room:
 Saturday 4th, 14:30-15:30: &amp;ldquo;DICOM for technologist&amp;rdquo; Saturday 4th, 16:00-16:30: &amp;ldquo;The rol of the technologist in the integration of new IT solutions in the radiology department&amp;rdquo; Saturday 4th, 17:00-17:30: &amp;ldquo;Image Post process: new technologies and the extended rol of the technologist&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Alvaro Gonzalez and Jorge Cortell talk about healthcare IT security at HOPE9</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘ Alvaro González(CTO) and Jorge Cortell(CEO) spoke today about &amp;ldquo;Digital Security in Health Care Institutions&amp;rdquo; during Hackers On Planet Earth number 9, New York, one of the most creative and diverse hacker events in the world (since 1994).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems nominated for Company of the Year, International Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-company-of-the-year-international-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 23:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanteron-systems-nominated-for-company-of-the-year-international-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to be nominated for the 2012 Company of the Year Award at the International Business Awards. Go team!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivers Master Class at London event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivered a Master Class about the NHS Great Ormond Street‘s successful implementation by Kanteron Systems of a new Cardiac PACS, at London event &amp;ldquo;A patient centered approach&amp;rdquo; (Central Hall Westminster, Storey‘s Gate) July 4th, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems invited to attend IBM‘s &#34;Redefining Value and Success in Healthcare&#34; business event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-invited-to-attend-ibms-redefining-value-and-success-in-healthcare-business-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 17:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanteron-systems-invited-to-attend-ibms-redefining-value-and-success-in-healthcare-business-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited to attend, as Independent Software Vendor (ISV) IBM‘s &amp;ldquo;Redefining Value and Success in Healthcare&amp;rdquo; business event, led by Dan Pelino, at the IBM Innovation Center and Healthcare Transformation Lab, Chicago (USA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to attend 2012 M&#43;Visión Consortium Biomedical Innovation Conference</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-attend-2012-m-visi%C3%B3n-consortium-biomedical-innovation-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-attend-2012-m-visi%C3%B3n-consortium-biomedical-innovation-conference/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will attend and exhibit at MIT‘s 2012 M+Visión Consortium Biomedical InnovationConference in Madrid (Spain), June 5th and 6th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to sponsor SEACV‘s diagnostic photo contest</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-systems-to-sponsor-seacvs-diagnostic-photo-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 18:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-systems-to-sponsor-seacvs-diagnostic-photo-contest/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to sponsor this year‘s diagnostic photo contestfrom the Spanish Society of Angiology and Vascular Surgery (SEACV).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to sponsor TEDxValencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-to-sponsor-tedxvalencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 16:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-to-sponsor-tedxvalencia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems presentation at NYC Health 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems, presented (soon available via livestream) yesterday some of the company‘s solutions geared towards reducing hospital readmission to a group of 70 professionals at the VNS of NY HQ (10 E 70th St., New York) during a Health 2.0 NYC – The New York Healthcare Innovation Groupmeeting.
Here are some of the twitter-comments from that session:
globalfjord ‏ @globalfjord
Health 2.0 companies to watch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico‘s President, Felipe Calderon, inaugurates a new hospital with Kanteron Systems technology</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/mexicos-president-felipe-calderon-inaugurates-a-new-hospital-with-kanteron-systems-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 19:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/mexicos-president-felipe-calderon-inaugurates-a-new-hospital-with-kanteron-systems-technology/</guid>
      <description>Mexico‘s President Felipe Calderón inaugurates a new ISSSTE hospital in Michoacan (Mexico) with Kanteron Systems technology (integrated by our distributors and partners in Mexico: Ceurac).
Video of the news in Televisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected again for inclusion in the 2012 European Business Awards</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/02/kanteron-systems-selected-again-for-inclusion-in-the-2012-european-business-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2012 17:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/02/kanteron-systems-selected-again-for-inclusion-in-the-2012-european-business-awards/</guid>
      <description>The European Business Awards Research team spend six months analysing over 15000 companies across Europe to seek out the very best businesses that demonstrate the guiding principles of the Awards: Commercial success, Innovation, Business ethics.
Wish us luck!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems delivers a Vascular Diagnostic Update Course</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-delivers-a-vascular-diagnostic-update-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2011 10:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2011/09/kanteron-systems-delivers-a-vascular-diagnostic-update-course/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems delivers a lecture in the Vascular Diagnostic Update Course held at the Polytechnic and University Hospital La Fe (Valencia – Spain), September 29 and 30, 2011, during the XIV National CDVNI-SEACV Congress.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>