<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tradeshows on Kanteron Systems Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/tradeshows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tradeshows on Kanteron Systems Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 21:52:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.kanteron.com/categories/tradeshows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to exhibit at BioEurope 2016 Cologne (Germany) November 7-9 - booth 58</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-to-exhibit-at-bioeurope-2016-cologne-germany-november-7-9-booth-58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 21:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/11/kanteron-to-exhibit-at-bioeurope-2016-cologne-germany-november-7-9-booth-58/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kanteron Systems is amongst &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://gotogrow.london/insight-and-case-studies/bioeurope-meet-the-companies&#34;&gt;the 7 high-growth digital health companies&lt;/a&gt; chosen by &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://gotogrow.london/&#34;&gt;London Mayor’s International Business Programme&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://www.medcityhq.com/&#34;&gt;MedCity&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;httpss://www.londonandpartners.com/&#34;&gt;London and Partners&lt;/a&gt;, to exhibit at &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;BioEurope 2016 Cologne&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Germany).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to join Microsoft in Festival of Genomics Boston</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-to-join-microsoft-in-festival-of-genomics-boston/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 13:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2016/06/kanteron-to-join-microsoft-in-festival-of-genomics-boston/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate, along with Microsoft Genomics group, in the Festival of Genomics conference to be held at Boston Convention Center (USA) June 27-29.
CEO Jorge Cortell, and President &amp;amp; CCO John Memarian, will be demonstrating how Kanteron‘s Translational Medical Information Server integrates medical images with clinical genomics, pharmacogenomics and other relevant data for the delivery of precision medicine at the point of care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come visit us at HIMSS 2016 Las Vegas (HDS booth 846)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/come-visit-us-at-himss-2016-las-vegas-hds-booth-846/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 11:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/12/come-visit-us-at-himss-2016-las-vegas-hds-booth-846/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will exhibit alongside its partner Hitachi at the HIMSSconference and exhibition Tues. March 1, Thurs. March 3, 2016, Sands Convention Center, Las Vegas (USA).
Schedule a meeting or demo here, and come visit us at Hitachi Data Systems Booth 846.
Note: Exhibition Hall‘s opening hours are 9:30 am – 6:00 pm (closing time Thursday, March 3: 4:00pm).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM features Kanteron Systems in an ad</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-an-ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 19:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/ibm-features-kanteron-systems-in-an-ad/</guid>
      <description>IBM has produced an advertising featuring Kanteron Systems, titled: &amp;ldquo;More precise diagnostics with Kanteron and IBM Cloud&amp;rdquo;.
Here is the IBM press release.
The ad, featuring Kanteron COO Juan Tatay and Kanteron CIO Alvaro Gonzalez, was filmed in Kanteron‘s offices in Valencia and Madrid (Spain), for the IBM Business Connectevent.
Watch the video here:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s solutions to be exhibited in Medica 2015 trade show</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanterons-solutions-to-be-exhibited-in-medica-2015-trade-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 16:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/11/kanterons-solutions-to-be-exhibited-in-medica-2015-trade-show/</guid>
      <description>Our partners Mediphealthwill exhibit and demonstrate Kanteron‘s solutions at Hall 15, booth B01, of Medica2015 trade show which will take place16-19 November in Düsseldorf (Germany).
Medica is the world’s largest event for the medical sector, and has been held for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Of London‘s Export Programme selects Kanteron to participate in BioJapan 2015</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/mayor-of-londons-export-programme-selects-kanteron-to-participate-in-biojapan-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2015 01:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/mayor-of-londons-export-programme-selects-kanteron-to-participate-in-biojapan-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Mayor of London Boris Johnson MP travelled to Yokohama (Japan) with representatives from 8 of the most promising BioTech companies in London to promote UK-Japan collaboration in cell therapy and regenerative medicine at the BioJapan 2015. BioJapan is Asia’s leading biotechnology event, attracting thousands of representatives from some 700 of the world’s leading bioscience companies every year. This year it took place October 14th – 16th at Pacifico Yokohama.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM invites Kanteron Systems to participate in IBMBCES</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/ibm-invites-kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-ibmbces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2015 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/10/ibm-invites-kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-ibmbces/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems has been invited by IBM Spain to participate in the IBM Business Connect, to be held in Madrid (Spain) November 25, 2015.
Click herefor more info.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems at HIMSS 2015 Chicago</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-systems-at-himss-2015-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 20:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/04/kanteron-systems-at-himss-2015-chicago/</guid>
      <description>If you are in Chicago April 12-16, stop by HIMSS 2015 Booth # 2480, Hitachi Data Systems Corporation (HDS), or Booth #1425, IBM, to see Kanteron Systems‘ clinical genomics in action.
As for Jorge, Stephanie, Craig or Kurt. See you in Chicago!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems in Arab Health, Dubai</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 23:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2015/02/kanteron-systems-in-arab-health-dubai/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems was back in Arab Healththis year (January 26-28), due to the increased interest and activity regarding Healthcare Technology in the Middle Eastern region.
Through our new partners in the region, we have over twenty projects going on in United Arab Emirates, Qatar, Iran, Iraq, Nigeria, Tanzania, and Ethiopia.Jorge Cortell, Kanteron Systems CEO, in the lobby of Arab Health Dubai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to exhibit at Federal Summit 2014 in Washington DC</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/kanteron-systems-to-exhibit-at-federal-summit-2014-in-washington-dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2014/06/kanteron-systems-to-exhibit-at-federal-summit-2014-in-washington-dc/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday June 11 (7:30-15:30h) Kanteron Systems will be demonstrating its state-of-the-art biomedical informatics solution at the 2nd Annual Federal Summit, where IT and management executives from government and industry tap the full potential of today’s computing environment to drive innovation, reduce operating costs, and deliver better mission outcomes and customer satisfaction.
Featuring Keynote Speakers:
Gen. Keith B. Alexander, USA (Ret.)
Former Commander, U.S. Cyber Command
Former Director, National Security Agency/Chief, Central Security Service</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan on Kanteron Systems’ latest innovation: “WOW!”</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2013 22:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/12/frost-amp-sullivan-on-kanteron-systems-latest-innovation-wow/</guid>
      <description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivanprofiles Kanteron Systems in the “WOW!” section of their latest Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics report.
Global growth consulting firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, which provides market research and analysis for the Healthcare Industry (amongst others), published today the report “RSNA 2013 Review: Scouting the Showfloor for the Latest-Greatest in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics”. In the report’s “Select WOW! Findings from the Showfloor” section, Nadim Michel Daher, Principal Analyst – Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics, and Siddharth Saha, Global Program Leader Advanced MedTech, identify six companies with disruptive innovations in Medical Imaging and Imaging Informatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems introduces the first Translational PACS-VNA in the world at RSNA 2013</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2013 00:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/11/kanteron-systems-introduces-the-first-translational-pacs-vna-in-the-world-at-rsna-2013/</guid>
      <description>PRESS RELEASE First Translational Medical Imaging System in the World New York, NY, USA, November 27, 2013
 Kanteron Systems will launch the world‘s first Translational Medical Imaging System (“TMIS”) at the Radiology Society of North America (“RSNA”) annual meeting in Chicago, December 1-5, 2013. TMIS is a fully integrated solution for radiology, genetic and pathology workflows that could change the way medicine is practiced.
 Translational research is an emerging field that aims to provide a better understanding of the molecular basis of disease, which in turn will inform clinical practice and ultimately improve human health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate in RSNA2013 along with IBM and AVNET (Booth B7510)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-rsna2013-along-with-ibm-and-avnet-booth-b7510/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 16:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-to-participate-in-rsna2013-along-with-ibm-and-avnet-booth-b7510/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate in this year‘s RSNAalong with Avnet &amp;amp; IBM at Booth B7510, North Building – Hall B, December 1-5, 2013 in Chicago (USA). More details to be announced soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participats in Siapec Rome</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 18:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/10/kanteron-systems-participats-in-siapec-rome/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems, along with our new partner NoemaLife, participated in the 6th triennal Siapec(Italian Society for Anatomic Pathology and Cytopathology Diagnostic – Italian Division of the International Academy of Pathology) congressheld at the Hotel Ergife Palace in Rome October 26-30, 2013, where we will presented Noemalife Athenapowered by Kanteron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems participates in IBM START014 in Madrid (Spain)</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/09/kanteron-systems-participates-in-ibm-start014-in-madrid-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 16:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/09/kanteron-systems-participates-in-ibm-start014-in-madrid-spain/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems had a booth in the IBM #START014 congress, November 20, 2013, Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to participate in IBM PartnerWorld Leadership Conference in Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/kanteron-to-participate-in-ibm-partnerworld-leadership-conference-in-las-vegas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 20:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2013/01/kanteron-to-participate-in-ibm-partnerworld-leadership-conference-in-las-vegas/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will participate in IBM PartnerWorld Leadership Conferenceto be held February 25 – February 28, 2013 at Caesars Palace in Las Vegas, attended by: 1,500 C-Level Business Partners, 500 IBM Senior level Executives, 60 Press and Analysts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems awarded &#34;Best Clinical Poster Award&#34; at Digital Pathology Association Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2012 01:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-awarded-best-clinical-poster-award-at-digital-pathology-association-congress/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is honored to have been awarded &amp;ldquo;Best Clinical Poster Award&amp;rdquo; at Digital Pathology Association Congress 2012 Pathology Visions, held in Baltimore (USA), October 28th-October 31st.
The poster was titled: &amp;ldquo;Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web)&amp;rdquo; and was presented and authored by Jorge Cortell CEO &amp;amp; President, Kanteron Systems USA, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems selected to participate in MIT‘s Emtech 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 22:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/11/kanteron-systems-selected-to-participate-in-mits-emtech-2012/</guid>
      <description>Emtechis the main emerging technologies conference in the world, organized by MIT‘s (Massachusetts Institute of Technology) Technology Review, in which outstanding scientist and researchers present the most innovative emerging technologies, still unknown to the general public and with great potential to improve people‘s lives and transform society and business in the following years.
After Emtech Spain 2011‘s success, MIT chooses Spain again to celebrate their second annual conference in Europe. Emtech Spain 2012 will takwe place November 22nd and 23rd in the city of Malaga and it will be an exceptional opportunity for scientists, technologist, business, innovators and entrepreneurs to attend a unique event which will change their vision of the near future and how to lead the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Madrid</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2012 15:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-participate-at-ibm-software-summit-madrid/</guid>
      <description> Kanteron Systems to participate at IBM Software Summit Start013#Start013, November 6th 2012, at Palacio Municipal de Congresos, Madrid (Spain). See you there!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to present a poster at DPA 2012</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-present-a-poster-at-dpa-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2012 21:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/09/kanteron-systems-to-present-a-poster-at-dpa-2012/</guid>
      <description>
Kanteron Systems will present the poster “Integrating Open Source Digital Pathology (PACS, LIS, DICOM or non-DICOM, EHR, web&amp;hellip;)” at the Digital Pathology Association’s (DPA) annual conference Pathology Visions, being held October 28-31, 2012 at the Hilton Hotel in Baltimore, MD (USA).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello to deliver two conferences at Colombia Radiology Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-to-deliver-two-conferences-at-colombia-radiology-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 08:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-to-deliver-two-conferences-at-colombia-radiology-congress/</guid>
      <description>During the Colombia Radiology Congress(August 4th &amp;amp; 5th, Cartagena de Indias, Colombia, Congress Center), Kanteron System‘s Marco Schiavottiello will deliver three conferences:
II Latin-American Congreso of Diagnostic Imaging Technologist, Academic Program, Barahona 1 room:
 Saturday 4th, 14:30-15:30: &amp;ldquo;DICOM for technologist&amp;rdquo; Saturday 4th, 16:00-16:30: &amp;ldquo;The rol of the technologist in the integration of new IT solutions in the radiology department&amp;rdquo; Saturday 4th, 17:00-17:30: &amp;ldquo;Image Post process: new technologies and the extended rol of the technologist&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Alvaro Gonzalez and Jorge Cortell talk about healthcare IT security at HOPE9</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2012 21:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/07/kanterons-alvaro-gonzalez-and-jorge-cortell-talk-about-healthcare-it-security-at-hope9/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘ Alvaro González(CTO) and Jorge Cortell(CEO) spoke today about &amp;ldquo;Digital Security in Health Care Institutions&amp;rdquo; during Hackers On Planet Earth number 9, New York, one of the most creative and diverse hacker events in the world (since 1994).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivers Master Class at London event</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2012 20:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/06/kanterons-marco-schiavottiello-delivers-master-class-at-london-event/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems‘s Marco Schiavottiello delivered a Master Class about the NHS Great Ormond Street‘s successful implementation by Kanteron Systems of a new Cardiac PACS, at London event &amp;ldquo;A patient centered approach&amp;rdquo; (Central Hall Westminster, Storey‘s Gate) July 4th, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to attend 2012 M&#43;Visión Consortium Biomedical Innovation Conference</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-attend-2012-m-visi%C3%B3n-consortium-biomedical-innovation-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2012 16:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/05/kanteron-systems-to-attend-2012-m-visi%C3%B3n-consortium-biomedical-innovation-conference/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems will attend and exhibit at MIT‘s 2012 M+Visión Consortium Biomedical InnovationConference in Madrid (Spain), June 5th and 6th.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems to sponsor SEACV‘s diagnostic photo contest</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-systems-to-sponsor-seacvs-diagnostic-photo-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2012 18:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-systems-to-sponsor-seacvs-diagnostic-photo-contest/</guid>
      <description>Kanteron Systems is proud to sponsor this year‘s diagnostic photo contestfrom the Spanish Society of Angiology and Vascular Surgery (SEACV).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron to sponsor TEDxValencia</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-to-sponsor-tedxvalencia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 16:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/04/kanteron-to-sponsor-tedxvalencia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanteron Systems presentation at NYC Health 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2012 20:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/03/kanteron-systems-presentation-at-nyc-health-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Jorge Cortell, Founder and President of Kanteron Systems, presented (soon available via livestream) yesterday some of the company‘s solutions geared towards reducing hospital readmission to a group of 70 professionals at the VNS of NY HQ (10 E 70th St., New York) during a Health 2.0 NYC – The New York Healthcare Innovation Groupmeeting.
Here are some of the twitter-comments from that session:
globalfjord ‏ @globalfjord
Health 2.0 companies to watch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HIMSS: Vendor-neutral archive can solve PACS problems</title>
      <link>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/himss-vendor-neutral-archive-can-solve-pacs-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.kanteron.com/2012/01/himss-vendor-neutral-archive-can-solve-pacs-problems/</guid>
      <description>According to a presentation by Michael J. Gray of Gray Consulting at a webinar on Jan. 26 hosted by the Healthcare Information and Management Systems Society (HIMSS):
 Implementation of a vendor-neutral archive (VNA) solves most of the problems associated with PACS, can save money over the long term and can prepare an enterprise to participate in a health information exchange (HIE)
 SourceKanteron Systems is a leading global supplier of vendor-neutral archive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>